Chapter 1

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Harry knew it was a stupid idea when he started to long for the sensations of portkey travel. Getting sucked into the Exit, he estimated felt like getting kicked in the balls with a seasickness curse. The wind rushing past was making Harry's cheeks flap and he couldn't even get out a proper manly scream of fright.

He grabbed onto his satchel with his right arm, not really trusting his magic to hold on to the bag. The feeling of falling while your body is being stretched from both top and bottom was as nauseating as it was painful. Compounding his discomfort was that the sheer amount of magic around him was blinding. He had his eyes shut tightly but the spell cast on them was forcing him to view all the surrounding magic and in a higher concentration that he'd ever seen before.

Harry idly wondered if he was scorching his optic nerve as he struggled to hold his wand up and cancel the magical sight spell. With a high-pitched grunt-like sound he succeeded.

Harry's glasses had so far managed to stay in place and he blinked his eyes open. He immediately regretted that move as he saw he was falling extremely fast through some sort of tube coated in blood and ectoplasm. The walls were semi-translucent and glancing through the pinkish haze in all directions there were endless arrays of more and more fleshy tubes.

Harry's vision blurred and everything around him seemed to gain a warming purple tinge. Oblivious to his continued descent, he thought back to his more often than not strained relationship with his best friends, Ron and Hermione. He wondered if maybe now Ginny could move on. He thought of the love he held for his parents and then Sirius.

There was a violent jerk to his right and Harry felt his body turn and rotate as gravity was pulling him, this time in a different direction. Thoughts of Sirius reminded Harry that he'd been sucked into the Exit and his vision cleared noticeably. Another jerk sent Harry careening forward, finally managing the elusive high-pitched manly scream that had evaded him earlier.

Harry could feel his stomach churning and really didn't want to know what puking in this ectoplasmic sorting system would do. Just when Harry didn't think he'd be able to make it, he was unceremoniously sent shooting out of the Exit, sliding across the stone floor, and crashing into the bottom set of stairs in the Death Chamber.

The moment Harry lifted his body up he began to retch all over the last step beneath him. He stopped to catch his breath for less than a second before resuming to empty the contents of his stomach. The thick puddle below him was spilling over the edge of the step and onto the floor.

Harry got a few more breaths of air and proceeded to dry heave every last painful drop he could. He wiped his mouth and looked up, only to find three Unspeakables surrounding him with their wands drawn and aimed at him.

Before he could react, two whispered disarming spells hit him, and his wand went flying. His body was forcefully pushed back onto the stairs. He opened his mouth to say something and only managed to belch a thick cloud of whitish smoke and dust.

Harry proceeded to cough and turned away from the welcoming committee. Thinking quickly he exclaimed, "Hang on. Let me drink the counter potion to my nundu's breath before you guys get sick."

Two of the Unspeakables cast immediate bubblehead charms, while the third had impressively managed to conjure or call an entire set of scuba gear complete with a working oxygen tank.

None of them made any move to stop Harry as he pulled a potion vial from his satchel and drank it immediately.

Harry let out a contented sigh as the steam whistled out his ears.

"You lied to us," the first Unspeakable stated. "That was pepper-up."

"True," Harry admitted tossing the empty vial into his bag. "But I didn't think you'd let me take it, if you knew it was pepper-up. Besides I was really exhausted and did you see how much I puked here? That's like what I eat in a week."

Finally after a moment of catching up to his surroundings and thinking clearer thanks to the potion, Harry realized that these Unspeakables didn't recognize him at all. Considering Harry definitely recognized Gruber, it was safe to assume this was an alternate dimension, one of the more intriguing potential destinations theorized for the Exit.

Seeking confirmation, Harry asked Gruber. "Do you have a brother that's also an Unspeakable?"

Gruber looked over towards his colleague and back at Harry. He spoke with a thick Slavic accent and was clearly sore about the issue. "If you must know my sister retired from the Ministry three weeks ago. She wasted her pension on a gender reassignment potion. I knew mother breast fed him too long."

"Wow," Harry uncertainly answered. "Okay."

"You're another dimension traveler, aren't you?" The lead Unspeakable asked.

"Easy guys," Harry tried to calm them with a smile, holding up his hands and acting harmless. "I'm one of you. Hold on, you said another? Did Sirius Black perchance come through here?"

The lead Unspeakable glanced at Gruber and then the woman to his left, all three of them still keeping their wands trained on Harry.

Hoping for a little less hostility, and fearing the idea that criminals sentenced to death may have just popped out into this world to cause problems, Harry explained. "Yeah, I think I am dimension traveler, considering I recognize Gruber there who in my world has a brother that's also an agent. And none of you seem to recognize me. I guess I'm not part of the Department in this world?"

The Unspeakables seemed to relax just slightly after catching each other's posture. "Sirius Black you're after?"

Harry nodded eagerly, jumping at the opening for a little information digging. Thinking of the role he should play, "Escaped convict Black? You betcha."

"We interrogated him," the lead Unspeakable said, standing straighter. "He's innocent of the charges you imprisoned him for."

"I know," Harry agreed, trying to imagine how the average Ministry worker would handle this. "But the law is the law. And he broke out of Azkaban. All breakouts get magically drained solitude or the Kiss."

"Excuse me?"

Harry puffed himself up proudly. "No man is above the law. Not even an innocent one."

The female was clearly confused by Harry's words and inched closer. "Who are you?"

"Come on guys, I'm one of you," Harry said, getting the feeling the walls were closing in on him.

"Your name," the lead Unspeakable ordered while slipping into a defensive stance.

Harry bit his lip for a second, and knew that if word got out he was a dimension traveler, he'd become rather well known, at least in certain circles, much quicker than he'd like. Not to mention the bloody red tape he'd no doubt have to go through. "I think for the sake of both our dimensions-" Harry cut off as he stepped back, twisting his body from three incoming spells. He avoided the stunner and the first body bind, but the second body bind clipped him on the shin.

Harry felt his body stiffen and he struggled to move his arms and legs. He was about to snap the weak spell when the female on his left ran up to him, and slapped a pair of magic inhibiting handcuffs over both of his wrists in a very precise and practiced motion.

Knowing he had an advantage, Harry decided to play along and accept his apparent defeat.

"We are going to interrogate you with Veritaserum," said the lead Unspeakable. "Standard operating procedure, you understand."

Harry raised a curious eyebrow. "You have a standard operating procedure for dimension travelers?"

The lead Unspeakable frowned at Harry and stared silently at him.

Harry made a show of wilting under the powerful stare and jumped at the opportunity. Slowly lifting his head to look the Unspeakable right back in the eye, Harry asked, "Was Sirius Black the last person you interrogated?"

Seizing advantage of the eye contact, Harry slipped into the Unspeakable's consciousness and caught glimpses of the memories flashing by that his words stirred. He saw the paperwork and discovered this was Senior Agent David Downing. The most interesting thing Harry managed to glean was the date of Sirius's arrival was April 5, 2006, or more accurately only two months ago today, the same day of Harry's only success with the Exit.

"Dammit," Downing cursed looking away, pushing Harry out of his mind as quickly as he could. "Keep your shields up and don't look this bugger in the eye."

"Agent Downing, is it?" Harry greeted, enjoying the victorious pain of being discovered and ejected. "Just wanted to keep you on your toes. A little reminder that magic inhibiting cuffs only stop magic from the wrists outward."

Downing sent a stunner at Harry, who dodged the spell. "Hey!" Harry argued. "I'm wearing cuffs. I'm coming peacefully. No need to be rude."

"Gruber, get his bag," Downing instructed while vanishing the puke from the steps. He turned to Harry, almost daring him to try Legilimency again. "And you lead the way towards the interrogation rooms on level eight."

Harry nodded, mentally cataloguing his wand was with Downing and bag was with Gruber. "Of course, Agent Downing," he said with a grin, knowing that just saying the Unspeakable's name riled him.

Harry's wrists were pulled together and bound by the magic of the cuffs. He calmly made his way up the steps, silently thanking the inventor of pepper-up once again.

The Unspeakables carefully followed Harry, all of them with their wands aimed at his back and a spell on the tip of their tongues.

Harry entered the circular spinning room and contemplated trying to escape here. But the spinning room had more identification and detection spells than he could hope to avoid. He turned towards the Unspeakables to get a glance of how they carried themselves and seek out any advantages.

"Face forward," Downing ordered. "Or we may misinterpret your attempts at coming peacefully."

Harry turned back around and doubted he'd be able to wrestle all three of their wands from them simultaneously. Breaking their necks was out of the question but that didn't stop him from once again wishing he were evil, for simplicity's sake. His best option was to use his magical arms to stun them, which would probably sap most of his energy. He quietly led the Unspeakables past the front desk that was being manned by the same witch as Harry had seen this morning.

Harry silently thanked his luck that the lift was empty when the doors opened. The three Unspeakables strategically maneuvered to surround him. Agent Downing pressed the button for level eight, keeping the tip of his wand aimed at Harry's neck.

Harry took a deep breath knowing this was going to be exhausting. The very second the lift doors closed, six invisible magical arms sprung to silent life extended from his body. Three of them snaked their way unnoticed and hovered right behind the base of the Unspeakables' necks, charging with energy. Hoping this would work, Harry willed the three arms simultaneously forward, hitting the Unspeakables with stunning spells.

All four people in the lift collapsed to the floor. The three Unspeakables crumpled because they were knocked unconscious, and Harry fell due to the sudden extreme draw on his magic.

Harry caught his breath, while the three other invisible arms retrieved his wand, grabbed his bag, and used the key to remove the magic inhibiting cuffs. He decided a pair of magic inhibiting cuffs could be pretty useful and stashed them with their key in his satchel. He steadied himself and stood, wavering as his equilibrium shifted. He knew he'd be paying for this later, but he summoned another potion vial and downed a second dose of pepper-up.

Steam shot out, hot and raw, scorching his inner ears. He was going to be down for the count when this wore off, but he needed to get away from here if he was going to keep his secrets intact.

Feeling that third wind kick in, Harry decided on a pair of layered memory charms. Just before he could cast the memory alteration, he heard the lift chime arriving at level eight. He quickly pulled the three unconscious bodies off to the side and hopefully out of view. He needed his luck to hold up as the lift doors opened, desperately hoping no one wanted to get on the lift at this floor.

Harry stuck his head out into level eight and saw a few Aurors looking toward him inquisitively. "This isn't the atrium," Harry announced smacking himself in the forehead as he quickly pushed the button inside the lift. He kept himself positioned in front of the Unspeakables wondering if perhaps this was the longest amount of time a pair of lift doors had ever stayed open.

The Aurors snickered at the loud sound of someone smacking himself in the head but went right back to their own business ignoring the unidentified, seemingly unaccompanied young man lost in the Ministry.

Once he was alone again, Harry focused immediately on a subtle memory alteration that would be hard to identify unless you knew it was there. Leaving the memories of their interaction intact, Harry changed their perception of him into that of a young buxom blonde woman. He shifted their memories of questions about Sirius Black into questions about Lucius Malfoy.

After applying a glamour charm that made him appear to match their altered memories, Harry locked them in body binds and woke the three Unspeakables up. He spoke with a feminine sneer and drawl, "Your bloody shields are keeping my spell out, but I doubt you can resist it when you're staring me in the eye. Obliviate!"

Harry did a simplistic memory modification charm this time, wiping out the last half hour from their minds. While still dazed from the memory charm that he wanted them to find, Harry transfigured the three Unspeakables into three shiny silver coins and canceled his glamour charm. The entire process took less than a minute from conceptualization to execution.

When the doors reopened at the atrium, Harry calmly exited carrying his satchel under his arm. As he walked past the fountain, he tossed the three coins into the water. The human to inanimate transfiguration was set to be released in exactly fifteen minutes, well after he was long gone.

Harry strolled out of the Ministry of Magic satisfied he'd made his escape and about as covered as he was going to get without doubling back to the Department of Mysteries. Looking up into the early afternoon London sun, he saw a world of answers to his questions about Sirius and the Exit all around him. He just had to find them.

All signs indicated Harry was in an alternate dimension, existing fully independent of his world. Since he hadn't been recognized, it was safe to assume the Harry Potter of this world was either dead or not quite as famous.

He had his wand and his satchel, with his research notes on the Exit and a few emergency potions. He had roughly fifty galleons in a small pouch, about ninety pounds in his wallet, and an absolute certainty that trying to use his credit cards would be a bad idea.

Harry walked to a nearby muggle café, ordered a meal to help fill his empty stomach, and took a moment to think things over. He wasn't sure if he'd be able to go back through the Veil and he wasn't about to try until he had more answers. He was tired enough that he wouldn't even entertain the possibility without more rest.

He could go to Hogwarts, but he wasn't sure whether Dumbledore or McGonagall might still be alive in this world. Harry realized that Voldemort could be alive in this world as well, in which case Hogwarts could have been razed to the ground or taken over. By the same measure Hogwarts could be a fashion institute and the Harry Potter of this world could be the androgynous one snootily using a fake French accent at the door.

With no idea about anything in this world, Harry focused on the best solution to most of his problems: finding Sirius.

Harry considered hitting Diagon Alley and staying at the Leaky Cauldron, but when he stood up after his meal he realized just how tired he was quickly getting. He decided to head to the one place that would feel most like home.

Harry walked out of sight and apparated to a back yard he was intimately familiar with. There was trash rotting and a completely unkempt growth crawling up the side of the building. He smiled to see there wasn't a Fidelius Charm as he gazed up the back side of Number 12 Grimmauld Place.

The back door was stuck shut, but an alohomora and a running start fixed that problem.

Harry crashed into the pantry, just off the side of the kitchen and fell to the floor skidding through a thick layer of dust. Cobwebs that would fit Acromantulas were littered all over the place. Sheets covered furniture and a strong, stale musty smell permeated the manor.

There was no sign of Sirius here, nor was there any sign anyone had been here in decades.

Harry stood back up and felt a wave of dizziness wash over him. It appeared like his body was going to take its nap here whether he liked it or not.

Stumbling into the living room Harry scourgified the immediate area and pulled a sheet off of the large couch. He quickly put up a few rudimentary protection wards and collapsed onto the couch. He grabbed onto the magically cleaned sheet and pulled it over himself while already in the process of snoring.

Sixteen hours later, Harry yawned and felt a weight on his chest as he exhaled. He opened his eyes and found himself staring into a pair of impossibly wide bright eyes staring right back at him.

"Is it true?" the squeaky voice inquired hopefully. "New Master has returned?"

Harry shrieked as he realized a wrinkly old house elf had mounted him in his sleep. He swung his arm wildly and swatted the elf across the room into the wall. A loud crunch and clatter as the elf landed stirred a small cloud of dust into the air.

"It's true!" The elf cheered wickedly. "Master has punished! Oh Master!"

Harry wiped the eye boogers from his face and took a better look at the wrinkled little urchin. "Kreacher?"

"Master knows Kreacher?" Kreacher cheered before smacking himself in the head. "Stupid Kreacher! Of course Master knows Kreacher!"

Harry wiped his eyes once more, to make sure they weren't playing tricks on him.

Kreacher ran up to Harry and hugged his leg. "Kreacher's been bad! Punish Kreacher, Master! Then Kreacher will start cleaning this place up."

"You want to be punished?" Harry inquired having always suspected most elves were masochists.

"Kreacher deserves it!" the elf gasped and slapped a hand over his mouth. "Kreacher will sharpen all the blood traitor torturing tools!"

"Wait, Kreacher!"

"Yes, Master?" Kreacher said sticking his rear end out waiting to be punished.

Harry just looked at the old elf that was practically begging to be spanked and completely forgot what he was going to say.

"Would you like me to go steal one of the neighborhood muggles for you, Master?"

"No," Harry answered immediately. "I just… you know what. Forget it. It doesn't matter. Do whatever you want."

"Kreacher will start cleaning the blades, chains, and tenderizing mallets! Oh it will be ever so much fun, Master!"

Harry watched the disturbed house elf scurry away. Considering the first Kreacher Harry met had chosen death over serving blood traitors, Harry was once again reminded that this was a completely different dimension with a different history.

There was a loud screech of metal dragging across metal from upstairs. Harry decided to go get some breakfast and begin the search for his godfather. He would put off to later the decision of ever returning to Grimmauld Place again.

Harry located his satchel, cast a cleaning charm over his robes, and focused on Diagon Alley. With a soft pop he apparated away, reappearing in the magical alley.

With practiced ease, Harry took stock of his surroundings, seeing no immediate threats. There were a few people walking around, but not an exorbitant amount. There wasn't a strong sense of impending doom, but this wasn't the carefree relaxation that Wizarding Britain had become after the destruction of his world's Voldemort. Those people had been too relaxed and complacent. The people Harry saw here were cautious and aware, many of them sneaking glances at him before moving along to continue their business.

Unsure what to make of this, Harry ventured towards the center of the Alley, and spotted a diner with patio seating. It looked pretty busy which was what Harry was looking for. He bought a copy of the Daily Prophet at the front counter and was seated outdoors, with his back to a wall, so he could watch the people in the alley while listening in to others' conversations.

He ordered a simple breakfast platter, and was keeping his eyes and ears open. Sipping on his juice, Harry opened the Daily Prophet and saw the front page. June 6, 2006 was the date indicating he hadn't moved temporally at all through the Exit. The entire front page was devoted to England's chances in the upcoming Quidditch World Cup. There were articles on the team, the event, the competition, but not a single mention of Death Eaters or Voldemort. Harry took this as a good sign.

He watched a familiar brown-haired woman walk into the apothecary across the street unable to connect a name to her face, but pretty sure she had been a year behind him and a Hufflepuff. He continued eating and flipping through the paper when a small article caught his eye and Harry began to choke. Apparently Death Eater attacks didn't warrant the front page. Or any of the first six pages for that matter.

"Careful there, buddy," a man who had been seated next to him said. He began to pat Harry on the back to keep him from choking.

"Thanks," Harry said getting a hold of himself. One or two sudden realizations were understandable, but to find out Death Eater attacks didn't warrant the front page, to find out that Voldemort was still around, that the muggles in the article were Vernon and Petunia Dursley, and that the Assistant Director of the Department of Magical Law Enforcement, James Potter, had intervened caused Harry to gasp in the middle of swallowing. "Sorry. Went down the wrong pipe."

"Breakfast can be a tricky mistress," the man said with a smile.

Harry recognized the man seated next to him despite not having seen him in over a decade. "It's the forks that trip me up. I keep grabbing the wrong end."

"As long as you remember which hole in your face to put the food, you should be okay," the man nodded extending his hand in greeting. "Florean Fortescue."

Harry shook his hand. "I'm Harry."

"Aren't we all?" Florean retorted before glancing at Harry's table. "You want some company?"

"Sure," Harry said eager to get a few answers from someone he relatively trusted and was obviously willing to talk. He moved his newspaper out of the way while Florean brought his plate over with him.

"So what did you read that caused you to inhale your scrambled eggs?" Florean asked as he took advantage of the better jams on Harry's table. He looked up and saw Harry staring at him curiously. "I happened to be looking over when your eyes went wide and you began to choke."

Harry nodded, though erring on the side of caution. "I was surprised to read about a Death Eater attack to be honest."

"Really?" Florean asked curiously. "What was so surprising about that?"

"Well, I know I've got the accent nailed," Harry grinned. "But I'm not actually from around here. And considering I remembered something about an attack many years ago, I was surprised they were still going on."

Florean shook his head. "They're sporadic, but they've been around for what feels like as long as I can remember. It's been years since my shop had any spell damage I needed repaired, but the threat is always there."

"You don't seem to let it get you down," Harry commented.

"I sell ice cream," Florean grinned. "All I deal in are smiles."

"Never had the taint of the war darken your doorstep?"

"War?" Florean asked curiously in between bites of breakfast. "What war? The Death Eaters and the Dark Lord are terrorists, thugs, at best. A couple of my neighbors were killed in an attack. It wasn't some glorious battle nor was their home part of some strategic plan. It was just an attack. Too many good people have been caught in attacks, but to call what those terrorists do a war gives them a respect they've not earned."

Harry nodded. "I'm sorry to hear that. About your neighbors I mean. It's probably the fact that it's not descended into all out war that's kept the whole thing going for so long."

Florean was wiping his mouth having finished his meal. "You certainly have interesting ideas about pleasant breakfast conversation."

"My apologies," Harry nodded. "You asked what startled me in the paper and my mind likes to go off on tangents."

"No apology needed," Florean waved him off. "I wasn't bothered in the slightest. But I should get back and prep my store for opening. It's been a pleasure, Harry."

"One last question," Harry interjected. "If you don't mind humoring me, but have you by chance seen Sirius Black?"

"The new one?"

Harry tried to mask his surprise. "There's more than one?"

"Sirius Black was a young man murdered twenty-five years ago," Florean explained swinging his cloak over his shoulders. "But another man with that name came into my shop just about a week ago with his cousin, Auror Tonks-Lupin."

"Thank you," Harry smiled. "Good luck on dealing with only smiles today."

Florean looked at the sky and saw the sun was shining brightly. "It's going to be a hot one. I doubt I'll need luck to have a very busy and profitable day."

Harry watched the pleasant man walk briskly down the alley towards the ice cream parlor and thought about his first solid lead. It appeared that as much as things change, some things, like Tonks and Moony, stay the same no matter what dimension you land in.

Harry left a galleon and seven sickles to cover his breakfast and tip. He had to be careful with his money as he didn't have much with him.

All the good wizarding records for locating someone often required identification and were handled at the Ministry, which was not a place Harry wanted to go if he didn't have to. Thus he began walking towards the Leaky Cauldron intent on venturing out into non-magical London.

"G'morning, Tom," Harry greeted as he walked into the Leaky Cauldron.

"Morning," Tom nodded looking at Harry curiously unable to recognize him. "Anything I can do for you, Mr.…?"

"Harry's fine," Harry said extending his hand to shake. "And I was hoping you might have a phone book and a phone I could use?"

"If you want a room, local calls are included but otherwise, the pay phone right out front has a book," Tom said pointing towards the street. "I check every morning to make sure no one's run off with it."

"Thanks," Harry nodded and walked out into the muggle side of London. He picked up the phone book and quickly flipped to the L section. Just as he'd hoped Lupin, Remus was listed but not at any address Harry remembered. He picked up the phone and dialed the number letting it ring for twenty seconds before admitting defeat that no one was answering.

He walked back into the Leaky Cauldron. "I don't suppose you know where Old Ford Road is?"

"Runs through Bethnal Green as I recall," Tom answered.

"There an apparition point there?" Harry asked.

Tom nodded. "Sure. Probably will drop ya at the tube station, but it'll get you close."

"Thanks," Harry nodded and walked out. He made sure he was clear of any wards on the Leaky Cauldron and out of view from any muggles. Focusing on Bethnal Green, Harry apparated away. He got directions from a young woman in the tube station and found himself walking down the road listed as Remus' address.

Harry couldn't remember the numbers other than a three and a seven were involved so he cast the spell that would allow him to see magic. He began walking down the road, directly across from a nicely wooded park when he noticed a cellar glowing with magic.

Harry was going to investigate and see if this was the place when he spotted a large black dog, sunning itself in the park across the street. His face split into a bright grin as he walked up to the extremely familiar mutt that was obliviously licking himself in a potentially embarrassing fashion.

"You know I think it's as clean as it's going to get," Harry stated having successfully snuck up on the dog.

The grim-looking canine stopped immediately, lifted his head, and slowly turned towards the vaguely recognizable voice with an expression as close to surprise as a dog could possibly have.

"Crikey, Padfoot!" Harry yelped throwing an arm up to cover his eyes. "Put that lipstick away."

Chapter 3

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

"I really thought you might have moved on."

"Oh Harry," Ginny greeted lightly reaching down to kiss him on the cheek. "When will you realize we're going to be together forever?"

Harry shuddered slightly at the chilling sensation of her lips on him.

"You're a bloody ghost!" Sirius exclaimed as his mouth finally caught up to his brain.

Ginny smiled at Sirius and perched herself ethereally on the armrest of Harry's chair. "I'm in the seventh year of my death."

"And you look great," Sirius admitted with a grin.

"Sirius!" Harry groaned. "She doesn't need any encouragement."

Ginny struck a pose and pushed her ghostly chest out. "You can't beat a Killing Curse for preserving beauty and avoiding disfigurement. It's even better than a basilisk stare."

"Hogwarts robes always did it for me," Sirius admitted grinning brightly at her.

"Whoa," Harry stood up quickly. "Back it up there, dirty old man."

"He's so protective of me," Ginny said with a saucy giggle.

"I'm not protective…" Harry stopped and refused to be baited. He turned to glare at the ghost when Sirius suddenly burst out laughing.

"Oh this is priceless!" Sirius snickered.

"I'm glad my life amuses you," Harry grumbled.

"I just realized she's anchored to you! She's going to haunt you for eternity!"

"We're destined to be together," Ginny agreed with a smile.

"This isn't destiny, Ginny. You're dead. I'm alive and attracted to girls with a pulse."

"You'll come around," Ginny nodded with certainty.

"Maybe a necromancer will come around," Harry mumbled.

"Fate has taken us across the boundaries of our world together. We're clearly soul mates."

"We are not soul mates," Harry argued. "I think I would have felt it, if my soul mate had died. Actually wouldn't I die if my soul mate died?"

"No," Sirius cheerfully interjected. "You're Harry Potter."

Harry growled at Sirius.

"The Soul Mate-Who-Lived," Sirius added before slapping a hand over an invisible poking. "Oww! My eye! Dammit Harry, that really hurts."

"You were protected by the magic-less properties of that cell, Harry," Ginny said shaking her head. "We've been over this numerous times and you refuse to see reason."

"You died while he was being held captive?" Sirius asked curiously.

Ginny nodded happily. "I wasn't able to draw on his strength. It's the only explanation for what happened."

"Wait a second," Sirius exclaimed. "I just realized I was right! Ginny's alive and well in this dimension, and here her ghost is. You don't have to be dead there to reach an alternate dimension."

"But she's dead," Harry pointed out jerking his thumb towards the ghost.

"You said they had to be dead in the new dimension, and Ginny is definitely not dead here, last I heard at least." Sirius paused and turned towards the ghost. "Then again you just now showed up. Why is that? Ginny here's not dead, is she?"

Harry sighed and grumbled. "She's a young ghost and wasn't that smart to begin with."

"Hush," Ginny snapped before answering Sirius. "I doubt my counterpart is dead. My afterlife varies depending on my love's mood. Oh! This must be how we're supposed to be together. I'll rejoin my spirit with my counterpart's body so that we can live happily ever after!"

Harry ignored the ghost and argued with Sirius. "It still isn't two matching live people in the same dimension so my theory holds true."

"No," Sirius disagreed. "You said our counterparts had to be dead to get to that dimension. You've just proven that's not true if one of us is dead and even that may not matter at all."

"You really want that Order of Moron First Class, don't you?"

Sirius grinned unrepentantly. He turned to Ginny and tactfully asked, "Hey! Were you pregnant with his kid? Is that why you're anchored to him?"

Ginny looked surprised for a moment and rubbed her ghostly belly. "I… I never thought of that."

"We never had sex!" Harry added, believing this to be relevant information.

Ginny shrugged. "But we kissed a lot."

Harry poured himself a little more firewhiskey having had this conversation many times before.

"So what happened when your soul mate was unable to provide you his strength?" Sirius asked Ginny with a grin, knowing it would rankle Harry.

"Here it comes," Harry mumbled walking towards the kitchen not wanting to hear this story again. "Don't forget your shovel."

Ginny watched him walk away sadly. "He still doesn't know how to cope with my death."

Sirius bit his lip. "I can see that."

"Anyways," Ginny happily segued. "I didn't know it at the time, but Harry had been kidnapped and was being held prisoner by the Dark Lord. He doesn't talk about it much, but I'm sure whatever he may have told you wasn't half as bad as it probably really was."

Sirius nodded. "I'm familiar with my godson's gift for underestimation, though it's nice to see he's grown more confident and even proud of some of his accomplishments."

"And hotter too!" Ginny added.

"He gets that from me."

"You are looking surprisingly good, aren't you?" Ginny said after giving Sirius a brief inspection. "But I only have eyes for my Harry." Ginny sighed happily, looking down the hall into the kitchen.

"Anyways?"

"Right," Ginny recalled where she'd left off. "So it was early March and the first Hogsmeade weekend since the winter holidays. We were all eager to get outside the grounds and may have been a little too lax in our constant vigilance. I was walking to Madam Puddifoot's to ask her where she bought her cherubs—you know, to get a jump on next year's Valentine's Day plans for my sweetie—when we spotted some Death Eaters destroying Dervish and Banges."

Sirius just nodded, thinking Harry probably wished it had been Madam Puddifoot's getting destroyed.

"It was my seventh year, and I was leader of the DA. I sent two students to run back and shepherd everyone to the safety of the castle, while all capable wands were to follow me. I kept asking myself the question, 'What would Harry do?' We couldn't let the Death Eaters destroy Hogsmeade, so we decided to try and keep them busy until reinforcements from the castle could arrive.

"I gathered up all of my Gryffindor courage, strengthened my resolve as the Chosen One's predestined soul mate, and stepped out from behind our cover. That's when we first saw the man from my nightmares walking calmly out of Dervish and Banges just as the structure collapsed. The Dark Lord Voldemort himself was there."

Sirius could hear Harry's mumbling and grumbling from the kitchen and didn't think there would be a happy ending to this tale, particularly considering it was being told by a ghost.

"Tom looked genuinely surprised to see me standing proudly with twelve members of the DA behind me. I remembered how Harry led by example, teaching me not to fear the Dark Lord, and I ordered Voldemort to leave."

Sirius couldn't stop the laugh that escaped from him. He hurriedly covered his mouth at Ginny's angry stare and urged her to continue.

"Seeing as how we didn't react the way the Dark Lord expected, he wasn't sure how to deal with us. He lazily held his wand and asked, 'Do you not fear me?'" Ginny said with her voice deepened and eyes narrowed in concentration, demonstrating her best Voldemort impression.

"Fixed in my convictions, I confidently answered 'No!'" Ginny sighed and admitted softer, "But the effect was lessened by Owen Cauldwell raising his hand and admitting, 'I kind of fear you' at the same time as my declaration.

"Voldemort announced that he'd honor that honest fear with a quick and painless death. Next thing I knew a bright green Killing Curse was headed straight for Owen.

"I was wondering what was taking my sugar-bear so long when I realized what I had to do."

"Oh no," Sirius mumbled under his breath.

"I thought about nothing but my love for Harry and stepped right into the path of the curse. I held my wand firm and just as the death curse was a meter away I shouted 'Love Shield!'"

"Oh no," Sirius muttered staring at the ghost that enjoyed embellishment a little too much.

"Sadly my attempt to reflect the Killing Curse back at the Dark Lord was unsuccessful, though I'm proud to say it did provide my snookums with the necessary protection to defeat the Dark Lord."

"Hey!" Harry exclaimed marching back in from the kitchen. "We had a deal on no more snookums! And there's no such spell as Love Shield. Even if there was, the incantation certainly wouldn't be Love Shield."

"Lovus Shieldus?" Ginny mused aloud.

"Maybe Lovio Shieldium," Sirius suggested.

Harry stared at the ghost and his godfather in exasperation. "You're both purebloods. Don't either of you know Latin at all?"

"If it's not in a family motto," Sirius admitted with a shrug. "Although I think I should know the Latin word for love…"

"I never had any interest in learning Latin," Ginny commented. "Hermione would probably know."

"Spermatozoa!" Sirius declared triumphantly. "That's Latin for love. Or something close to it. I think."

Harry slumped back in his chair, not even caring that he just swung his arm straight through Ginny's incorporeal body. He rubbed the bridge of his nose thinking that there were some things best left as mysteries.

Sirius watched Ginny staring at Harry all googly-eyed. "So no luck on reflecting that Killing Curse? Or surviving it?"

Ginny shook her head. "It hit me and then it all went black. I found out the rest later when I appeared by my very sad little Harry bear."

"What was the rest?" Sirius asked curiously. "Or do I not want to know?"

Ginny glanced at Harry and silently requested permission.

"He probably doesn't want to know but go ahead," Harry said nodding at Ginny.

"Obviously we don't have first hand information," Ginny explained. "But Voldemort killed the twelve other members of the DA."

Sirius winced.

"Oh it gets better," Harry said with a weak laugh.

"Voldemort then animated their corpses and they marched the path back to Hogwarts," Ginny continued.

Sirius winced again.

"Headmistress McGonagall saw them in the distance and thought they were alive and being escorted to safety by some inhabitants of the Forbidden Forest." Ginny paused to make a face of disgust. "It was just some thestrals chewing on a couple of fifth years and licking up the blood trailing the group."

Sirius winced but was reminded they'd missed lunch.

"And so who does just about everyone blame for this tragedy?" Harry ruefully grinned. "Obviously it's the fault of the kidnapping victim, who at this time was still locked in a magic-less cell."

"Well it certainly doesn't sound like you did anything to help them," Sirius pointed out.

"I didn't know it was happening and I kinda had my own problems to deal with."

Ginny softly frowned. "The vast majority of parents did make Harry into a bit of a scapegoat."

"Vast majority," Harry grumbled. "They all did. Your parents included."

"They lost their baby girl," Ginny argued with a pout. "And I think they were jealous that I chose to spend eternity with the love of my life rather than my family."

"The Weasleys blamed you?" Sirius asked skeptically.

Harry shook his head. "Not outright or anything. They defended me from all the editorials calling me dangerous and a bad influence, but… it was a lot more awkward the few times I'd visit the Burrow, especially when ghost girl here came out to play."

"How did the Prophet and its collectively minded readership make this little leap of logic?"

Harry shrugged. "I told the DA not to fear his name. That he was just a wizard who went about as bad as one can go. And despite the fact that it had been a year and a half since I'd even been to a DA meeting, according to the public I'm the one who convinced students they were soldiers, told them that they were old enough to stand up to Death Eaters, and I'm the one who led them to a slaughter."

"I said I was sorry," Ginny mumbled looking ashamed.

"I know," Harry admitted. "I should have been a bit clearer in that fearing a made-up name is silly, but fearing an extremely powerful ruthless dark wizard is just common sense."

"Ahh," Sirius nodded. "Wizards aren't too good with that stuff."

Harry looked at Sirius in confusion.

"Common sense, I mean," Sirius added. "Your mother always told me that instead of common sense, wizards got magic. Which actually explained quite a bit," Sirius said thinking of the people that got the most magic including various Dark Lords and Albus Dumbledore.

A loud crack from by the front door announced an arrival by apparition.

"Moony?" Sirius called out curiously.

"I tell you, Padfoot," Remus called back. "Some muggles get so worked up and angry at me. Like it's my fault they can't…" Remus stopped as he entered his living room and spotted the ghost of Ginny Weasley, a young man he couldn't quite place, and Sirius grinning at him, clearly a little inebriated.

Remus closed his eyes and counted to ten. When he opened them all three people were still there, smiling and waving at him.

"Please tell me you didn't kill Miss Weasley," Remus begged of his houseguest.

"Remus," Sirius proudly introduced. "I would like you to meet my godson, Harry Potter."

Remus turned to look at Harry closer. "Bugger me. He's even got that scar you talked about."

"Sirius," Harry whined turning towards his godfather.

"Hey," Sirius defended himself. "It's pretty damn hard to talk about our dimension without that story coming up. And Moony, before you freak out this is the Ginny Weasley of my original dimension, who is bound for eternity to her soul mate, Harry."

Ginny curtsied towards Remus, while Harry just groaned.

"I didn't think one soul bonded could die and the other live," Remus stated.

"Thank you," Harry boisterously agreed. "It's because she's not my soul mate. Most of the time I can barely tolerate her."

"Of course I didn't think you could get hit with a Killing Curse and live either," Remus added grinning like a Marauder. He walked over towards Harry extended his hand to shake, "Pleased to meet you."

Harry forced a fake smile and shook Remus' hand. "You're a barrel of laughs already."

Remus nodded towards Ginny. "I thought you looked a bit younger, though your counterpart here could easily still fit into her school robes."

Remus brushed Sirius' feet off the couch and poured himself a drink settling down in the cleared space on the couch. "So are we celebrating or mourning or both?"

"As it turns out," Sirius happily explained while Harry seemed a little put out at the lack of reaction from Remus. "Harry, here, began working on the veil back in our dimension just a few months back. He's the one that triggered it to spit me out when it did."

"Really?" Remus grinned, sipping his firewhiskey. "And now you're here to clean up your litter?"

"We've decided we're going to stay," Ginny announced gleefully.

Harry saw Remus looked worried that he might be running out of couches and guest beds real soon and explained, "I still don't know exactly how I triggered it two months ago, but the Exit changed significantly on our side. I find it hard to believe that it's merely coincidence Sirius got spit out on this side the same day."

"And you?"

"Yes well," Harry fidgeted a little. "I've been working on the Exit and had a little accident yesterday."

"You just got here yesterday?" Remus inquired. "Sirius was healing for several weeks."

"I could've located this lunkhead sooner, but it was quite tiring crossing dimensions and then escaping from the Unspeakables."

"You what?" Sirius yelped unaware his godson was a fugitive.

Harry smirked. "Not all of us are so helpless and willing to submit to memory charms and veritaserum."

"Wouldn't they know you're here and be looking for you?" Remus asked curiously.

Harry shrugged. "I'm hoping not, but it's definitely possible."

Another crack from the entryway indicated another arrival. Tonks' voice carried into the living room. "Sirius? You here?"

"Yup, in here," Sirius called back.

"Pretend I just subtly inquired about a blonde veela-like woman associated with Lucius Malfoy," Tonks yelled back, still out of view. "The Department of Mysteries is in a right tizzy because they think she came from the veil yesterday."

Harry grinned brightly at Remus and Sirius inquiring looks.

"A blonde woman?" Sirius repeated.

"Yeah," Tonks called back. "Apparently she took out three Unspeakables but did a crap job of memory charming them." Tonks walked into the living room just as she finished and stopped curiously. "Err… hello?"

"Tonks," Sirius waved at the stupidly grinning young man. "I'd like you to meet my godson, Harry."

"Hi," Harry grinned at her.

"Bugger me," Tonks whispered doing a double take at all the smiling faces. She only now noticed the ghost hovering behind Harry. "Ginny!"

"Hi Tonks," Ginny said with a small wave.

"It's not this dimension's Ginny," Remus assured her. "It's theirs."

"What the hell did you do, Harry?" Sirius asked curiously. "Come through the veil polyjuiced as a hooker?"

Harry shook his head and gave Tonks a long look. "You're not going to arrest me, are you?"

"Doubtful considering the way those two boys are smiling," Tonks answered pointing to the two Marauders on the couch.

Harry nodded. "I only had about forty-five seconds so I did a pretty slick memory alteration, substituting my presence for a large-breasted blonde woman, and my questions about Sirius for questions about Malfoy."

"Veela-like my arse," Tonks grumbled.

"I followed it up with a clumsy brute force memory modification," Harry explained. "I didn't have time to check what sort of alarms I triggered, and I figured that the mess of trying to clean out the second memory charms would further hide the first ones. Especially since the first ones were only alterations leaving no blanks."

"You did that in forty-five seconds?"

Harry nodded pleased with the apparent success of his ploy.

"Hey!" Sirius exclaimed. "This is perfect! Tonks can be hunting you down the same way Kingsley 'hunted' me."

Tonks had heard about Sirius' escape and life on the run and was considering the idea.

"We can feed you whatever clues we want to make up," Sirius continued.

Tonks agreed the idea had merit. "It does get me out of work anytime I want to just be in public with you," she said looking at Sirius, "under the guise of you being uniquely suited to spotting someone from your dimension."

"That doesn't sound very responsible," Remus commented with a frown.

"Oh get off your high horse," Tonks scolded pouring herself a drink. "These are the same idiots who won't even let you get in a job in the wizarding world."

"Yeah, what do you do?" Harry asked curiously looking at Remus. "You said muggles get worked up and angry at you."

Remus saw Sirius was going to laugh and immediately defended himself. "They give me three days off every full moon, and it's easy work."

Sirius was still snickering.

"It pays for this place," Remus said with a clear undertone reminding Sirius that he had no home or money in this dimension.

Harry saw Tonks was rolling her eyes seated across from Remus and Sirius. "What is it?"

"Are you familiar with computers?" Remus asked looking at Harry.

"Vaguely," Harry said having sat in front of one for about an hour at a muggle library.

"I'm a senior consultant in client relations for technical assistance," Remus explained. He saw Harry didn't follow that at all. "Tech support on the phone," Remus clarified.

"Oh," Harry caught on. "I had no idea you knew so much about computers."

"Padfoot," Remus scolded noticing Sirius was about to burst.

"He doesn't," Sirius exclaimed mirthfully. "He doesn't know anything about computers."

Harry watched Remus smother a very Marauder-like smile.

"I know about computers," Remus countered. "I just don't know anything about fixing them, per se."

"So what do you do?"

"Tell people to reboot," Remus shrugged. "And if that doesn't work, they have to cover shipping costs to mail it back to us."

"That's it!" Sirius chuckled. "That's all he does."

"No," Tonks jumped in. "He plays a lot of computer games too."

"Careful there, young lady," Remus warned with a smile. "I'm not above breaking out some very incriminating photos."

Tonks knew exactly which ones he was talking about. "You wouldn't."

"That's right," Sirius jumped in and looked over at Remus. "You mentioned something about a spanking?"

"I don't want to hear this," Harry interrupted, while Ginny smiled next to him. "I kind of do."

"And you were trying to make me feel guilty about responsibility," Tonks grumbled.

"There's no honor in the work I do," Remus said looking at Tonks. "You took an oath and wanted a career where you could help people, where you can do the right thing. Your responsibility is-"

"Whatever Dad," Tonks grumbled and stuck out her tongue.

Harry wondered how close this dimension's Tonks and Remus were, because when Harry left Tonks was still constantly wanting to be near Remus and holding his hand. These two seemed to have a much more blasé dynamic and Harry wondered when the honeymoon had ended. "So Tonks, how long have you been Auror Tonks-Lupin here?"

Tonks was counting in her head. "Umm…I've been an Auror fourteen years now."

Harry shook his head. "I meant how long have you had the Lupin tacked on to the end of your last name?"

Tonks looked at Harry in confusion. "Since I was eight."

Harry gasped and snapped his head over at to look at Remus' proud smile in abject horror.

Sirius saw Harry's pained face and explained, "Her parents and godparents were killed the same night we were, Halloween 1981. Guardianship then would have gone to me as the only relative her parents acknowledged. I left everything to Remus, so rather than risk her being sent to the Lestranges or Malfoys, Moony here got custody legally through the muggle system and raised her on his own."

Tonks shrugged seeing Harry looked struck speechless. "I remember my real parents, but I liked calling Moony my Daddy and took his last name. Most people think Tonks is my first name which suits me just fine. Sirius already told us that my parents lived in your world. Why?"

The ghostly Ginny was staring open-mouthed at Tonks and Remus completely speechless while Harry fell to the floor unable to breathe he was laughing so hard. Every moment Harry looked up to begin speaking, he would collapse again and slap his hand on the floor.

"I don't think my parents dying is really all that funny," Tonks added feeling a bit annoyed.

"What's your problem, Harry?" Sirius asked. Seeing Harry was still no help, Sirius looked towards the ghost and asked, "Ginny?"

Ginny licked her ghostly lips and calmly explained, "Your name is Tonks-Lupin in our world too."

Sirius furrowed his brow. "What do you…" He quickly spun around to stare straight at Remus and sharply pointed an accusing finger. "You!"

Harry was nearly unintelligible but in between his racks of laughter he added, "I think you call him Daddy there too."

Remus looked just as confused before he realized exactly what the addition of his last name implied. He snarled angrily, "That filthy pedophile!"

Tonks was horribly lost now and looked towards her father. "Who?"

"Me!" Remus exclaimed poking himself in the chest.

"What?" Tonks asked again, unable to even consider the cruel truth staring her right in the face. "What does that have to do with my name?"

"You're my victim!" Remus explained far louder than necessary.

Harry was still snickering but composed himself enough to add, "I believe the term we've been using is wife, but that works too."

"Oh god," Tonks wheezed turning green without using any metamorphmagus skill. "That's disgusting!"

"I know!" Remus said struggling to even look his daughter in the eye.

Sirius was clearly just as amused as Harry. "When did this happen?"

"Less than a year after your accidental pirouette," Harry answered. "But they didn't get married until after Voldemort was gone."

"That's- that's- that's so wrong," Tonks mumbled fearfully. "I mean, Moony's my dad!"

"Less than a year?" Remus repeated with a pained face. "That's practically cradle robbing. Don't I even know the age rule?"

"I know you do," Sirius stated. "You taught it to me when that third year grew those huge-"

"Vera Helbig!" Remus agreed. "Same thing happened here."

"And you asked me about the rule," Sirius exclaimed spinning around to point at the queasy looking Tonks. "Just a couple months before I left. Merlin, I thought you had the hots for Harry. That's why I encouraged special circumstances."

"Really?" Harry inquired waggling his eyebrows at Tonks.

"No offense Harry," Sirius explained. "But life expectancy for you was more often measured in weeks than years."

"Would someone care to explain this age rule to me?" Ginny interjected curiously.

"Half your age, plus seven," Sirius and Remus said in unison repeating the universally accepted measuring stick dividing healthy and unhealthy relationships.

Remus continued, "Rounding up for good measure. Meaning when I was 36, no wait, 37, the youngest I should date is 25, or 26 if you round up. That's why Tonks at 23 should've been off limits."

"There are a few other reasons I should've been off limits, Dad," Tonks added with a shiver.

"I need a drink," Remus said, shaking his head.

"Me too," Sirius agreed pouring large glasses for everyone.

"I need a memory charm," Tonks added, only half joking.

"Me too," Remus seconded.

"If it makes you feel any better," Harry said waiting until the other three were taking drinks. "Tonks was pregnant when I left."

Sirius spurted up his firewhiskey in laughter while Remus and Tonks both painfully swallowed the liquid in their mouths.

"Why would that make us feel better?" Remus asked giving Harry a dirty look.

Harry shrugged. "Well it made me feel a little better to tell you."

Tonks just rubbed her temples. "You know until that, I'd managed to convince myself our counterparts may never have…" She stopped herself from saying anything more.

"Of course you have," Ginny helpfully added. "Why even before my death, Tonks was telling me all about the benefits of werewolf strength and how frisky he'd get, the closer to the full moon it was. Hell, you guys even managed to synchronize your cycles."

Sirius and Harry found themselves briefly as horrified as Tonks and Remus were, before catching each other's eyes and cracking up.

Ginny as the calmest one in the room continued. "Something about the wolf being able to smell-"

"Stop!" Remus yelled. "Stop! For the love of Merlin, stop!"

All four people and a single ghost descended in silence, broken only by the occasional snicker or shudder.

Harry realized this was the sort of cruel joke that was going to last a lifetime and felt pity on the two Lupins for now. "Moving forward, what's the plan for tonight?"

"I don't know," Sirius said as Tonks and Remus seemed to be a little shell-shocked still. "Tonks? Any luck?"

"What?" Tonks asked.

"Any luck on locating us a Lord?"

"Oh sorry," Tonks said. "Actually yeah, the head of the Zabini family is willing to hear from you."

"And as far as we know, they're not Death Eaters, right?"

"They've almost always stayed neutral on the divisive issues," Tonks explained. "Chris is the only one I know at all and he's a nice enough bloke."

"Why are you looking for a Lord like Zabini?" Harry asked curiously.

"Trying to get the old house back and maybe a couple galleons too," Sirius explained.

"And Zabini has the house keys?"

"It's old family politics," Sirius explained. "But basically when the Sirius of this world died at the same time you did, you were his designated heir, and you, as a one year old, hadn't designated anyone so the Black family as a whole, was headless."

"The Black family?" Harry asked curiously.

"It's how a lot of the old pureblood families operate," Sirius explained. "There's a family vault, which in families as competitive and heartless as mine, doesn't usually have much money. It does have some family heirlooms though, including the magical deed to the family manor."

"Grimmauld Place?" Harry clarified.

Sirius nodded. "When the family's headless, the vault and manor seal up. And the family ring goes back inside the family vault. It's a bunch of outdated mularky, but if I can get another Lord to vouch that I'm the new Lord Black, the goblins can get me in the vault for the purposes of seeing if the ring will accept me."

"No sacrifices or bathing in blood?" Harry grinned before adding, "And you know Grimmauld Place isn't all that sealed up. It's where I crashed last night. Dusty as hell and Kreacher's even further off his rocker in this dimension."

"You've been there?" Sirius asked in surprise.

Harry nodded. "Though it looked like I was the first one in a long time."

"I didn't think you'd have been able to even get near it without the Black family ring," Sirius said seeing Tonks and Remus looked as clueless as him.

Harry twisted a ring on his finger making it visible. "This one?"

Sirius' eyes widened. "Bloody hell, Harry! You're Lord Black."

"Umm… I think I would've remembered something like that."

"No," Tonks agreed. "You are."

"Harry," Sirius explained, rubbing his forehead. "If that ring didn't accept you as Lord Black, it could've killed you. Or at least really hurt."

Harry huffed. "That miserable little bastard. Kreacher gave it to me and told me it would make the wards I was trying to put up actually work."

"Well, yes," Sirius agreed. "It would do that, but knowing Kreacher I think he was hoping it would kill you."

"He was," Harry agreed. "He went from smiling to frowning as soon as it flashed when I put it on. So this is why I was able to get into Grimmauld Place."

"Well I guess we don't need Lord Zabini for anything," Sirius told Tonks. He turned to Harry, "And we're not homeless anymore."

Harry smirked. "Oh, so now you're crashing on your Lord's couch?"

"Couch?" Sirius grinned. "I've got seniority. The Master bedroom is mine."

"Why don't we let the ring decide?" Harry offered twisting it back into invisibility.

"That's brilliant!" Sirius agreed. "That's the ring from our dimension. This dimension's ring might still be in the vault."

"Two Lord Blacks?" Remus asked. "Is that even possible?"

"I got Harry involved, so we got a decent shot," Sirius explained.

"Well then you still need a Lord Zabini or someone to vouch for you," Tonks pointed out.

"We got a Lord Black right here," Sirius said pointing to Harry. "He can vouch for me, but he can probably open the vault just fine himself."

"Lady Black," Ginny said, trying the name out. "It suits me."

Harry sighed and thought back to a certain portrait. "Well I always did think of Mrs. Black as a long-dead insanely annoying harpy."

Ginny scowled at Harry punching her fist through him, giving him a literal cold shoulder.

"Aww good old Mum," Sirius recollected. "Thank Merlin she didn't love me the way a father loves his daughter."

Complete, dead silence followed as everyone stared at Sirius. He couldn't take it and cracked up. "This is going to be great."

Chapter 8

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Author's Note: Two and a half weeks for a normal-sized chapter is undoubtedly too long for many of you. But oh well. I've been busy. And I've got a jump on the next chapter now. Expect the next one in less than two and a half weeks. Thanks for all the reviews. They make my day and make me write faster.

"Twenty eight thousand galleons?"

"I know."

"But twenty eight thousand galleons?"

"Yes Sirius, I know."

"The furniture alone is worth that much. That was an original Van Eyk charmed boudoir in perfect condition. That's probably fifteen large on its own. And even in that shape, the Mage Cloak was still worth-"

"Sirius?"

"What?"

"You're looking at this the wrong way."

"We're knowingly taking less than half of market price. How else am I supposed to look at it?"

"Sirius," Harry said making sure he had his attention. "We just made twenty eight thousand galleons."

Sirius frowned.

"With Felix we may not get as much as we could elsewhere, but we can trust him. He can spread these things around to make them untraceable. He offered to let us obliviate him-"

"He only said that because he can break memory charms."

"It's symbolic. He gave us an Unbreakable Vow to never reveal anything about us. This wasn't just 'stuff' when we had it, it was evidence. And Sirius, I'll repeat it once more a little louder: we are now twenty eight thousand galleons richer than we were yesterday afternoon."

"True." Sirius was fighting a smile.

"It's a good thing," Harry said with a nod. "We may get less money but we get more peace of mind."

"I know," Sirius grumbled scuffing his shoes. "It's just-"

"You know what might make you feel better," Harry interrupted. "Why don't we go spend a few thousand galleons?"

"Okay!" Sirius shouted excitedly. "Wait. Are we spending our own money or someone else's?"

Harry had to think about the question. "I suppose we are spending our own money. But, and this is an important 'but,' but at least we didn't earn it through an honest day's work like a sucker."

Sirius nodded slowly. "I can live with that."

"I'm not going to wear it," Sirius indignantly argued. "And you need to slow down before we go broke. Again."

"Sirius," Harry sighed. "What have I bought? Have you even been paying attention?"

"You spent three thousand galleons just to get a couple of trunks impenetrably charmed to us."

Harry nodded, urging for Sirius to continue.

"You spent twelve hundred galleons on just anchor stones, including some that cost over a hundred galleons for one hunk of rock!"

"Yup."

"A pair of chameleon cloaks for each of us. I'll admit they're nice, but at 400 galleons each, I don't think we both need an extra cloak that'll just collect dust in the back of our closets."

"You do understand that with the chameleon cloak, we don't have to buy any muggle outfits… ever?"

Sirius ignored him. "And now you just spent seventeen hundred galleons on a couple of necklaces."

Harry nodded. "I like to think of it as we spent not just me, but yeah."

"They're supposed to be for a husband and wife," Sirius bemoaned. "And they're ugly."

Harry frowned. "Okay, I'll admit they're… a bit gaudy."

"A bit?" Sirius questioned, unconsciously raising his voice. "Harry, inch thick gold chain is more than a bit gaudy."

"It's not that thick," Harry grumbled. "And you're a wizard, aren't you?"

Sirius shook his head. "It's the principle. You don't bang fat chicks just because they can cast a glamour."

"Do you even know what these necklaces are?" Harry said gripping a hold of the thick chain around his neck.

"Yeah," Sirius grimaced. "They're an old traditional wedding gift used for the consummation of arranged marriages."

"I suppose that's one use, but do you know what they do?"

Sirius shook his head.

"They allow a shared mental connection between the two people wearing them. It's for the purpose of creating a feedback loop of pleasure to ease the tension of the wedding night."

"Listen, I don't know what anyone told you about a godfather's duties, but-"

"Please don't finish that thought," Harry said with a wince. "The point is that it opens a mental connection between us. They allow us to communicate completely silently across distances. Think like the magical mirrors but without anyone ever knowing we're talking."

Sirius thought about it. "That would've been great for pranking. And tests."

"Exactly."

"So instead of carrying a mirror like a Malfoy, we're gonna wear jewelry that even a blind goblin would find hideous?"

"Everything I've bought for us is going to make our new hobby easier. That's more than you can say. Why did you buy a photo development kit anyway?"

Sirius snickered to himself. "I might have come across a wizarding camera last night."

Harry looked at him expectantly. "And?"

"And I want to develop the pictures."

Harry frowned. "You're that curious what pictures are on it?"

"Well I know one picture that's on it."

Harry began to put two and two together. "And of course you took a picture of your privates and can't exactly drop those off at the Wiz-mart photo department."

Sirius shook his head, inordinately proud of himself. "It's not a picture of my boys. But good idea."

"I hope you didn't take any pictures that are going to be later described as the prosecution's exhibit A."

"Not exactly," Sirius mysteriously answered.

Harry just looked at his godfather not wanting to indulge him at the moment.

Sirius was waiting. "Aren't you gonna ask?"

"Why should I when you're about to tell me anyway?"

Sirius couldn't hold it and joyfully explained, "Fine. Don't get all pillock-like on me. So you know I grabbed all their toiletries, right?"

Harry frowned. "I assumed you were just too lazy to buy your own shampoo and toothpaste."

Sirius shook his head. "I actually didn't clear out the entire bathroom." Sirius paused and couldn't have stopped smiling if he wanted to. "I left behind the Baron's toothbrush."

Harry closed his eyes. "Oh Merlin, Sirius. I've heard rumors about things like this."

"Now," Sirius continued ignoring Harry. "I knew you'd throw a hissy-fit if I sent them a picture of my bum, because then they'd know I'm a wizard, white, and have an adorable arse."

Harry thought hissy-fit wasn't the term he would've used but nodded silently.

"Then I just happened to walk past a perfectly good unconscious house elf, and I just happened to be carrying a wizarding camera, and I just happened to have the good Baron's toothbrush." Sirius shrugged helplessly. "So I did what any wizard would have done."

Harry was tempted to debate just what any wizard would have done but settled for silently pitying the poor elf.

"It was like Fate herself was slapping her knee, pointing, and begging, 'Do it again! Do it again!'"

Harry felt slightly ashamed that he was looking forward to the picture. "Let's go get the floo connected."

"Great," Sirius mockingly agreed. "We should throw more money away, this time at the government." He shook his head grumbling "Why can't the Ministry close on Sundays like the whole muggle world does?"

"Ow!" The little man behind the counter whined rubbing his arm. "Did you just throw a sickle at me?"

Sirius shook his head trying to fight a chuckle. Partly because it was horribly cheesy that Harry took Sirius' words literally and just physically threw money at the government, and partly because Sirius wished he had thought of it first. "Could be worse. He could've thrown a sickle at you."

The stocky wizard was confused. "What?"

"Good afternoon," Harry greeted paying no attention to the coin he'd just thrown. "We would like to get our ancestral home reconnected to the floo system."

"A reconnection? What's the address?"

"Number Twelve Grimmauld Place."

The short man had pulled out a thick ledger and was flipping through it. "That's London?"

"Yup," Harry said while entertaining himself by using his magical arms to nudge Sirius' hair. Sirius kept swatting behind his head thinking a bug was landing in his hair.

"Ah-ha! Number Twelve Grimmauld Place, the Noble and Most Ancient House of Black."

"We prefer Ancientest," Harry corrected.

"Excuse me?" the man asked in confusion.

Harry maintained his deadpan expression. "Most Ancient is a muggle phrase. We're the Noble and Ancientest House of Black."

"I'm Lord Black," Sirius introduced with a nod. "My associate, Lord Black, never finished his proper schooling and you know how dropouts are. So he overcompensates and tries to correct people for no real reason."

The man had stopped flipping through the ledger and looked up at the two men. Completely flummoxed on how to respond, he just looked back down and went back to his search.

"Lord Black and Lord Black," the man greeted while retrieving all the paperwork on Number Twelve Grimmauld Place. "I've heard about you two. I'm Greg Olson." He was looking through the file and snuck a glance up at the two Lord Blacks. "Do you mind if I ask you how the House of Black is going to vote tomorrow?"

Harry turned towards Sirius wondering if he knew anything about this. Sirius shook his head and asked, "There's a Wizengamot vote tomorrow?"

"The issue of Muggleborn Rights," Greg explained. "I was just wondering if you knew or were willing to share which way the House of Black is going to vote."

"I want to do it," Harry said to Sirius.

"Alright, we can do it," Sirius agreed and clarified, "We're on the side that thinks muggleborns should have rights, aren't we?"

"If you are," Greg butted in, "then you're probably against the issue they're calling Muggleborn Rights this time."

"Why?" Harry asked curiously.

"This steaming pile of legislation supposedly empowers muggleborns over their muggle relatives, but it also empowers the Ministry over their muggle relatives."

"Ugh," Sirius grumbled hearing the explanation and noticing Harry was listening intently. "Learning. Politics. Getting weaker..."

Harry frowned at Sirius and asked Greg, "What do you mean empowers over?"

"You should research the issue if you're going to vote on it tomorrow."

"Yes," Harry agreed enjoying the frown on Sirius' face. "We definitely should."

"This is your fault," Sirius warned leaning towards Greg. "I may forget a face or two, but I never forget a name, Craig Olson."

"Greg," Harry corrected.

"Greg," Sirius continued without blinking.

Greg fidgeted under Sirius' angry stare. "Let's get an appointment scheduled for you to get your floo reconnected."

"Can't you just turn it back on from here?" Sirius complained. "Do you really need to come to our fireplaces?"

"Yes, we could," Greg nodded. "But we don't do that anymore."

"Why not?" Harry asked curiously.

"It's policy."

"But why?"

"It's policy, sir."

"That's not a reason," Sirius argued.

Harry held up a hand, stopping Greg from responding. "Let's set up the appointment."

Greg looked down at the calendar on the front desk. "Looks like we have some time tomorrow."

"We've now got the Wizengamot vote tomorrow," Harry said. "How about the day after?"

Greg was shaking his head and making quiet clicking sounds. "Sorry, no open dates the day after. Nor the next day, nor the next…" Greg was flipping the pages of the calendar quickly, just shaking his head. "Here we go. Our next open appointment is August 18th."

"August 18th?"

"Yes, sir."

"Tell you what, Harry," Sirius volunteered. "I'll stay home and handle the installation while you do the research and homework stuff Greg assigned."

Greg cleared his throat and added, "For what it's worth, if you both wish to be able to augment your floo connections, then you'll both need to be present for the installation."

"Guess we won't be able to get in and vote this time," Sirius said patting Harry on the back. "We'll do lots of fun research next time. Don't worry."

"August 18th really is the next earliest we can do this?"

"Yes sir," Greg answered. "But if I may point something out?"

Harry nodded that Greg should continue.

"We only do appointments during normal business hours, and the Wizengamot vote is an evening session. They won't overlap."

Harry beamed a smile at Sirius.

Sirius was half growling. "Your name is quickly moving up my list, Craig."

"Greg," Harry supplied again.

"Greg," Sirius corrected.

Greg was beginning to wonder if Sirius was getting his name wrong purposefully. "So the appointment tomorrow, should I put you down for eight to noon or one to five?"

"One to five," Sirius answered immediately, while Harry responded, "Eight to noon."

The two Lord Blacks turned to each other and began to have a silent battle of wills.

"I'm sorry," Greg interrupted them. "You misunderstood me. The appointment times have to be flexible. I was asking if I should put you down for tomorrow, yes or no. The appointment tomorrow is for eight to noon or one to five."

"Both times?"

Greg nodded.

Sirius frowned. "That's just cruel."

"That's our policy, sir," Greg answered happily.

"We'll take the appointment tomorrow," Harry said glancing at his watch. He looked at Sirius and said, "It's quarter past. You want to go bug Moony at work? We're going to need his help setting up some of our new toys."

Sirius nodded. "I probably owe him a dinner or two. And now I can afford it."

Harry turned towards Greg and asked, "Do we pay you now or when it gets turned on?"

"You have to pay at least your past due charges now," Greg assured them, finishing the paperwork. "And if you want it set up as joint custody, you both need to sign here and here."

They signed the paperwork, while Sirius was obviously fretting over ways their new necklaces and 'joint custody' could easily be misconstrued.

Harry and Sirius walked back to the apparition point in the Ministry. Sirius knew the way to Remus' office and apparated away with Harry following on his trail.

Sirius led him out of the tube station and down the street a half block. They entered an office building and walked up to a suite on the second floor. "Is Mr. Lupin in his office?"

The woman at the front desk just nodded without pausing in her phone conversation.

Sirius waved Harry to follow him and led him back through a small cubicle farm. He reached an office that said Remus J. Lupin across the door.

Sirius glanced at Harry and urged, "Do me a favor and close the door behind you." Sirius grabbed the handle to Remus' office and whipped it open, shouting out loud, "Scotland Yard! Get your hands up and face the wall."

Remus looked up suddenly. "What are you-"

"I said face the wall!"

"Oh god."

Sirius grabbed a hold of Remus and spun him around before shoving him hard into the wall and rattling a framed poster of a kitten.

Harry looked both ways and saw almost everyone was looking towards Remus' office. He let no emotion show on his face as he stared them all down before sharply closing the door with him in the office.

"Dammit Sirius," Remus grumbled easily breaking free from his grip. "I'm trying to work here."

Harry peered at the computer screen. "That's a card game."

"I didn't say I was succeeding at working, just trying to," Remus haughtily retorted.

"And what would your bosses have to say about this?"

Remus plopped back into his chair. "Who knows? They might give me another promotion."

"They gave you one already?" Harry inquired. "I thought you didn't know much about computers."

Remus nodded. "A couple months ago there was a free seminar on our products for any employee who wished to take it. Everyone in my department wanted to go, including me. But the seminar was during the full moon, so I couldn't. When I got back to work on Thursday, I discovered everyone else knew a lot more than me about computers. And apparently for that reason, they promoted me to Senior Consultant."

"Because you know less than the others," Sirius clarified.

Remus shrugged. "I don't understand muggles any more than I understand wizards."

Sirius glanced at Harry and back at Remus. "You ready to sneak out of here?"

Remus paused to consider the question while closing his computer game windows. He hopped up and opened his office door to address his gossip-loving colleagues. "I'm not in any trouble. These were just a couple of my friends playing around. Julie, is McAlister here?"

Julie looked up from her desk. "Is McAlister ever here?"

"What about Maddox?"

Julie shook her head. "She went home over an hour ago."

"Alright, thanks," Remus said closing the door to his office again. He pulled on the cord that shut his blinds. "You got something fun for us to do?"

"We need your help on a little project," Harry explained.

Sirius added, "And I wanna buy you dinner."

"You? Buy?" Remus asked in surprise. "Are you sure?"

Sirius smirked, "Well I am a little buy-curious."

"We came into a little money and need your help," Harry interjected. "Everybody wins."

Remus nodded and waved the two men towards him away from the window in his office door. "We can just apparate out from here."

Harry blinked half-expecting they would need to kidnap Remus to get him to skip out on work. "Won't they notice you never left your office?"

Remus shrugged. "I wouldn't be surprised if they think I'm just working late."

Sirius tapped his chin. "You know this whole work thing doesn't sound quite as bad as I'd expected."

"I prefer our new jobs," Harry argued with a smile at Sirius.

"Hang on," Remus said looking at the two grinning Lord Blacks. "You guys got jobs?"

Sirius and Harry exchanged a glance just before they both apparated away. "Meet you back at Grimmauld Place."

"No way," Remus repeated for the sixth time, shaking his head in amazement. "They were just going to throw this stuff away?"

"Hard to believe, isn't it?" Sirius grinned.

"This is a really nice robe," Remus said enjoying the feel of acromantula silk. "I mean really, really nice. Normally, I'd refuse your generosity, but I can see you stumbled across plenty of them."

"I know!" Sirius cheered.

"You guys must be the luckiest blokes in the world," Remus commented while he and Sirius were arranging where to put all the new electronics. Remus was explaining the various parts while Sirius just nodded and didn't even try to pay attention.

"Dammit!" Harry swore as the ward stones flared up and died. "I'm still not doing this right."

"Are you following the instructions correctly?" Remus asked from behind a quickly growing mess of wires and cables.

"Yes," Harry answered. "I'm doing the spell exactly the way the book says. But it's not working."

"Try your other wand," Sirius suggested with a shrug.

Remus stuck his head out and glared at Sirius. "The wand he's using won't make any difference in the magic."

"Hot damn!" Harry cheered. "Sirius I could kiss you right now if that didn't mean I'd be admitting you were right."

"Hah!" Sirius smirked at Remus. "I told you."

Remus just went back behind the TV and ignored Sirius.

Since the spell was working, Harry cast sticking charms on the rest of the ward stones and affixed them to the four corners of the ceiling and the four corners of the floor. The four walls, the floor, and the ceiling all needed the spell cast on it, isolating this particular room off from the magic of the rest of the home.

Remus came back around to the extra long couch and had three different remotes in his hands. "We're ready whenever you are."

Harry had just finished casting the spell for a sixth time and was inspecting where the magical boundaries met. "I think we're good."

"Here goes nothing," Remus said pointing the remote at giant television while the two other Lord Blacks collapsed into the couch on either side of him. The screen flickered to life and had warning text stating, 'Warming Up…'

"No way," Remus cheered. "It works." He turned on the DVD player and saw it light up. "No way!"

Sirius glanced at how excited Remus was and commented, "This isn't exactly the stimulating sort of show I was looking for."

The screen had finished warming up and was a royal blue, exclaiming it was looking for an 'input signal.'

"If there's a disc in the player, it should have just started up," Remus explained. He looked down at the first remote for the television and began to fiddle with the buttons. "Maybe I need to-"

"AAH!" Sirius shrieked as blaring loud music came from all directions around him. All three men had their hands over their ears and yet continued to try and communicate.

"Is it supposed to be that loud?" Harry screamed over the noise.

Remus shrugged, fiddling with more buttons. "I think so."

"Maybe a silencing charm," Sirius was mumbling as he took out his wand.

"No!" Remus snapped grabbing the wand from Sirius' hand. He chucked it out into the hallway. "Don't cast magic on the electronics."

"I'm pretty sure you can turn the volume down," Harry shouted over the orchestral song and movie's opening credits.

"How?" Remus shouted back, showing the remote to Harry.

Harry looked at it. "Perhaps the arrow buttons labeled Volume?"

"Oh right," Remus agreed and quickly lowered the volume to a far more acceptable level. "Sorry about that."

"Shh!" Sirius scolded slapping Remus.

"Excuse me?" Remus said when he saw Sirius hadn't even looked towards him.

"I'm trying to watch this, I don't want to miss it and you keep talking," Sirius explained while clearly enraptured by the screen.

Remus hit pause.

"What? No!" Sirius snapped. "You broke it. Fix it, Moony. Fix it."

"I paused it," Remus explained and hit play followed by pause again.

Sirius huffed and tried to grab the remote, but Remus pulled his hand away. Sirius whined, "Give me the wand. You don't know how to work it right."

"If you think it's a wand, then it's clearly not safe in your hands," Remus retorted.

Remus let out a slightly feminine shriek when he felt pokes on both the left and right sides of his belly. He dropped the remote in reflex as an invisible hand grabbed it and pulled it away.

"Why don't I hold the remote, while you two children wrestle for it," Harry said keeping the remote up in the air and out of their reach.

"You're on!" Sirius agreed, grabbing a hold of Remus and taking him by surprise.

"Padfoot, he wasn't being sincere. He was calling you childish," Remus complained despite being held in a half nelson.

"That's the talk of a loser if I ever heard one," Sirius grumbled as Remus' werewolf strength quickly turned the tables on him.

Harry just rolled his eyes and hit play on the remote.

The two grown men, who were wrestling on the floor, stopped and just looked up at the giant screen. Neither had bothered to extricate themselves from the other's grip. They were both simply entranced at the wondrous technology of muggles and the tale unfolding before their eyes.

Harry was stifling his chuckles at the fact that Remus and Sirius were still holding each other and watching the movie. He summoned Sirius' camera and snapped a few shots when they gripped each other tightly in moments of fright and surprise. Before long Harry also got caught up in the movie.

"You guys here?" Tonks' voice came from the foyer.

"Upstairs," Harry called back suddenly realizing they'd been watching a movie for over twenty minutes.

Remus and Sirius were still on the floor, neither even aware that Harry or Tonks had said anything.

"Holy crap!" Tonks exclaimed at the sight of the giant telly.

"Shh!" Remus and Sirius both shushed.

Harry hit pause on the movie.

"No!" Sirius whined. "What are you doing?"

Remus suddenly realized his predicament. "Padfoot. Could you take your arm off my waist please?"

"It's stuck between two pillows."

"We don't have any-"

"Gah," Sirius said quickly pulling away.

Tonks looked at Harry. "Do I want to know?"

Harry smiled at Tonks. "I took pictures of the lovers' embrace on the floor."

Sirius plopped himself back on the couch and yelped, "Hey! That's my new camera, you thief."

"You found a camera too?" Remus asked in surprise. "No way!"

"Speaking of thieves," Tonks grinned. "Last night someone cleaned house at Parkinson Manor. Potter's been moaning about it all day."

"Hmm," Harry said without conviction.

"Hmm," Sirius echoed innocently.

"I only mention because you just happened to find a camera around the same time someone stole a camera from the Parkinsons, along with the vast majority of their other earthly possessions," Tonks said glancing at the massive muggle home entertainment center. "It's curious timing."

"This stuff is probably all stolen!" Remus suddenly realized. "I mean the odds of you guys just finding all this stuff in one place the same night as a major robbery have to be astronomical. You did say you found it all in the same place, right?"

"Hmm," Sirius said before Harry poked him in the belly. "Oof."

"Yup," Harry said with a wide smile. "Found all of it in the same place."

Tonks saw the nice robe her adoptive father was wearing and smirked. "And just what else did you find?"

"Tons," Remus answered for them. "They got a whole…" He stopped and turned towards the two Lord Blacks who were inspecting their surroundings and whistling nonchalantly. "You didn't just find anything at all, did you?"

"Doubt it," Tonks said through her snickers. "Unless you count finding things around Parkinson Manor."

Sirius looked at Harry and asked, "How long are we supposed to act innocent?"

Harry deflated and sighed. "Well you can stop acting now."

"You guys stole from the Parkinsons!" Remus yelled in outrage.

"Yeah," Sirius answered with a firm nod.

"Aren't you ashamed of yourselves?"

Sirius looked at Harry and shook his head. "No, not really."

"It's not so much that we wanted to quote-unquote steal from them, as it is that we wanted to remove some of the Death Eaters' resources," Harry feebly explained.

"And reallocate them to our pockets," Sirius added with a grin. "Why are your panties in such a twist, Moony?"

"I don't know," Remus said still unable to keep his voice down. "But it's wrong."

"If we let things like 'right' and 'wrong' get in the way, then the terrorists have already won," Sirius sagely argued.

Harry got the distinct feeling Sirius wasn't the most skilled debater before turning to face Tonks. "To be honest, I wasn't sure if they were even going to report it. Did they manage to dispel the calling card in the entryway?"

"You guys took everything," Tonks added. "They had to report it. And no, the floating dildo was still there when we arrived, which by the way was getting a lot of discussion on what to call it. I think the frontrunner last I heard was the After-Dark Mark, though Rockwell was insisting that it should be called the Dirk Mark for some reason. Personally, I think-"

"Tonks," Remus interrupted.

"Right," Tonks said as she realized a dildo discussion in front of her adopted father and the two dimension traveling knuckleheads couldn't possibly end well. "Anyways, they left it up for the investigators. The DoM captured the wand signature from the mark and it wasn't on file."

Sirius frowned. "Did you at least ask Baron Parkinson some uncomfortable questions?"

Tonks shook her head. "He was away on business, or so we've been told. He left the missus to deal with the DMLE. Are you sure Parkinson is a Death Eater?"

"Harry?" Sirius asked.

Harry nodded. "As certain as I can be."

"Was this a gut feeling or did you see the mark?"

"Snakes can sense the serpent magic of the Dark Mark," Harry explained. "Parkinson had it. 'It leaves a stain on the soul' a particularly poetic cobra told me once."

"That's a useful trick," Tonks said with a low whistle, "detecting the Dark Mark."

"I can't detect it," Harry clarified. "I'm just one of the few people in the world who can talk to the ones who can detect it. And before you even ask, you don't have to worry. We're not going to be reallocating from anyone until after we've confirmed they're branded Voldemort cattle."

"Wait," Remus jumped in. "You're going to do this again?"

"We finally get new jobs and you're trying to get me to quit?" Sirius said shaking his head. "Moony, I'm disappointed in you."

"It's a not a job, it's a crime," Remus said looking over at Tonks. "And come to think of it, you've implicitly made us all accomplices, including a respected Auror."

"That's a good point boys," Tonks jumped in. "I can't just turn my head the other way."

"Thank you," Remus nodded glad to have some support.

"Certainly not when the old guy here gets himself such a fine silk robe and I've got nothing to wear to help you celebrate your new jobs."

"Well we're going to have to do something about that," Sirius grinned back as Remus' head dropped in disappointment.

"Come with me, Auror Tonks-Lupin," Harry said swinging an arm over her shoulder. "I think we can locate a wardrobe or two in your size. Or maybe some jewelry that befits a member of the Black family."

"Now we're talking," Tonks agreed.

Harry gave her a playful squeeze of the bum, adding, "Who knows? We may even figure out a way to celebrate where having nothing to wear is the appropriate attire."

Remus sighed as Tonks and Harry walked away. "We were good people before we met you two. Honest, hard-working magical citizens."

Sirius slung an arm over Moony's shoulder imitating Harry's earlier action. "Maybe, but you weren't having this much fun either."

"True," Remus admitted with a smile.

"And why do you even care so much about us thieving from the folks you'd openly consider the enemy?"

Remus smirked. "I don't care. But someone needs to disagree with you two before you try to overthrow the government."

"That's tomorrow," Sirius assured him as he picked up the television remote. "Why don't you show me how to make the thing louder with this muggle wand?"

Remus grinned. "You want to watch the rest of the movie?"

Sirius nodded. "That and I figured you'd want to make sure to drown out any noise coming from Harry's room right about now."

"Okay, that's it," Remus insisted. "You really need to learn a thing or two about fathers and their daughters."

Sirius could always tell when Remus was ripe for riling up. "Well I think your daughter may be the one learning a thing or two."

Remus clenched his eyes shut. "It's about common courtesy and basic propriety. Things you just don't say, to certain people, even when they're obvious."

"You know we picked up a whole lot of really old musty smelling books," Sirius teased when he saw Remus' eyes light up. "I only mention it because there's a chance that right now Harry and Tonks are having sex."

Remus growled softly.

"At this very moment, his penis could be in her-"

"Give me the muggle wand and shut up," Remus snapped, figuring if he couldn't beat him, he should join him. And make sure to beat him later much harder with a big stick.

Chapter 9

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Author's Note: Another chapter for your reading and reviewing pleasure. Thanks for all the reviews and keep the feedback coming.

"Harry," Sirius whined. "Stop reading about the Wizengamot and entertain me."

"I can't believe this stuff," Harry said shaking his head. "You know we can settle disputes with duels? I don't think the charter has changed in about a thousand years. There's even a wielder of the Sovereign Saber!"

"There's a sword?" Sirius asked curiously.

"Yeah," Harry explained. "Whoever's got the saber has the right to interrupt any proceedings at any time for any reason. And they must be heard."

"That does seem a bit… medieval," Sirius said. "Can you stab people with it?"

Harry shrugged. "What good does wielding the Sovereign Saber do if you can't stab the guy next to you when it tickles your fancy?"

Sirius had a very thoughtful and intelligent response to Harry's question but they were interrupted by a knock at the door.

"It's about freaking time," Sirius yelled, marching to the front door. "Do you have any idea how long we've been waiting…" He wrenched open the door and discovered a curvaceous young woman with a tool belt hanging loosely on her hips. She wore a half buckled pair of overalls covering a tight soot-covered white t-shirt. Sirius' face split into a smile and he finished his question "…for you to walk into our lives?"

She was popping her chewing gum and decided to blow a bubble while eyeing Sirius up. The bubble she was blowing burst and she licked the gum from her upper lip. "Sorry about that. You need a floo reconnection?"

Sirius pulled the door open wider and waved her in. "Either that or it was just something we said to get you in the door."

She tried to ignore his advances and asked, "Where do you want the primary fireplace and how many others do you want active?"

Sirius closed the door and flashed a innocent grin. "I suppose that depends on how good you are with your tools."

Harry looked up from his copy of A People's History of the Wizengamot. "In here," Harry called out answering her first question. He pointed towards the large hearth. "That's our primary fireplace. The only other two we need are the two Master bedrooms."

"You have two Master bedrooms?" she asked while glancing over her shoulder at Sirius.

"The Manor actually provides one for each Lord Black," Sirius said leaning against the side of the mantle while the young woman climbed into the fireplace. Sirius was happily checking out the visible parts of her body while she was banging around with her tools. Sirius loudly explained, "When you finish up with this fireplace, I'll show you mine. Common courtesy would be for you to show me yours."

"Uh-huh," she commented skeptically.

Harry was just shaking his head and poking Sirius for being shameless.

The young woman leaned out of the fireplace and flirted right back at them. "Lord Black and Lord Black, I'm ready for you in here. Bring a wand."

"Please, call me Sirius," he announced sidling up next to her. "And what should I call you?"

"I'm Sindy with an S."

"Yes you are," Sirius agreed.

"You're just keying in the wand signature, right?" Harry clarified without getting up.

Sindy nodded, wiping the soot off her hands, accentuating her chest. "Yeah but it needs to be in your hand."

"That's alright," Harry said. "You guys look cozy in there. I got it from here."

"Are you sure," Sindy questioned. "Only those keyed into the primary can affect the other fireplaces on the account."

"What's the matter Sindy with an S? Don't think I'm enough Lord Black for you?" Sirius grinned pressing his wand tip into back of the fireplace.

Sindy grinned back. "I'm quite certain you're too much Lord Black for me, Sirius." She saw Sirius was already resting his wand in the right spot but was surprised to see another wand floating opposite it waiting to be keyed in. "What's that?"

Sirius saw where she was looking and answered. "That's Harry's wand. And Harry's holding it, so go ahead and key us in."

She didn't question it and activated the floo network for them.

"That it?" Sirius clarified pulling back his wand when she nodded.

Sindy watched the other wand float out of the fireplace and zoom over towards Harry. Harry hadn't even looked up from his book and just raised his left arm into the air. The wand slid right into the wrist holster and Harry's arm came down. The page in his book turned itself without Harry ever noticing his audience.

"Come on Sindy," Sirius said as he picked up her tools off the ground. "I think I've got something in my bedroom you'll want to see."

Sirius and Sindy walked past Harry, and Sirius mumbled out of the corner of his mouth, "Show-off."

Sindy gasped, turned around, and slapped Sirius across the face. "If you pinch my ass without permission again, I'm going to write up a report and you'll never get connected to any floo in this country."

Sirius just shook his head, trying to ignore the not so quiet snickering coming from Harry, and preparing to argue his innocence when he instead asked, "So this permission thing, how's it gonna work?"

Sindy was smiling in spite of herself. "You're incorrigible."

"You have no idea," Harry commented loudly still nose deep in his book.

"Thank you, Harry," Sirius snapped back, disappearing towards the bedrooms with Sindy.

Ten minutes later the two were coming back down to the living room, shamelessly flirting and giggling the whole way.

"You can't sign Lord Black twice," Sindy said with a laugh. "There are two different wand signatures on the account, and they each need their own authorization."

"Help me out here, Harry," Sirius requested with a hopeful look. "Sindy here is getting off her shift after finishing up with us. And I'm trying to convince her to take a few more hours on the clock and spare us the agony of going to the Wizengamot vote tonight."

"I said I would if my boyfriend-"

"Don't even give me that boyfriend cock and bull story unless you're ready to prove you feel nothing for me with a kiss."

"Sirius, can I talk to you for a moment?" Harry said pulling the older man into a corner away from Sindy.

Harry glanced over and saw Sindy was pointedly ignoring them. He looked at his godfather. "Okay first, I'd avoid mentioning bull cock in the same four word span as boyfriend when you're chatting up a girl."

Sirius nodded at the advice he could've used a moment ago.

"And second," Harry glanced over at Sindy again. He looked Sirius in the eye. "How old do you think she is?"

Sirius took a glance and answered, "Twenty-six or seven maybe? Why? You don't think she's thirty do you?"

Harry rolled his eyes at the look of fear when Sirius said the word thirty. Harry leaned to the side and called out, "Hey Sindy? Remember I'm an ancient and noble Lord who can verify this with your boss when I ask, how old are you?"

"Eighteen," Sindy answered uncertainly. "No nineteen. I turned nineteen a couple weeks ago."

"Thank you," Harry said with a smile.

"And my real name is Marge," she admitted out loud in a oddly honest moment.

Harry looked back at Sirius. "Nineteen. For a man who wants to keep making fun of the old Remus, you're not exactly sparkling with virtue at the moment."

"Nineteen," Sirius repeated incredulously looking her over again. "I'm like-"

"Old enough to be her father? Twice her age? On the sort of diaper duty that reserves you a place in hell?"

"You're being a big help here," Sirius nodded sarcastically thanking Harry.

"I'm not saying if a pretty minnow jumps in your boat to throw it back," Harry explained. "But maybe you shouldn't be fishing for the ones just spawning for their first time."

"I used to know a mermaid who dirty-talked a lot like that," Sirius replied. "And yes, point taken. Obviously I was overestimating her age. Blah, blah, blah. We'll still go play with the icky politicians tonight."

Harry walked back over to the woman. "Sindy, err… Marge, where do you need my signature?"

"Here and here," she pointed to two spots on her work orders.

"Thanks for setting us up," Harry said going back to his chair and book.

Sirius smiled at her. "I'm sorry to say the evil, anal retentive Lord Black has insisted that we attend this evening's Wizengamot session. Which means I'm not going be able to steal you from your boyfriend tonight. But now you know my floo address for the next time he disappoints you and you want to get back at him."

Sindy walked over to the freshly connected floo and tossed in some floo powder. "You're such a dirty old man," she said with a wink before loudly announcing, "Ministry of Magic."

Sirius watched her disappear. "I'm a dirty old man, eh?"

"Easy way to fix that," Harry said closing his book and standing up. "Take a shower. We should drop in and visit the Chamber of Lords lounge before the Wizengamot convenes."

"There's a lounge?" Sirius asked.

Harry nodded. "And hookers there to service you."

"Well alright," Sirius agreed, finally seeing the benefit of establishing a political presence.

"Harry," Sirius commented as the two walked into the private chamber. "I see a bunch of old men. Perhaps we need to clarify the definition of hooker."

"I don't think that's necessary," Harry added. "You might have misinterpreted my meaning when I said there would be hookers here to service you."

"You mean when I took your line 'there will be hookers here to service me' to mean that there would be hookers here to service me?"

"Yup," Harry agreed. "That doesn't sound anything like my meaning."

"How do you do?" A man greeted walking up to them. "Lord Thomas Hooker. My friends call me TJ. Would I be correct in believing you two to be the infamous Lords Black?"

"I hardly think we're infamous yet, Lord Hooker," Sirius grinned shaking the man's hand. "But the day's just getting started."

"TJ," another man greeted as he approached. "Don't scare the new guys too much. Lord Jason Bennington. My friends call me JC."

"Lord Black," Harry answered shaking Lord Bennington's hand. "My friends call me Harry and not to worry. It'll take a lot more than a room of stodgy, old men to scare me."

"Did you just call me stodgy?" A man interrupted puffing up himself with pride.

"PJ, must you always posture?" Lord Hooker said with a grin.

"Lord Peter Potter," He introduced sticking his hand out. "My friends call me a right old bastard."

"Well if that's all it takes, I wouldn't be surprised to count you as a friend someday," Sirius answered shaking hands. "Lord Black. My friends call me Sirius and this is Harry, another Lord Black."

"I also get called PJ a lot because 'right old bastard' just takes too long to say sometimes."

Harry was shaking hands with a great uncle he never knew he had when he felt a powerful presence enter the room.

"Speaking of stodgy old men," Lord Potter mumbled under his breath.

Harry spun around and did his best to focus on his frustratingly weak Occlumency shields. "Chief Warlock Dumbledore, I don't believe we've met."

"Lord Black," Albus replied, his eyebrows rising in surprise at the emblem on Harry's shoulder. "Or should I say Warlock Black? It's been a while since I've seen a declaration patch worn."

The other Lords looked at Harry curiously, having not noticed or recognized the importance of the patch.

"Yes, well, I figure it's my first day here," Harry answered with an innocent shrug. "What better way to kick off my foray into the world of wizarding politics than with a little friendly stabbing among dignitaries?"

"A friendly stabbing?" Albus repeated as his eyes twinkled.

Harry was waiting for the moment he felt any sign of Legilimency but it never came.

"How often do you find stabbing… friendly?" Albus asked.

Sirius saw Harry and Albus were almost staring each other down. "Well, there was this swordfish the other day."

Three loud gong sounds rang throughout the Chamber of Lords, ending all conversation.

"Civic duty beckons, my Lords and Ladies," Albus said loudly.

The large group walked together out from the Chamber of Lords and into the half-filled Wizengamot general assembly. Sirius led Harry over towards the pulpit reserved for the Black hereditary seat. Sirius crossed the boundary on the alcove and the center chair magically grew into a slightly raised almost throne like wingback.

Harry followed right behind Sirius and when he crossed, there was a bright white flash attracting all attention their way. What had been one impressive wingbacked Lord's chair was now replaced with two identical regal seats.

"Great," Harry said blinking his eyes. "People are staring at us and I'm seeing spots. A little warning might've helped."

Sirius plopped down into the chair and was rubbing his own eyes. "I didn't know that was going to happen."

"Please everyone, be seated," Albus instructed from his commanding position in center of the first row. "Yes, we are graced by the presence of not one but two Lords Black for the first time and we will have a proper introduction to them after the vote."

As soon as the proceedings began, several people remained standing, waiting to be recognized. Albus called on the most senior member of the Wizengamot first, Lord Burke.

The skinny old man rested both hands on his cane, and imperiously announced, "I challenge the appointment of two Lords from a single house. It creates irreparable conflicts."

"You are certain you wish to challenge?" Albus clarified looking over his glasses at Lord Burke.

Lord Burke nodded.

"Lord Black, Warlock Black," Albus called. "You have been challenged. How do you respond?"

Harry stood up while Sirius just leaned back and rested his feet on the front banister of their pulpit. A few people were muttering over the lack of respect Sirius was showing.

Harry swept his gaze across the hall looking at everyone and lingering on the people still standing. He grinned deviously and began. "Now I suppose I can easily rebuke this amateur and sophomoric challenge by pointing out we still only one have vote per recognized wizarding line whether it's delivered by a Lord or an appointed representative. Having two Lords is no different from having two appointees of equal stature insofar as any vote in the Wizengamot is concerned."

Harry was relishing in the stern looks and cold stares headed his direction. "But I'm not going to do that, because as challenged and declared Warlock, I wish to earn the right to wield the Sovereign Saber."

Albus hid his surprise to find that there really could be some stabbing this evening. "The Sovereign Saber?" he repeated. "You realize no one has made any public mention of the Saber in all my years of service?"

"Sounds like it may be a historic evening then," Harry retorted with clear determination. "Because I want it."

Albus sat back tiredly. "This is why you wear an emblem of declaration?"

"That's correct, Chief Warlock."

"You do realize some could argue you are just wasting our time," Albus said. "We are more than willing to hear any reasonably brief comments you wish to make no matter whether you carry a sword or not."

"And if my comments aren't reasonably brief?" Harry replied showing he wasn't budging.

Albus heard the murmurs from the crowd and was stroking his beard. "I don't suppose you know who is currently in possession of the saber?"

Harry nodded. "I believe it is the Donnelly hereditary seat, as Lord Charles Donnelly wielded the saber at sessions as recently as 1782."

"1782, that's a little outdated," Albus said clearly not amused. He turned towards his right. "Sir Tapper, you're the representative for Lord Donnelly and the Donnelly family, are you not?"

"Yes sir," the lone man in a far less throne like chair of a private pulpit answered.

Albus knew it was fruitless but asked, "Did you perchance bring the Sovereign Saber with you?"

"Begging your pardon Chief Warlock, but until a minute ago I didn't know any Sovereign Saber existed."

"I surmised as much," Albus nodded and turned back to Harry. "I am sorry we are unable to accommodate you Warlock Black."

"Come now, Chief Warlock Dumbledore," Harry grinned dangerously again. "I don't think we have to throw in the towel just yet."

"Oh?"

"Wizengamot charter states that appointees cannot wield the saber anyway, so there's nothing Sir Tapper could have done with it even if he had brought it. But I assumed you of all people would know that the forger of the Sovereign Saber was also the swordsmith who made Godric Gryffindor's famed magical blade. And he made it with many of the same charms, notably including the ability to be called."

Harry glanced around as he explained, "In the absence of its current owner the Chief Warlock may call it and present it to a requesting noble line. Lord Donnelly may challenge to get the saber back the next session he attends, but if no one wishes to challenge my right to the blade by requesting it themselves, then I should be permitted and presented the Sovereign Saber."

"You certainly did your homework on Wizengamot charter history, didn't you?" Albus agreed, willing the Sovereign Saber to appear before him.

Harry nodded and ominously added, "Suffice it to say what I've learned has been disturbing."

"Very well," Albus said lifting the jewel encrusted but otherwise rather plain looking blade in the air. "Warlock Black has requested the Sovereign Saber. Is there anyone who wishes to dispute Warlock Black's claim?"

"A dispute on this matter is settled by a blades-only duel, correct?" A fit young aristocrat inquired. When Albus nodded, he quickly announced, "Yes, I wish to dispute the Sovereignty of Warlock Black."

"As will I," another man quickly stood.

"And I," a witch stood up announcing.

"I'm sorry Baroness Pince," Albus answered. "But you wear no declaration and are unable to dispute this. Baron Switzer and Lord Fullbright, your objections are noted." Albus raised his wand into the air gave it a couple of twirls, creating two plain swords sticking in the ground in the central floor of the Wizengamot.

"Baron Switzer, Warlock Black," Albus said waving his hands to large open area below. "Since neither of you has the right to the saber yet, you will both duel with the blades provided."

"Rules?" Baron Switzer sneered as he walked down to the courtroom floor.

"Unfamiliar with your Wizengamot charter, Baron?" Harry answered before Albus could. "Well, the rules are we swing our little poking sticks around until one of us yields or dies. Of note is the fact that the rules didn't provide for unconsciousness, and thus if you pass out I'll have to kill you to win."

Albus saw Baron Switzer look up to him and added, "What Warlock Black is overlooking is that the Chief Warlock can intervene and declare a winner when the outcome is no longer in doubt."

"But he doesn't have to intervene," Harry answered arriving at the first sword jutting up out of the stone floor. Harry wrenched the sword loose and was whipping it back and forth in the air. "Unless he really, really wants to."

Baron Switzer saw how inexpertly Harry was swinging the sword and thought he'd have a good chance. He pulled up his blade and held it steady, aimed straight at Harry.

Albus was reluctant to say it, but both combatants were staring back at each other silently. "Begin."

Baron Switzer was an accomplished swordsman and began to circle Harry.

Harry just stood there while he was being circled and the Baron just kept slowly moving closer in.

With a lunge, Baron Switzer swung his first strike at Harry.

Harry saw the attack coming and surprised everyone by using his free hand to catch the blade and grab a firm hold of it. He was cheating of course and it was the strength of a magical appendage that kept the strike from slicing his hand in two and instead only split the skin. A shallow cut was seeping blood, and Harry merely looked at it in annoyance.

The surprise on Baron Switzer's face showed and Harry took the opportunity to jab his sword straight at the man.

Baron Switzer twisted his body out of the way of the first two swings. He was unable to get Harry to release the Baron's sword.

"Hold still," Harry whined just before his third lunge connected solidly, piercing right through the man's armpit.

"Ahh!" Switzer's grip went slack and he'd let go of his blade in an involuntary muscle reflex.

Harry was still holding the sharp end as blood was dripping down his hand. He proceeded to poke Baron Switzer again with Harry's own sword.

The aristocrat gasped and shrieked, slapping a hand over his second open wound.

Harry just smiled and stabbed him once more hoping to avoid vital organs. "This is kind of fun."

Baron Switzer grunted and was sliced again rather shallowly. "Stop!"

"Do you," Harry paused and stabbed him in the thigh, "yield?"

"Yes, yes," Baron Switzer pleaded, as he was quickly losing blood. "I yield."

"Excellent," Harry agreed and stabbed the Baron in the foot. "Whoops. Sorry. That one was my bad."

Baron Switzer had crumpled to the floor as a couple men hurried down from the stands to tend to him.

Harry flipped what had been the Baron's blade, so he was holding it by the handle. He wiped his own blood off the sword and onto his cloak's sleeve. Once he'd sufficiently cleaned the blade, he used magic to launch it slicing through the air. It embedded deep into the wood of the chair just a few inches away from a seated Wizengamot member.

"Lord Fullbright," Harry said with a small bow. "I believe you were next?"

Lord Fullbright turned his head slowly to the blade that was still shaking back and forth from the sudden impact. He looked back at Albus and stated, "I think I'll retract my dispute for now."

"Understood," Albus agreed clearly not approving of Harry's barbaric actions. He waved his wand, vanishing both hastily conjured swords. "Warlock Black, I confirm you are the rightful wielder of the Sovereign Saber."

Harry mentally called for the enchanted sword and it appeared in his hand. "Thanks, Chief Warlock."

"Are you going to be challenging for my seat next?" Albus inquired watching Harry closely while Sirius just looked bored.

"Not today," Harry answered. "But we do still need to address Burke's challenge that-"

"That is Lord Burke to you, Warlock Black," Burke insisted angrily.

"Actually," Harry happily corrected. "The Sovereign Saber permits me to interject, interrupt, and demand to be heard at any time. You could beg me to continue to use your frilly little title, but the saber excludes me from the laws restricting speech and titles in all Wizengamot matters. Isn't that right, Albus?"

"You are correct, Warlock Black," Albus answered. "But I think perhaps you have made enough enemies for now."

"I'm just getting started," Harry said plopping back into his chair and kicking his feet up, mimicking Sirius' position.

Albus looked at the two Lord Blacks for a moment before addressing, "In any event, Lord Burke, I agree with Warlock Black's initial comments that the private dealings of a House are up to the House. And as long as the House retains a single vote, there isn't any legal precedent prohibiting more than one Lord of the family recognized by the Wizengamot. Do we need to vote on your challenge?"

Lord Burke shook his head irritably and sat back down.

"We have a vote before us," Albus explained. "The bill is Muggleborn Rights. We shall hear closing statements on both sides of the issue from Mr. Johnson and Madame Fillman."

"Excuse me," Harry blurted out happily. "Just one thing."

"Yes, Warlock Black?" Albus reluctantly answered.

"Since it seems like all the blood purists and traditionalists around here are very much in favor of this bill, and all the people that foolishly believe Muggleborns deserve equal rights are opposed to the bill, shouldn't we think about renaming it?" Harry said loudly. "I was thinking Muggle and Rights both sound fine, but what if we change 'born' into something more fitting like 'Hating Baby Rapist?' I know it's not quite as catchy, but Muggle-hating Baby Rapist Rights feels a lot more in line with the spirit of the bill."

"Thank you Warlock Black," Albus loudly replied, silencing cries of anger. "But renaming the bill is not up for discussion. The time for that has long since passed."

"Alright, just checking," Harry nodded while playing with the Sovereign Saber.

Albus ceded the floor to Mr. Johnson who spoke emphatically in favor of Muggleborn Rights, while Madame Fillman waited her turn to speak against the bill.

Harry tuned them out and turned to Sirius. "How are you holding up?"

"Maybe if I got to stab someone it wouldn't be so boring."

Harry tossed him the blade. "Be my guest. The House of Black and its Lord are in possession of the saber. Stab away with sovereignty."

Sirius was playing with the sword a bit and leaned over towards Harry. "Any thoughts on when or where you want to go back to work?"

Harry cast a small silencing charm around them and answered, "It's been two days."

"I know," Sirius admitted. "But I figure the work is going to get harder as we go, not easier."

"True," Harry said. "And yes, I've had some thoughts. As we speak, I've got a pair of small snakes working their way around figuring out how many marked people are in this room."

"Oh yeah," Sirius replied with a smile. "Are you that sure you're going to find any?"

Harry nodded. "Simmons and Darcy from the lounge are already on the short list."

"Speaking of short," Sirius attempted to segue. "What's up with you and Tonks?"

"Did Moony put you up to this?"

Sirius grumbled. "Moony doesn't even want to know. I get the feeling he was a little too overprotective when Tonks started dating. I think Tonks might have coerced him into a magical oath. So no, he didn't ask, this is just my own burning curiosity."

"We're just friends," Harry answered looking forward as Dumbledore had stood up to begin the vote.

"Friends?"

"Friends with benefits you could say."

"That's nice and all. Maybe you two can pass notes in the common room," Sirius interjected. "But I was looking for some details. I mean I've heard stories about metamorphmagi…"

"Stories, huh?" Harry commented. "Well, I wouldn't be surprised if they were all true."

"Not all of them," Sirius replied. "I know Andy and Ted didn't flip a coin and decide to raise her as a girl."

Harry bit his lip. "You know I don't think it's worth the risk to ask that one."

"So come on," Sirius asked. "Did Tonks make like Ginny and get the ghost off your back?"

"You know I haven't seen her in almost a week," Harry said. "She's probably due to appear at the worst possible time."

"So who'd you ask for?" Sirius insisted. "Hermione? Luna? McGonagall?"

"No, no," Harry said. "Nothing like that."

"You can't tell me she just looked like Tonks."

Harry shook his head with a grin. "Well not exactly. I mean there's something to be said for the ability to go from a blonde school girl to a redheaded French maid to a blue-haired high-priced hooker in a crotchless catsuit with fishnet stockings all without even changing positions."

"Outfits too?" Sirius was impressed.

"There was a perfectly good chameleon cloak hanging in the closet."

"That's why we got two. Brilliant!"

Harry saw people were being called on to cast their votes. "That girl has got one fantastic imagination."

"That girl is almost eight years older than you."

"She likes to go through almost every sort of fantasy you can think of just to see which ones elicit the strongest responses. And yes, this is during. She borrowed my glasses and did this stern librarian thing then she gave them back, morphed, and tried to sell me a box of cookies." Harry paused and tried to remember where he'd left the cookies. "Did you know she can fake a pregnancy? Massive bulge of the belly complete with welcome and unwelcome swelling. She even pinned me to the ground and ordered me to call her Dora the Sexplorer. What's that about?"

"You want to talk about names that are out there," Sirius jumped in and related. "That one muggle girl, whose name I'll never remember, she actually named my-"

"Wait," Harry interrupted. "You'll never remember her name, but you remember what she named your-"

"Yup," Sirius answered. "You'd remember it too if you got christened Lord Crotch, the Womb Raider."

Harry was unable to contain his snort. "Lord Crotch, the Womb Raider?"

"Yeah," Sirius grinned. "I'm not sure I get it, but I think I'm going to order a plaque made with that name."

"Lord Black and Warlock Black!" Albus Dumbledore's magnified voice broke through their silencing charm.

"Something the matter?" Harry innocently asked, knowing Albus had been calling for them the last thirty seconds.

"How do you vote on the bill titled Muggleborn Rights?" Dumbledore asked in a quieter voice.

Harry glanced at Sirius and back. "Nay."

"Thank you," Albus said. "Lord Black votes nay. Baron Blackenshire?"

"Nay."

Harry and Sirius tuned out the rest of the vote and continued to chat back and forth.

The vote finished and the Muggleborn Rights bill passed easily with sixty-four percent. Chief Warlock Dumbledore was saying the closing words of the session. "Traditionally at this point we would hear a few words from our newest members, but I am not certain that either Lord Black is paying attention right now."

"You'd like a few words?" Harry asked curiously.

"I don't believe there's anything in the charter you might have read," Albus mockingly answered. "But in the past, when someone new has taken over a seat, they would introduce themselves and maybe say a few words about any issues they feel strongly on. I think we'd all understand if you were unprepared for this."

Harry raised his hand as he stood up and began. "I don't think I need to prepare that much to introduce myself." He waved his hand back and forth at everyone. "Hello Wizengamot. I'm Harry. Though, I suppose in this room I'm Lord Black."

"Lord Black," Harry repeated. "I still think that's hilarious. A few years ago, I put on a ring for the purposes of warding a home I'd inherited. I just thought it was a ring. And then I find out it was the Black Family ring and it had accepted me as the new Lord. That's ridiculous. I just wanted to put up an apparition ward and suddenly that means I actually have a mildly important voice in one of the premiere governing bodies? That's retarded."

Harry shook his head as some people were muttering unhappily. "I did a fair amount of reading on the Wizengamot before tonight and I got to say this place is outdated and stagnant."

"I understand the idea that if it's not broke, then you shouldn't fix it. But I'm telling you, it's broke. Listen to me. I'm Lord Black and I have a vote. Something had to have gone wrong along the way for this to happen."

Harry saw he wasn't making any friends but that they were at least paying attention to him. "It's not that complicated. Hereditary seats plus a growing rate of inbreeding does not a good judicial and legislative body make."

"I'm not arrogant or foolish enough to believe I have all the answers. But if you try to feed me a plate of shit, I'm going to call you on trying to feed me a plate of shit. Like the bill tonight? That was a plate of shit."

"But I digress," Harry paused. "The short of it is that I consider it my civic duty to piss you all off. Thank you." Harry sat back down happily.

"Thank you Warlock Black," Albus tiredly replied. He looked straight at Sirius and asked, "Lord Black?"

Sirius glanced at Harry and pushed himself up to his feet. Sirius took a deep breath and began. "I'd imagine you all have taken notice of the fact that there are two Lord Blacks. And I don't want to give off the impression that we are anything but a united front. So I will simply reiterate the shared opinions of the two Lord Blacks in my own words: Fuck you all very much." Sirius smoothed down the front of his shirt and sat back down. "Thank you. And your mother twice."

Albus huffed in frustration. "I think that's enough for tonight. I call this session to a close. Good evening." Albus banged a magical gavel to his desk and gathered up the parchments around him.

Sirius stood up and looked at Harry. "Shall we make a dramatic exit?"

"You can if you want," Harry said. "I'm still waiting on a couple of reptilian delegates that wanted to keep an eye on the door."

"Don't sneak out on me," Sirius warned as he exited the courtroom and ran into a number of reporters and photographers.

Harry briefly chatted with the two scout snakes as he slipped them into his pocket. He had just begun to wonder how long he could wait in the courtroom when Sirius bellowed, "Get out here, Harry."

"What?" Harry came out quickly. "What's the matter?"

Sirius grinned. "Nothing. But it's a better photo op with both of us. Smile at the camera."

Harry turned towards a group of four photographers and was blinded by flashes.

"Lord Black! Lord Black!"

Harry saw Sirius wasn't going to let him get away and figured he probably owed Sirius for coming tonight. He turned towards the shouting man with the quill and notepad. "Yes?"

"Lord Sirius Black indicated that you wrote your own introductory remarks," the reporter supplied. "Could you expound on your meaning when you said you consider it your civic duty to piss people off?"

"Now you're just twisting my words," Harry argued. "I don't consider it my civic duty to piss people off. I consider it my civic duty to piss off the back-ass-wards inbred idiotic geezers who think blood purity matters. Given the performance of the Wizengamot over the last couple centuries, I think it's safe to consider back-ass-wards inbred idiotic geezers is a fair description of the majority."

The reporter gulped and glanced at Sirius smirking. "Can I quote you on that?"

"Sure," Harry said with a shrug.

"Aren't you worried about backlash from the other more senior members?"

Harry shook his head. "Not really. They could try to make up some new laws, circumventing all of their precious ancient charter, but to do so would actually mean they're breaking away from outdated traditions, which is basically the point of goading them in the first place. Not to mention, they'd be validating me as an opposing voice to the blood purists. A voice they were unable to deal with."

The reporter was furiously scribbling down everything Harry said. "When you say blood purist, do you really mean Death Eater?"

"I'm referring to the political landscape, not a recent terrorist organization," Harry replied. "The problems of our society aren't the fault of the addle-brained extremists but the fault of lazy people doing nothing to improve the status quo. If you want a quote, use this: the wizarding government is run by a bunch of the stupidest muggles you can find, who just happen to be able to do magic."

"We're just muggles who can do magic?" A firm but feminine voice clarified. "All of us?"

"Madame Bones," Sirius greeted. "I'm sure Lord Black here meant to imply everyone but you."

"Lord Black," Madame Bones greeted. "A couple of old friends are waiting over there and were hoping to talk to you."

Sirius spotted two Unspeakables he knew by name and patted Harry on the back. "I'll catch up with you later Harry."

Harry leaned over to Sirius' ear and whispered, "Keep your necklace on if you need a breakout. And remember, you're a Lord now. Something you weren't last time they drugged, interrogated, and obliviated you."

"You worry too much," Sirius assured him.

Harry watched Sirius walk away when Madame Bones repeated her earlier question. "So muggles who can do magic, huh?"

"I may have exaggerated a bit for shock effect, but basically yeah," Harry argued. "Too many wizards and witches think themselves different from muggles and have an us-versus-them attitude."

"And you don't?"

Harry shook his head. "Like I said, we're all muggles. It just so happens that most of us who can do magic are completely ignorant of almost everything else in the world."

"That's a pretty unpopular attitude," Amelia Bones pointed out without disagreeing.

Harry shrugged. "Popularity only matters to elected officials. I'm content to loudly disagree with everyone. And maybe ruffle a few feathers, sleep with a few daughters. All the things my bloodline and magical ability entitle me to."

Amelia Bones really didn't want to like Harry, but she couldn't ignore he had annoying charm. "Good evening, Lord Black," she dismissed. "Do me a favor and try not to stab any other members of the Wizengamot tonight."

"You have my word that I will try, but it's this Sovereign Saber," Harry said hefting his new toy, swinging it dangerously close to the reporter. "It lusts for blood and I can only resist its call so long."

Amelia said nothing else as she turned away shaking her head and hiding a smile.

Harry got word from Sirius that he was fine but would be a couple more hours.

Tonks then decided it was her responsibility to the Black family to take Harry out and find him a piece of tail.

It was only about twenty minutes after they'd arrived at the wizarding bar before Tonks had ditched Harry. The drummer for Stubby Boardman's reunion tour was too dishy to ignore in favor of her self-appointed responsibility to the Black family.

Harry wished her well and moved over towards the bar, where he saw a very attractive and familiar face drinking alone.

"Can I get you another of those?"

Susan Bones looked up to see Harry smiling at her. "Sure."

Harry signaled the bartender and sat down next to her. "Why would someone as attractive as you be drinking here alone?"

"That's your line?" Susan asked unimpressed. "You buy me a drink, you sit down next to me, and you loosely wrap a question around an uninspired compliment?"

Harry sipped on his own bottle of beer. "Well now that I've seen your confidence, I know we're not waiting on the boyfriend to arrive. And I was needlessly worried about coming on too strong."

"You were going to come on stronger?"

"You really want to tee that one up for me?"

Susan laughed, unashamed of the color in her cheeks. "So what would have your line been?"

Harry sat his bottle down and stared right at her. He silently watched her until she finally turned and asked, "What?"

"You remind me of Celestina Warbeck."

Susan gave Harry a curious glance. "I look nothing like her."

"No, you don't look anything like her," Harry agreed. "You're much cuter, but I never said you look like her. Just that you remind me of her. Two things about you actually."

"Oh yeah?" Susan asked. "What two things?"

"First thing," Harry argued playfully. "First is that you both blush the same when properly embarrassed and slightly flattered."

"Are we speaking from firsthand knowledge here?" Susan inquired.

Harry smiled mysteriously and continued, "The second thing is that you both get a deep husky voice after your second orgasm." Harry grinned as Susan nearly choked on her drink. "See? There's that blush."

Susan had to look away as she felt embarrassed to blush this time. "You're awful."

"I try," Harry agreed sticking his hand out in greeting. "Harry."

"I know who you are, Lord Black."

"And I know who you are, Miss Bones."

Susan turned to him in surprise. "Now that is interesting. And here I was going to suggest we get to know each other a little better. But it appears we know each other already."

"I may know your name," Harry pointed out. "But I would appreciate the opportunity to count and catalog every freckle on your body."

"I don't have any freckles on my body," Susan retorted.

Harry tipped back the rest of his beer and set the empty bottle down. "Prove it."

Susan was watching Harry and found herself relishing in the way his eyes felt on her. She knocked back the rest of her drink and got up from the bar. "Okay."

"Really?" Harry's voice cracked before he could stop himself. "Let's just pretend I didn't say that. You ready to go?"

Susan nodded and accepted Harry's hand. She let him pull her side-along as they apparated away.

Harry woke up suddenly trying to determine what roused him. He felt the calming sensation of a warm body next to him and smiled in remembrance of the night before. His fond recollection of newfound carnal knowledge was interrupted by a sharp chill in a very sensitive area. He glanced forward and saw the covers were still in place. He decided that even with a comforter in the way, Susan Bones still had great curves.

Harry's eyes widened and he became far more alert when he felt the chill again in the exact same place.

Harry slowly tried not to wake up the young woman next to him as he lifted the sheets over his head to assess and evaluate the potential shrinkage situation.

Ginny frowned harshly at him as her head was the only visible part of her incorporeal body sprouting up from the mattress. When she caught his eye, she brought up her fist again and punched Harry in the crotch.

The chill made a lot more sense now, but somehow felt even colder. "Ginny! Stop that!" Harry whispered angrily while trying to rub some heat into his body.

"You slept with Tonks!" Ginny whispered back.

"Now's not really the time-"

"Sirius says you didn't even ask her to look like me!"

"Well there's only so much blood in my body," Harry argued. "And it's hard to think when the little head called dibs on the circulation front."

"I understand you're scared, Harry," Ginny continued softly. "I know you don't know how to handle love-"

"Oh for Merlin's sake," Harry snapped loudly. "I'm not scared of you!"

"Harry?" the voice from the other side of the sheets warily asked.

"Get out of here!" Harry reached out, slapped both hands on the top of Ginny's head, and pushed her down. He was momentarily shocked to see he had actually managed to push a ghost away. He didn't have a moment to consider the implications when he was reminded of more pressing issues.

"Are you talking to me or your penis?"

Harry pulled the comforter off and smiled up at Susan. He saw the cool room air had an immediate effect creating some enticing goose bumps on her body. "Sorry about that."

Susan shivered and pulled the comforter back down to cover her. "Brrr. It's cold."

Harry grinned and cast a warming charm around her. "I'm a big fan of low room temperatures where you don't want to get out from under the covers."

"As long as you're not scared of your penis," Susan smirked. "By the way, does it talk back to you?"

Harry failed to mask his embarrassment explaining. "I was talking to… well, the ghost between my legs to be honest."

"Mmm-hmm," Susan agreed fully turning around to face towards Harry. She propped her head up with her arm. "Sounds like a lucky ghost."

Harry felt a sudden icy chill connect with his loins again and he gasped. He hopped up out of bed and hurriedly put his pajama bottoms on. He pulled on his chameleon cloak and shifted it into a fuzzy terrycloth robe. "Why don't I make us breakfast? Are you hungry?"

Susan sat up a little and felt the thrill of Harry's eyes on her body again. "I am hungry," she admitted beckoning Harry closer with a finger.

Harry slowly stepped towards her, fearful that Ginny's head might pop up suddenly. "You want some eggs? Bacon?"

Susan grabbed the waistband of his pajama bottoms and pulled him towards her. Her chin was resting on his bellybutton as she looked up at him. "I was thinking sausage."

"Pork or Italian?"

"Shut up."

"Okay."

It was almost an hour later before they were both satiated and famished. They walked down the stairs and could hear sizzling sounds coming from the kitchen. Harry pushed the door open, calling out, "Sirius? Are you making… oh."

Sirius was fighting with a frying pan at the stove, and it appeared his date for the previous evening was wearing only a bathrobe while she sipped some tea.

Harry didn't feel any shame as both he and Susan were dressed in similar bathrobes, but he was a little worried about the woman's presence.

"Hey," Sirius greeted and pointed at the woman jumping to her feet. "You remember-"

"Susan!"

Susan had walked right behind Harry and eeped in surprise. "Auntie Amelia!"

Harry looked at Sirius and pinched the bridge of his nose. "We have got to work on our communication."

Chapter 11

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Author's Note: I don't say it often enough, but a big thanks to all the fine folks helping me alpha and beta this fic including Jim, Chuck, Sean, IP, JJ, Rob, and Chris. I'm probably forgetting some but the help is appreciated even if I don't say it every update. I do so enjoy getting reviews. Thanks for all of them and keep them coming.

Harry woke up with the feeling it was going to be a morning like any other.

He cracked an eye open and saw Luna Lovegood sitting up, staring at him with wide unblinking eyes.

Harry lost the little faith he had in his initial feeling.

He then quickly thought back to when he first saw the Luna of this world. She'd waved him over to her table but he had been pulled away. He remembered Sirius called for help and then he remembered… pain.

Ginny Weasley.

No, not Ginny Weasley, Harry mentally corrected, Gin Weasley.

"Ginny is the name of a little girl who plays with dolls. A Ginny wants to be a princess. A Ginny wants to be saved by a knight in shining armor. A Ginny would get her pampered little ass kicked and thrown out of MY bar. There are very few people in this world I allow to call me that and neither of you are them. Can you remember that or do you need another reminder?"

Harry smiled in remembrance that about a half hour later Sirius had in fact received another reminder. Luna had joined them at the bar and they got to hear the story of how Gin beat Aberforth Dumbledore in a drinking contest and won herself a pub. And it had been Aberforth who had personally charmed the bar to make it easier for her to handle rowdy customers. Sirius made the mistake of asking for a demonstration and earned himself that second 'reminder.'

Harry recalled going to the mens' room and nearly making a mess as the pictures hanging above the urinals were apparently also charmed by Aberforth Dumbledore. Charmed to be action portraits of the faces made by the three most recent recipients of kicks from the charmed bar. So Harry had to try and pee straight while pictures of Sirius, Harry, and Sirius again all went pale, shivered, and had eyes that bulged out or rolled back up into their heads.

Just about everyone in the bar had been greeted and served by name. Harry had come to the conclusion that even if he'd wanted to try and play the role of the indignant noble Lord then he'd probably have a whole pub of people with something to say about that.

The most intriguing changes Harry noticed had been in Gin's attitude and character. He'd been extremely amused to see she was filled with strength, confidence, piss, and vinegar. Harry knew better than to mention it to the ghost haunting him, but he'd never been more attracted to any Weasley than when Gin looked at him indifferently. That was when he silently made a personal vow to never touch this Gin either. Primarily because it would make living with her ghost impossible.

He clearly recollected Fred and George coming by and agreeing to a partnership with them. The Black family would finance a significant expansion in exchange for a third ownership stake in the company. Requesting custom creations was planned but not until a little further in the future.

And then he remembered Luna saying something about the wuffwaffles in the air indicating it was the ideal time for enhancing the pleasure of intercourse. That was when Harry bid the three Weasleys and his godfather 'good night' and came back home with Luna.

This was where Harry's memories started to get really fuzzy. He remembered a crazed look in Luna's eye, small and furry purring, his own screams, and… something about friction inducing combustion.

"Harry?"

Harry was drawn out of his short jaunt down memory lane by the voice he'd been replaying in his head. His eyes snapped open and he saw Luna was still sitting there topless just staring at him.

"Do you remember me? I'm Luna," she indicated pointing towards herself. "Luna Lovegood."

Harry smiled at her peculiarity. "Yes, Luna. I definitely remember you."

Luna smiled brilliantly. "I don't have much time here, but I must say it is very good to see you."

"You too," Harry agreed happily humoring her.

"Oh! Oh!" Luna gasped in realization. "Did you find your godfather?"

Harry tensed immediately, knowing that information was supposed to stay private. "What do you mean?"

"Sirius? Your godfather?" Luna explained slowly. "You know, the reason you were working on the Exit?"

Harry's mind froze for a moment unsure what was going on. He squinted to look at her closer. "Luna?"

Luna frowned. "I thought you said you remembered me."

Harry's paranoia quickly downshifted into the 'What Would Mad-Eye Moody Do' gear. "Who did the commentary on my quidditch matches sixth year and who did I take to Slughorn's Christmas party that year?"

"Me and me," Luna answered before smiling back at him. "You don't have to prove it, Harry. If you say you remember me, I believe you."

"What… but…" Harry stopped, smiled, and lunged forward to catch her in a hug. "Luna! Why didn't you say anything before? Wait," Harry leaned back to get a better look at Luna's expressionless expression. "You said you didn't know me."

"When did I say that?" Luna frowned trying to think back.

"Last night," Harry reminded, "at the bar?"

"I didn't go to any bar last night," Luna answered in confusion. "I went to bed and read great-great-great-aunt Thethpa's diary. I've been spending my morning trying out a theory of hers she could never prove. I'm still a bit skeptical though so that may be coloring my perception."

Harry just looked at her trying to locate any identifying marks but got distracted by her bare breasts.

"You might be confusing me with the Luna native to this world," Luna explained before sticking a hand under the sheet testing her soreness. "Did you have sex with her last night? Because my vagina feels extraordinarily tender."

Harry nodded slowly before warily asking, "Luna, what have you done?"

Luna pulled her fingertips away from her nose when she realized she'd been caught smelling. "Since I last saw you? That's a pretty long list and if this is in fact a different dimension, I think you should forgive me for not having brought my photo album."

"I mean how did you get here," Harry clarified. "And why aren't you the Luna I met last night?"

"It's one of Thethpa's theories. Right now, I suppose, I am possessing this world's Luna," Luna answered.

Harry blinked. "You're possessing the Luna of this world? How?"

"As I understand it," Luna tapped her chin. "You know how you sometimes daydream? Or imagine how things could be different in your head?"

Harry nodded.

"Well when you do that, according to crazy aunt Thethpa, you're actually possessing yourself in another world. Her theory is that certain people can control it and stay in those worlds a bit longer than their subconscious minds intend to," Luna explained before pondering aloud. "I'm still not sure if I buy that. But I suppose if I don't then you're just a figment of my imagination. And I suppose I may have sacrificed another of the neighbor's cats unnecessarily."

Harry tried to picture what his life would be like if he were a figment of Luna's imagination. After several seconds where he was unable to come up with a difference, he figured he wasn't going to like the answer. "Okay," Harry paused once more and when nothing came to mind, decided to address Luna's earlier question. "And yes, I found Sirius. He was trapped in between this world and our old one for almost ten years. But he's doing real well now."

"That's wonderful," Luna smiled. "I told Hermione I was sure you were with him, but I was just saying that to get her to stop crying. I'm glad you didn't make a liar out of me."

"Hey," Harry suddenly realized he could get some answers to questions about his former world. "How is she doing? How's everyone doing? Did I get a funeral or are people trying to get me back?"

Luna shook her head. "The Ministry said it was too dangerous an artifact to keep around and that you nearly destroyed the arch when you got sucked in. Hermione thinks the Minister just didn't want you coming back."

Harry was guessing Hermione was probably right. "It was crumbling as I tried to hold on so it might have imploded. But still, I don't think I'd want to come back anyway."

"Good new world?" Luna asked cheerfully.

Harry grinned and nodded back. "No one knows me, well, that's not quite right. No one knows the Boy-Who-Lived. And just the other day I joined the Wizengamot and got to stab a guy. It's a lot more fun to be on the stabber side than the stabbee."

"Really," Luna said filing that information away. "I'll have to try that sometime. It does give me an excuse to track down Cho…" she trailed off deep in thought.

"So come on, how's everyone holding up? Hermione? The Weasleys? Minerva? Remus and Tonks?"

Luna shrugged. "Hermione cried a lot, but I think she was happy for you. The Weasleys felt kinda bad both because you were gone, and also Ginny was really gone now. Ronald was angry though that may be how he grieves. But really? I thought your death was rather… anti-climactic. No new Dark Lords suddenly appeared, no strange magical phenomena, not even an outbreak of green-eyed black-haired babies claiming themselves heirs to the Potter name. Well, yet anyway."

"Excellent," Harry agreed. "Do me a favor and let people know I'm happy and healthy."

"Okay," Luna answered.

"Hang on," Harry asked. "Can you teach them to possess themselves? They could drop in for a visit."

Luna stroked her chin in thought. "I doubt it. Great-great-great-aunt Thethpa could never do it. The only person I can think of that might be capable of managing the theoretical magic would be you. And you don't have a body in our world anymore. You're dead."

"Why just me and not the others?"

"Even if they were willing to pay the… erm, costs involved," Luna carefully worded. "We're still talking about magic across dimensions. And we know Ron, Hermione, and Neville didn't even hear any voices in the Exit. Besides, the more we talk, the more I'm convinced this is all my imagination."

Harry frowned, wanting to argue but trying to avoid any universe-shattering realizations. "So… umm… what else is new in my old world?"

Luna turned to make sure she had Harry's attention. "Listen Harry," she glanced at the clock. "I'm going to wake from this magical coma in about forty more minutes and I don't particularly want to spend the rest of my time with you trying to subtly convince me that you're real."

"I am real, you know."

"I know you think you are."

Harry pouted for a moment before conceding, "Fair enough." Harry sat up to face her. "What would you like to do for the next forty minutes in this world?"

Luna sighed shaking her head. "This is my imagination and I sought you out, Harry. What do you think people use their imagination for?"

"Oh?" Harry said before realizing, "Ohhh. Really? I thought that was just guys."

Luna swung her leg over straddling him and smiled dangerously. "You poor, naïve child."

Shortly thereafter, Harry regained some of his fuzzier memories. And the screams started up again.

Approximately thirty-nine minutes later, Harry and Luna collapsed against each other, entwined like a sweaty flesh pretzel.

"Hmm," Luna mused as her time was running out. "That was… exactly like I expected it to be."

Harry turned his head to look at her.

Luna shrugged. "I'm sorry Harry but Thethpa's theory is clearly just a fool's dream. And you are only a figment of my imagina-"

Harry was about to retort when Luna's head just fell forward and slapped against Harry's chest. It was approximately two seconds later that she began to snore, and Harry felt a drool puddle begin to form.

The Luna of his old world was gone. And the Luna of this world seemed quite tired.

Harry carefully extricated himself from underneath Luna and gave her a large pillow to snuggle. He put on some pajama pants and quietly left the room. He walked down the steps and was going to the kitchen when he heard voices coming from the den. He turned around and caught traces of a heated conversation. He spotted the floating spectral form of Ginny Weasley facing away and wondered why she hadn't come to say hello to Luna.

"It's not so much that I slept with him because he's Lord Black, as it is in spite of the fact that he's Lord Black."

Harry knew the voice was familiar but couldn't quite place it. He reached the den and stuck his head in to see who it was. He blinked. "Fuck."

"There's the lovebird," Ginny greeted with a wide smile.

"Aw fuck," Harry repeated glancing between the ghost and the witch. "Fuck."

"Who… him?" Gin the-very-much-not-a-ghost Weasley said, shaking her head. "That's Harry. He's not the Lord Black I slept with."

Harry heard the words and saw the ghost visibly pale. "Aw fuck."

"You what?" Ginny whispered dangerously, her incorporeal state shivering in air. "But… you… I… oh dear… my heart… Harry… I'm having a heart attack… Harry. Help me!"

"You're a ghost," Gin reminded the overdramatic apparition. "You don't even have a heart."

"Oooo," Ginny steamed, positioning herself behind Harry. "Don't hold me back, sweetie. Let me at her! Come on!"

Harry saw the ghost was pretending to reach forward while being supposedly restrained.

"You're a ghost," Gin repeated incredulously.

Ginny was seething. "I lied! That haircut looks horrible!" She snarled at what she felt to be an abomination to the Ginny Weasley name. "And you're fat."

Harry kept turning his head between the ghost over his shoulder and the proprietor of the Hog's Head on his left.

"My Harry's going to kick your ass," Ginny snapped pointing angrily at Gin. "And he's going to obliviate you. And he's going to give me your body. And together, we're gonna spit on your-"

"Ginny," Harry interrupted knowing he'd let this go on long enough. "Get out of here."

The ghostly Ginny turned towards Harry, looking shocked and heartbroken. "But…"

"Go!" Harry snapped.

There was a small poof and the ghostly form of Ginny popped into dust. Harry sighed and saw Gin Weasley resting comfortably on the couch. He winced. "There's a very good explanation for what just happened."

"I'm sure there is," Gin retorted.

Harry closed his eyes. "Out of curiosity, just how much did she tell you?"

"Not too much," Gin wryly commented. "But apparently we're going to have black and white magical roses in the centerpieces at our wedding reception… as Mr. and Mrs. Potter."

Harry flinched. "Fuck." He sighed knowing what he distastefully had to do.

"Listen, I-" Gin stopped when she saw Harry draw his wand. "Whoa!" She snapped out her own wand and held it steady in front of her.

"I'm not going to hurt you," Harry said moving towards her. "But you're better off not knowing some things."

"Stop right there," Gin ordered, quickly casting a shield around herself and turning her body sideways into an alert dueling position.

Harry caught her gaze and encountered immediate resistance to his gentle attempt at Legilimency. A little mental nudge and he discovered the start of her conversation with ghostly Ginny. Knowing now that he had all the mental distraction necessary, he quickly shattered her magical shield, twisted her wand straight from her grasp and used the remaining four magical arms to grab Gin's wrists and ankles, holding her in place in the air.

"Bugger me," Gin swore with wide eyes as she was pinned and held in the air. She hadn't even seen a spell.

"This is for your own good, as much as mine," Harry assured her, preparing to cast a memory charm.

"Wait! Wait!" Gin pleaded. "Hang on. Just hear me out."

Harry allowed his wand arm to relax while he pulled her close to hover right in front of him.

"Merlin," Gin breathed out as she was pulled through the air with just a thought. She looked at Harry and cautiously asked, "You're actually hearing me out?"

Harry nodded. "Contrary to what you might think, I'm not an enemy. And I like you well enough, considering I just met you last night."

"Yeah," Gin answered, feeling especially vulnerable. "I got the impression you're a regular chivalrous hero, though I think she might have been exaggerating a bit."

Harry figured that was an understatement but added, "You know the more we talk, the more I'm going to have to obliviate from you."

"Don't. That's what I'm saying. Don't obliviate me. I was thinking I could give you a conditional oath. Keep me magically unable to spill your secrets, rather than risk a charm I'd probably notice and eventually break."

Harry considered it for a moment, just looking at Gin. "I think perhaps you underestimate my skills at memory charms, but what sort of conditions are you looking for in an oath?"

"Nothing huge, just something like as long as you're not committing any heinous crimes or making me an accomplice to something, as well as maintaining a good business relationship with my brothers, I won't reveal your secrets."

Harry set her down and released her but kept her wand still out of reach. "I'm not sure if you've heard any of my opinions on the current state of affairs in the Ministry, but some things others might officially call heinous crimes, I may be a big proponent of."

"So what conditions are you looking for?" Gin said more than willing to negotiate.

Harry figured she just wanted assurance she wouldn't be in danger. "As long as I don't curse you, you can't talk about me?"

Gin shook her head. "I'm not that naïve. I've heard about your skill, or lack there of, with a sword so we're not limiting it to cursing. And being unable to talk about you at all would be too obvious. What if as long as you never mean harm to me, my family…" She paused for a moment before adding, "Or innocents in general then I can't tell anything about you, that is otherwise unknown?"

"Otherwise unknown is too vague. Change it to anything I don't allow you to and we'll even remove temptation from you," Harry said knowing conditional oaths could be unbreakable unlike those sworn on life or magic. Those could easily be broken at the cost of the oath-bound's life or magic.

Harry smiled slightly when he saw Gin reluctantly nod. He floated her wand right in front of her.

Gin took her wand and for a moment considered making a break for it before catching Harry's amused glance once more. She quickly swore her conditional oath to be unable to share anything about Harry that he didn't allow her to.

Harry relaxed considerably once he saw the tendril of magic form into a bond. It shrank smaller than his eye could see, but he could still feel its presence.

Gin put her wand away and sat back down. "You know my oath didn't say anything about Sirius…"

Harry knew she was demonstrating her trustworthiness by voluntarily offering that information but he still remarked back, "You know I can still obliviate you and not mean you any harm."

"Touché," Gin conceded before falling into an awkward silence. "So… are we cool now? Or…"

"We're good."

"Lovely." Gin boldly demanded, "So what the hell was that?"

"What was what?"

"Taking my wand and holding me up in the air like that. It felt like hands were actually around my wrists."

"That was just magic," Harry answered in an attempt to avoid the question. "You want some breakfast?"

"You're not going to tell me, are you?"

Harry smiled and jerked his head towards the kitchen. "Come on. Just because you're keeping my secrets doesn't mean I've got to tell you all of them."

Gin had tended bar long enough to know she was more likely to get answers if she didn't press for them. She nodded in understanding and walked with Harry down towards the kitchen.

"So what are you doing up so early?" Harry asked as he began to make enough breakfast for himself, Gin, and Luna. "And in that room too?"

Gin shrugged. "Running the bar means I'm nocturnal. We're still a good hour from my usual bedtime. And I was in that room looking for something to read before a certain ghost tried to possess my body and I quote, merge our pure untainted souls."

Harry winced and chose to skip over the metaphorical elephant in the room. "I doubt there was much worth reading in there. Some of those old books are cursed pretty nasty."

"I avoided the shelf with the tray to catch dripping blood."

"That's a good shelf to avoid."

The pair fell into an easy camaraderie and Harry saw glimpses of the friend he had in Ginny prior to her death. He figured tending bar made her a better than average conversationalist and was beginning to like the idea that he could spill any secrets to a welcoming ear and know magically, they were protected.

Of course, he still planned to kick Sirius' ass for managing to find someone even worse to bring home than the Director of Magical Law Enforcement.

"Oww!" Sirius yelled jumping up. He picked up the pine cone that had made its way onto his recliner in the brief seconds he'd been out of it. "Dammit Harry! I said I was sorry."

Harry just quietly hummed, while looking through the omnioculars at the solid walls surrounding the Malfoy land.

"You keep this up much longer and I'd swear you're jealous," Sirius added with a smirk.

A pine cone came mysteriously flying off the ground and beaned Sirius in the back of the head. "Oww!"

"Fine," Sirius said rubbing his head. "Not jealous, just PMSing."

Harry pulled the omnioculars away from his eyes and looked over at Sirius.

"I've been good," Sirius claimed. "We cleaned out Simmons place, got back all our ward eaters, made over twenty thousand galleons, and haven't spent a knut."

"You left that 'After Dark Mark' of the Death Eater Bandits again."

"It's our signature," Sirius argued. "And besides, if they hadn't printed the picture in the paper, you'd never have known so that doesn't count."

Harry didn't really care but felt he had to needle his godfather about something. He handed Sirius the omnioculars. "It doesn't look too inviting."

Sirius took the omnioculars and gazed through them. "You weren't kidding about locating the right frequency. I count at least a dozen different ward sets all within separate parts of the larger ones extending past the wall."

Harry answered. "Turn the magic knob to max and the overlay completely off."

Sirius pulled the omniculars away and set the two dials as Harry suggested. He looked through them at the Manor again. "What am I looking for?"

"Notice the murky green covering all of the basement and dungeons?"

"Mmm-hmm," Sirius affirmatively replied.

"That's similar to the color of magic the Dark Mark flashes when he issues a summons."

Sirius looked over at Harry. "What's that mean?"

Harry shrugged. "Could mean anything, but it's not a color I've ever seen in wards before. And we're way past my current understanding."

"Worst case scenario, what do you think it is?"

"It detects for the Dark Mark, it alerts everyone with a Dark Mark, or at least, Voldemort, it allows people in but not out, it neutralizes our magic, it kills us instantly. Take your pick."

"So what then?" Sirius asked while looking through the omnioculars again. "We loot everywhere else but those parts?"

"There's also a dark red ward over the entire guest house and several other areas," Harry added. "Another color that's new to me."

"So we avoid those too."

Harry shook his head. "I don't know if you can tell, but there's a large compartment under the drawing room floor. That's one of the places with the really good stuff. I think it might be a blood-warded safe."

"I know you're not saying we should do nothing to that pompous twit."

"I want to steal from him as much as you do," Harry explained. "But I think we'd be better off doing this job later, once we have a bit more experience and hopefully knowledge on our side."

Sirius frowned not wanting to say anything he might regret.

"You may notice the three main bubble wards are all solid and round: no gaps, no corners, no weak spots, and all over a meter apart."

Sirius nodded after resetting the dials and viewing with the mansion once more. "Didn't those new charmed thingies you bought allow us to extend beyond the limit of a meter?"

"Yep," Harry agreed. "But that's not the point. The distance separating them is a clear indication that they're up to date on the tricks ward-breakers use."

"Oh."

"I mean it, Padfoot. I want to rob Malfoy. And I want to trash his place. But we should stick with what works and learn more as we go."

Sirius sighed and tilted his chair back. "We still gotta stay here and do the homework though, don't we?"

"You know the answer to that," Harry said, flipping open his trunk. He reached down into it and grabbed a pair of chilled butterbeers. He handed one to Sirius and popped the top of the other.

Harry took a slow sip, while looking toward the Malfoy grounds. "Do you want to talk ideas on cracking this place? Or something other than work?"

"Other than work," Sirius answered. "My brain's going to be refusing to brainstorm for a bit. Tell me something I don't know."

"You don't know," Harry said. "So many options…"

"You're hilarious."

"I got one for you. Did you know we're just figments of Luna's imagination?"

Sirius glanced at Harry and saw he was smiling. "I must admit, I did not know that."

"Not this world's Luna, but the Luna of our original dimension," Harry clarified. "She told me herself last week."

"Hang on," Sirius interjected.

"Yup," Harry agreed.

"Luna from our old world talked to you last week? Wait, the one who spent the night?"

"Actually it was just for an hour in the morning that she possessed the Luna of this world and took advantage of me. But before our acts of depravity she caught me up on our old world a bit."

"You're kidding."

"Nope," Harry said sipping his butterbeer. "She told me they destroyed the Veil to make sure I couldn't come back, and that everyone seemed to be doing okay. She violated me in a wonderful way and then informed me that I, and by extension this entire dimension, was figment of her imagination."

"And you really think that was her?"

Harry nodded. "Oh yeah. No question in my mind."

Sirius gave an approving nod. "I bet she's a blast at parties."

"For freaking others out without even trying, she's in a class of her own. Now it's your turn," Harry said. "Tell me something I don't know about you."

Sirius took a moment, trying to think of something. "Cankles scare me."

"What?" Harry asked unsure he heard that right.

"Cankles," Sirius repeated. "You know those scary girls whose ankles are so thick they blend right into their calves? All the Holyhead Harpies have some scary cankles. Actually most female Quidditch players have cankles."

"And they scare you?"

Sirius grimaced. "Well, they're a hideous disfiguration, and usually indicative of the sort of girl who could kick a bloke's arse. Gin's aren't quite cankles, but they were close enough to remind me of my fear."

"You're a picky pervert," Harry decided taking another sip of his butterbeer.

"I got one for you," Sirius said after his mind had strayed towards ways to circumvent the Malfoy wards. "Why haven't you become an animagus? You said you'd tried."

"That's a good point," Harry realized. "Maybe I should try again."

"How exactly have you tried and failed?"

Harry shrugged. "I've read a couple of the books. I've done the practice exercises. I've searched inside for my spirit animal."

"Did you try the potion?"

"Three times."

"Black or white mist?"

"Neither," Harry said shaking his head. "Grey mist."

"Erm… my memory is a bit rusty. I thought black mist is for those without the ability."

"Yup."

"And white mist is when your form's undecided?"

"Or when you're too young to accept your animal side, if you favor MacArthur's interpretation."

Sirius frowned and looked at Harry. "So what does grey mist indicate?"

"Grey indicates I'm yet another exception to the rule," Harry retorted. "I've talked it over with Minerva several times, and she had a theory."

"Killing Curse?"

Harry was slightly impressed. "Wow Padfoot. It's good to see you thinking like McGonagall. And yeah, considering my circumstances, she thinks the Avada may have killed my spirit animal."

"I don't think like McGonagall," Sirius pouted. "So no animagus for you?"

Harry shook his head. "Not yet, but I'm going to try again. Because you know how some people can't tame their animals but can be put into enchanted sleeps to try and stay there long enough to mess with them? She dropped me into one for an hour and I was bodiless in the grey mist."

"And you saw something coming through the mist?"

"Sort of," Harry admitted. "I saw what looked like… well, someone. I thought it was me. But the form never fully solidified. I think I might have just left my body and turned around to look at it through the mist."

Sirius looked up, deep in thought. "Maybe you're not human. You could be a flobberworm and your humanimagus form is Harry Potter."

"Humanimagus form?" Harry tried out the word doubtfully.

"You're an octopus!" Sirius realized. "That's why you have the arms!"

"I'm not an octopus," Harry assured him. "I can make dozens of arms, not just eight. And I'm kinda doubting that I've spent my entire life in my humamamagus form or whatever. Though I should thank you for the mental image of my mum giving birth to an octopus. Besides, after those mixed results, Minerva put me in enchanted sleeps a half dozen more times. All I've seen is grey, sometimes it's kinda silvery but I've not seen any form since the first."

"Could you be a demiguise?"

Harry looked over at Sirius in surprise. "I hadn't thought of that."

"I mean you do kinda look ape-like and you could've been invisible all the other times."

Harry harrumphed. "I'll let that one slide because you actually had a decent idea."

"I have some indecent ideas too," Sirius offered.

Harry ignored him. "I think I'm overdue to try an animagus potion again, this time seeking out a demiguise."

"And if that doesn't work," Sirius said. "I could put you in an enchanted sleep."

"Yeah," Harry skeptically replied. "Or maybe Moony could put me in an enchanted sleep."

"A demiguise would be a great form for a thief," Sirius said. "Could turn yourself invisible at will."

Harry smiled hopefully. "Now that you mention it, I am craving a banana."

"You know a banana-"

"Keep your indecent ideas to yourself, Padfoot," Harry interrupted.

Sirius opened and then closed his mouth. After a couple seconds of silence he added, "I think that's all of them."

The two continued chatting amicably for two hours through the twilight and as the sun set. Sirius was trying to make his impatience as clear as possible without giving in and actually asking if they could call it a day.

Harry sat the omnioculars back down. "You about ready to get out of here?"

"Oh thank Merlin," Sirius readily agreed jumping to his feet.

"We can go," Harry smirked. "Just as soon as you tell me how to get into Malfoy Manor, disregarding the wards we can't identify."

"Dammit Harry," Sirius whined trying to come up with something. "I don't have any idea short of simply stretching a hole in every layer."

Harry sighed. "And from the looks of just the outer ones that'd take about a month assuming it didn't get noticed within an hour."

"Which knowing the twit, it would," Sirius insisted. "Honestly, I think our only hope is going to be getting Lucius to add us to his wards."

"I'm not sure how open to that idea he'd be."

"We'd have to ask him real nice," Sirius argued. "And it would take away some of the subtlety and elegance associated with the Death Eater Bandits."

"Feels like cheating too," Harry said. "But for Lucius, I expect I could overlook that."

Sirius nodded before turning on his puppy dog eyes. "Can we go now? Please?"

"Yeah," Harry agreed tossing everything they'd brought with them back into his trunk. He shrunk his recliner and Sirius' too dropping them in. "We've got enough info on these wards to try and figure something out. But tomorrow we should begin the preliminary work on Burke and Darcy."

"Tomorrow," Sirius whined, drawing out the word. "Haven't we earned a day off?"

"I won't make you work if you don't want to," Harry said making sure everything was packed up, before beginning to dismantle the Fidelius. "But I'll probably be doing some shadowing and intel gathering like a good, subtle, and elegant Death Eater bandit."

"I know you want me to feel guilty, but I don't," Sirius stated hoping it'd keep Harry from working tomorrow.

Harry nodded. "Charm is coming down. Apparate to Diagon Alley first in case someone tries to trace us." The anchor stones of Fidelius charm all crumbled inwards and the hidden square of space flashed.

Two soft pops and there was no sign of their former presence.

They walked to the entrance of the Leaky Cauldron and apparated back to Grimmauld Place.

Right when they arrived next to the bookcase blocking Mrs. Black's portrait in the foyer, Harry silently held up a hand to stop Sirius.

"What is it?" Sirius whispered drawing his old driftwood wand.

"Someone's here," Harry said testing the wards over their home. "And it's not Tonks or Moony." He pointed Sirius towards the living room while Harry quietly went to check the kitchen.

Sirius stuck his head into the living room and couldn't believe his eyes. She was looking straight at him, so he attracted Harry's attention by loudly spitting out the name, "Bellatrix."

Harry was by Sirius' side immediately and barely recognized the far more attractive Death Eater. Harry doubted she'd spent any significant time in Azkaban. "She's alone," Harry assured Sirius while loosely aiming his own holly wand.

"Lord Bla-" she began right as the first spell was fired her way. A smooth practiced motion and a pink humming shield snapped into place around her. It easily deflected the yellow jet of light and ricocheted into a wall sconce, melting it immediately.

"You've got a lot of nerve," Harry warned her sending two light blue spells towards her left and right sides.

Bellatrix twisted sideways avoiding them both while swatting away the next spell Sirius cast.

Harry sent a large area blast at her, and she was forced to take cover behind a couch.

Sirius and Harry kept up a flurry of spells as they began to circle and close in from separate sides of the room.

It was a testament to her skill that she'd only been grazed by a couple of cutting curses.

Sirius faked a quick lunge towards her, after Harry's signal. Utilizing the distraction, Harry was now close enough that one of his magical arms snuck past her defenses and quickly twisted her wrist and wand behind her own back.

"Ahhh," Bellatrix shrieked as her body arched away from Harry, leaving her wide open and vulnerable.

Sirius had already begun casting the spell he'd dreamed of hitting her with, before Harry had effectively rendered her temporarily harmless and twisted her to expose an unprotected front.

Bellatrix's face locked in surprise when the crimson jet of light collided with her midsection and washed over her. Her legs went limp and her head made a loud crack as it bounced off the hardwood floor.

Harry looked at Bellatrix's prone form on the ground and his godfather's triumphant expression. "Was that spell what I think it was?"

"If you think it was the blood freezing curse," Sirius relished in answering, "then yeah. It was."

Harry had just started to relax when he saw Bellatrix's body convulse and flip over onto her back. He sent a stunner at her for good measure, but she managed to get a weak shield up.

"Lo- Lord Blacks," she slowly stuttered out the words as her body began to shut down and her arms began to shiver. "I'm- I'm- I'm he-here to pledge loyalty… to the family."

Sirius' look of triumph disappeared as he stood up a little straighter. "Did she just-"

"Yup," Harry said, rubbing his temples. He'd been so surprised she wasn't taunting them or using her bloody annoying baby voice, that he completely overlooked the fact that Bellatrix hadn't cast a single spell at them.

Sirius looked like he'd just swallowed a doxy. "Aww… bugger."

Chapter 12

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

"I don't suppose you're gonna try and convince me we should just let her die?" Sirius half-heartedly asked.

Harry let out a loud sigh while looking down on the shuddering form of Bellatrix. He lifted her sleeve and found what he already knew to be there, the Dark Mark. "No. I'm not."

"Stupid bloody Gryffindors," Sirius said, referring to himself and Harry.

"As ridiculous as the privileges provided to a noble Lord are," Harry reluctantly explained while Bellatrix's shivering slowed down. "I can't help but take the 'responsibility to the family' aspect of it to heart."

"Bugger."

"Blame the Dursleys," Harry said looking up with a weak smile. "I do."

Sirius was curiously watching her shudders finally reach an end as she lapsed into unconsciousness. "I don't suppose you happen to know the counter to the blood freezing curse?"

Harry whipped his head towards Sirius. "Excuse me?"

Sirius frowned. "Yeah… didn't think so." He shrugged helplessly.

"Fuck," Harry said, suddenly grasping the full disaster of their situation. He quickly tried to think of anyone they could call in the next minute who would be able to counter that curse. The only people he could think of that might know the counter and would trust him enough weren't from this dimension.

"I do know the counter has to come from the same wand, so we'd need someone compatible," Sirius added seeing the wheels in Harry's head had begun turning. "And I think it's a different blood based curse rather than just a spell reversal."

"Dammit," Harry decided. "We're taking her to St. Mungo's."

Sirius had surmised as much. "You know they're gonna notice-"

"Yeah, I know," Harry said as he bent down to scoop up her body and felt the absence of heat. "Ah hell, she feels like a reptile." Harry grabbed a handful of floo powder and tossed it into the fireplace. "St. Mungo's!" He called out as he and Bellatrix were whisked away.

Sirius quickly followed after.

Harry emerged in the front lobby of the hospital for magical maladies and injuries. He was carrying Bellatrix's limp body, while making sure her sleeves stayed down. Harry scurried up to the front desk asking, "Emergency?"

The lady just looked up at him and pointed towards the right corridor.

Harry nodded and began to jog that way spotting a generic mediwitches' desk. "I need a…" Harry trailed off and had stopped his running as he recognized one of the last people he was prepared to see.

Lily Potter had been visiting an old friend and was headed towards the public fireplaces. She moved out of the way when she saw a young man barreling toward her carrying a woman in his arms. As he approached, she felt something inside of her calling out to him. She was inexplicably drawn to this man. She just stared at him with her wide identical green eyes as he slowed down to walk past in a moment that felt frozen in time. Her mind was belatedly processing the fact that this was one of the new Lord Blacks her son had been so impressed by.

There was an ache inside Harry that he'd not felt in years and didn't expect to ever feel again. If he had been more alert to his surroundings he would have registered her presence much sooner. But it was magic that informed him this was Lily Potter before his eyes had ever made that connection.

Sirius caught up with Harry and began to push him forward. "Kind of in a hurry, here, Harry."

"Right," Harry said as he snapped out of his momentary daze, unwilling to contemplate the Lily Potter of this world right now.

Sirius flashed Lily a smile and nod as he pushed Harry towards the emergency rooms. It was only after they were gone that Lily realized he had been carrying Bellatrix Black, a woman widely assumed to be a Death Eater.

"Healer Armstrong!" Sirius called out spotting a familiar face while Harry dashed into the first empty room he found. "We got an emergency here."

The man in question recognized Sirius Black and allowed him to direct him towards the room. "What's the problem?"

"She was hit by a blood freezing curse a couple minutes ago," Harry answered, glad to see Sirius closing the door behind him.

Healer Armstrong put his hands around her neck to estimate her temperature and check how strong her pulse was. "Did you cast any warming charms on her?"

"No sir," Sirius quickly answered.

"Good," the healer replied hurrying over towards a cabinet of supplies. He grabbed several vials of potions and hurried back towards the patient. "This is going to get bloody, so wait outside if that makes you queasy."

Harry and Sirius both shook their heads.

Healer Armstrong quickly grabbed a blade and sliced open arteries on both of Bellatrix's wrists. He directed a pair of pans to the floor that were catching the thick dark blood oozing out while he forced potions down her throat.

Harry glanced at Sirius inquisitively.

Sirius caught the unasked question and answered. "Healer Armstrong was the first healer I woke up to a few months back."

The healer had repositioned both of Bellatrix's hands over a single tray with a drain attached to her abdomen. The blood was being funneled back into her body, leaving a nasty black sludge residue in the pan filter.

Healer Armstrong let out the breath he'd been holding as the tension and pressure of the situation had passed. He picked up a pink magically heated blanket and slid it behind Bellatrix's back, wrapping around her neck. "Okay," Armstrong said. "You guys got her here just in time. I expect after several days of feeling weak she should make a full recovery."

Harry and Sirius didn't exactly jump for joy, but nodded their heads in appreciation.

"Now before I call the aurors because of a certain tattoo on her arm," Healer Armstrong forcefully asked, "Is there anything else I need to know?"

"We're not sure," Sirius answered, hoping Harry knew better than to attempt a memory charm. "But we'd appreciate it if you didn't call them."

The healer didn't show any emotion as he asked, "Why not?"

Harry answered, "Because she's a Black who got hit by a blood freezing curse. With her last words before passing out she asked the Lords Black for protection. If she knew to come to us, then she knows that it means abandoning the Death Eaters."

"She's leaving the Dark Lord and his Death Eaters?" Armstrong clarified.

"I'd imagine the loyal ones don't get hit with that curse very often," Harry deftly replied.

Armstrong turned to Sirius. "So why aren't you sure what else I need to know?"

Sirius shrugged. "'Lord Blacks, I'm here to pledge loyalty to the family.' That's everything she managed to get out when we met her for the first time a few minutes ago."

Armstrong sighed. "I still have to report this." He held up a hand to stop their objections. "But I think I could hold off on informing the authorities until after she's been discharged into your care. I want her to stay overnight for observation, but in the morning I expect she'll be able to leave."

"Thank you," Sirius said with Harry nodding his assent.

"I've got restraints activated on the bed," Armstrong explained. "She could wake up within the hour or perhaps not until morning. In the meantime though I want at least one of you with her at all times."

"We're not going anywhere," Harry assured him. "We need to get some answers from her ourselves."

Healer Armstrong nodded in understanding and in a more friendly cordial tone asked, "How've you been, Sirius?"

"Great," Sirius answered. "Better than I've felt in years."

Healer Armstrong smiled a little for the first time. "I'll be back in a couple hours to take her off the filter." He shut the private room's door closed behind him leaving Harry and Sirius alone with the pale but temporarily harmless Bellatrix Black.

"Fucking Lestrange," Harry grumbled.

"Not Lestrange," Sirius corrected. "She's never been married here."

"Really?" Harry asked in surprise.

Sirius nodded.

"For some reason I thought everything before Halloween 1981 in this world was going to be the same."

Sirius shook his head. "Considering how strong Voldemort was in our world at that time, this place would have been fucked if that were true. No, it's close to the same but there's a few differences. Of course you were barely a tickle in Prongs' leg around then, so you might not recognize some of the differences."

Harry nodded in agreement. "It's somewhat comforting to know she didn't torture Neville's parents into insanity."

"That's not to say she hasn't done that to others but Moony doesn't think she's ever been arrested," Sirius said. "Frankly, the only thing they may even have on her would be being a Death Eater."

"Is that a crime?"

"Probably," Sirius said as he flicked her toe really hard. "God I hate this bitch."

"I'm with you."

Sirius looked at her closer and saw small flinches of pain and discomfort on her face. "She looks damn good though."

"Sirius," Harry winced. "She's your cousin."

"So?" Sirius shrugged. "It's not like I'm planning to make some three-headed cyclops pureblood heir. She's a cruel bitch and she's hot. Those two characteristics go together an awful lot."

"And what would the two Aunt-Mums have to say about this?"

Sirius shook his head. "You and your silly muggle-raised ideals."

"My only cousin was Dudley."

Sirius banished the mental image and spoke softly, "I don't think I want to forgive her." He took a deep breath. "Even though this one hasn't ever done anything to me. And she's hot."

"Oh for Merlin's sake," Harry groaned.

"I'm sorry," Sirius said. "It's just so much easier to hate ugly chicks. I'm… confused."

"About what?" Harry yelled. "Whether or not she's going to kill you in this world too?"

"Please Harry," Sirius said with a roll of his eyes. "You've got that honor reserved."

"Oh yes," Harry snapped. "Pick on the orphan boy with guilt issues."

"You're not that upset," Sirius lazily waved Harry off. "But speaking of… it sure looked like Lily recognized you back there. That's a pretty damn impressive mother's intuition."

Harry sighed trying not to think about it. "That wasn't mother's intuition."

"Of course not," Sirius agreed. "I'm sure Lily always greets new people carrying Death Eaters by staring with her mouth open."

"Dammit," Harry swore. "You know she might actually guess pretty close for all the wrong reasons."

"The wrong reasons?"

"Never mind," Harry said waving him off. "Anyways… no one will ever believe the truth, as long as we keep denying it."

Sirius wondered briefly what Harry meant but was interrupted by a moan from the bed.

Harry and Sirius were at her side immediately. Sirius had drawn his wand, while Harry revealed Bellatrix's. "Don't move," Harry instructed. "The curse is still being flushed from your blood."

Bellatrix heard the calm voice that had sounded so angry before. She blinked her eyes open and looked to her left and right. "Is this St. Mungo's?"

"Yes," Harry answered without explanation. "Are you prepared to disavow allegiance to any other Lord and swear your loyalty to the family?"

Bellatrix leaned forward and got a little dizzy from the head movement. "My sister seemed to think you might be able to protect me."

"Protect you from what?" Sirius asked, speaking up for the first time.

"The Dark Lord, the Death Eaters," she weakly answered, "the Ministry."

"You still haven't answered my question," Harry said.

"Nor you, mine," Bellatrix snapped.

Harry and Sirius glanced at each other warily.

"Yes," Bellatrix said breaking the uncomfortable silence. "I am prepared to, but I was hoping to meet you before deciding whether I should or not."

"We can't promise or guarantee your safety," Harry explained. "But for as long as you remain a loyal member of the Black family, I will do everything in my power to protect you."

Bellatrix turned to look Harry in the eye. "You will stand against him?"

The him in question was clear as day. Harry held eye contact with her and answered, "When he stands against a Black, yes."

Bellatrix saw a determination in Harry that reminded her of the Dark Lord and turned to look at Sirius. From him she felt a warmth that reminded her of the Dark Lord. She let out a sigh. "I've no doubt a healer has seen the mark I carry. What happens when the aurors come?"

Harry lifted his hand displaying her wand. "I know the cunning of Tom Riddle and sending you to gather information on us is by no means a stretch for him. I think it's time you rejoin the family before we humor any more of your questions."

"I've seen your respect for wizarding tradition," Bellatrix answered knowing she couldn't reach for her wand if she wanted to. "So this is my choice? Joining a couple of muggle-lovers who are all set to hand me over to my reserved seat in Azkaban or going back to the situation that you know I want to leave?"

"You're the one looking to upgrade Lords," Harry countered. "It's not like our life is going to be any simpler with you under our protection."

Bellatrix still hesitated.

Sirius looked at Harry and said, "She had her chance. Let's go."

"Wait!" Bellatrix called out. "I'll swear."

Harry nodded at Sirius and slipped her wand into her right hand. Her wrists were still draining chunky blood at a rate equal to the blood flowing back into her body.

Bellatrix took a breath and said, "I hereby pledge my life, my loyalty, and my magic to the House of Black. In doing so, I disavow and sever any previous allegiances others may claim to my life, my loyalty, or my magic. So mote it be."

Harry and Sirius both felt the invasive pulse in their Black family rings and replied in unison. "So mote it be."

"So mote it be?" Harry repeated in a higher voice after the magic in the air finished. "People don't talk like that."

Sirius snickered.

"Stupid old magic using archaic language," Harry grumbled.

Bellatrix collapsed back and Sirius took the wand from her before it fell into the tray of blood. "What have I done?" she wondered for the first of many times.

Sirius grinned deviously. "That's exactly what we want to know, Bella. What have you done?"

Bellatrix hissed and tensed at the sting in her arm. "He's calling me. You gotta get me out of here."

"No," Harry calmly answered. "You're not answering this one. Tonight you're staying here, healing, and then tomorrow morning we're checking you out. Your healer has agreed to put off contacting the aurors until we're gone. After that we can hide you or move you."

She was gritting her teeth as she added, "Maybe we should have them amputate the damn thing while we're here."

"Wouldn't help any," Harry said. "The mark is based off a bastardized serpent tattoo, but one of his modifications was including soul magic. It's visible on the skin, but attached to the soul. Lose the arm and you'll still feel the magic."

"You sure, Harry?" Sirius clarified with a knowing look. He was reminded that Harry had been incorrectly assuming everything before their deaths here was the same. "Why not take a look?"

Harry pulled up her sleeve to look at the Dark Mark and was shocked by what he saw. At first glance it looked exactly the same. Only this one was not burning red, but was in fact animated with the tattoo snake weaving in and out of the tattoo skull. Harry leaned down as he heard soft hissing coming from the serpent.

"The bitch won't like it," the snake rhythmically hissed. "Master's calling, Master's calling. The bitch won't like it." It paused again, before repeating its short song. "Master's calling, Master's calling."

Harry blinked having recognized the tune. "This little bugger is singing."

"What?" Sirius asked.

"What am I doing?" the snake tattoo stopped in surprise to ask.

"It stopped," Bellatrix announced happily as her face softened.

"Whoops," the snake said as it began moving wildly again.

Bellatrix winced. "Spoke too soon."

"Hey," Harry hissed in parseltongue at the Dark Mark. "Do me a favor and stop that for a second."

Bellatrix flinched at the sound, while Sirius looked happily disturbed by it. The snake tattoo froze in surprise, but it was the voice from the hospital room door saying, "Wow," that startled Harry.

"Don't mind me," Healer Armstrong said while closing the door behind him. "I just need to check on my patient."

Sirius backed away from her bed and Armstrong took his place by her side. He began to cast diagnostic charms while Harry continued his conversation.

"Thank you for stopping," Harry said.

"Who are you to command me?" the snake asked curiously.

"I do not command you," Harry said. "I can only ask as a courtesy for… the bitch."

"Then I must continue," the snake explained beginning to slither around the tattooed skull. "Master ordered me to continue until she answers the call."

"She has felt the summons and now stands at her Lords' side," Harry explained to the serpent. "Your work is done."

The snake began to slow and came to a stop after thinking it over. "I will extend you this courtesy until Master commands me again."

"Thank you," Harry said as the tattoo went back to the static image normally associated with the Dark Mark. Harry looked up and saw Bellatrix, Healer Armstrong, and Sirius were all watching him closely. "Sorry about that but your Dark Mark doesn't speak English."

"I didn't know it spoke at all," Bellatrix murmured.

"It's quiet, but yeah," Harry explained. "I told him you felt the summons and are at your Lords' side. He agreed to stop until 'Master' commands him again."

"Fascinating," Healer Armstrong said with a grin.

"Don't you start," Harry interrupted the man. "We're not going be fetal flobberworms for your experimentation. How's she doing?"

"Improving rapidly," Armstrong answered. "Might be well enough to leave soon, but I'd still prefer to keep her overnight." He turned towards Bellatrix, "I expect you'll get intermittent chills for the next few days and you'll feel quite weak. If after two weeks, you still get a chill, inform a healer. You may have to filter your blood again. Don't assume it's nothing."

Sirius assured Armstrong that one of the Lord Blacks would stick around all night, if not both. Armstrong was leaving for the night, but would be back in the morning and left instructions for no others to check on her.

Once the healer was gone, Bellatrix sagged back into her bed. "May I ask you something, my Lords?"

"Don't call us that when the situation doesn't dictate it," Harry said. "My name is Harry."

"You can call me your Lord," Sirius countered.

"Right," Bellatrix said looking between the two before looking down. "I just wondered… who was it? Who did I hurt or kill? Or who do you blame me for?"

Harry and Sirius looked at each other, partly wanting to keep her in the dark despite knowing the oath to the family should protect them. Harry asked, "What do you mean?"

Bellatrix kept her head down staring at her freshly healed wrists, not wanting to look up at them. "I know a look of hatred, a thirst for revenge. Both of you had that look in your eyes. So I wondered who it was that caused you to look at me that way."

Harry sighed and waved at Sirius to answer her.

"Sorry Bella," Sirius decided. "We'll protect you, because you are family. But that doesn't mean we trust you." He paused at the look of sadness on her face when she closed her eyes. He felt like giving her a glimmer of hope adding, "Nor is that to say we never will."

"We just don't want to," Harry admitted pulling out the recliners for himself and Sirius.

Albus Dumbledore watched the faces of people as they entered the room. This was one of the better barometers for measuring the volatility of their current struggle against the Dark Lord Voldemort. When there were numerous smiling and laughing faces they were at their most relaxed. But when they looked somber and stayed quiet, it was because they could sense the oncoming danger, fearing the calm before a storm. The most violent atrocities and horrible actions of Voldemort had always come suddenly and then he would go silent to revel in the moments of fear he inspired.

Albus hoped this wasn't going to be one of those times. Based on the laughter coming from Remus, Tonks, and James Potter Jr., he felt he may not need to worry. But it did not escape Albus' notice that these three were the most likely to be singing the praises of the enigmatic Lord Blacks.

"Please everyone," Albus announced. "Be seated. We have a number of new items to discuss, as I'm sure anyone who has read today's paper will know."

There was muttering and curious conversations springing up all around the Order meeting.

"For those of you who may not have heard," Albus explained. "Bellatrix Black was admitted to St. Mungo's to be treated for some rather serious curse damage. She stayed overnight and was released into the custody of the two Lord Blacks, as the parties responsible for her well being. After her healer discharged her, he then called the Department of Magical Law Enforcement and informed them that Miss Black bore the Dark Mark on her arm."

Albus could easily tell the few who hadn't heard this news from the looks he was receiving. "I have spoken to Healer Armstrong wondering why he didn't contact the aurors immediately, and he determined there were no outstanding warrants for her arrest, saw her commit no crime, and felt the allegiance issue was an internal family matter. He wasn't going to violate any patient confidentiality, but I believe he may have treated Lord Sirius Black in the past."

Albus held up a hand to forestall objections and said, "We may not have any proof of her crimes, but she could be an extremely valuable resource for the knowledge and experiences to which she could testify."

"What's the Ministry doing?" Bill Weasley asked.

Albus glanced at James Potter and then Tonks who both shrugged inconclusively. "They have no substantial evidence or implications of illegal activity, but they are seeking reasons to justifiably bring her in for questioning. The protection offered by her family complicates the issue both legally… and because they could simply hide her away at any time."

"What do you mean by the protection?" Arthur Weasley inquired.

"According to Healer Armstrong, the Lord Blacks were only willing to assist her after she disavowed her allegiance to the Dark Lord and pledged herself to the Black family. As a sworn member of an ancient and noble bloodline, her Lords assume some legal responsibility and culpability for her. The laws are a bit muddy, particularly among the noble families that predate the Ministry."

Albus pursed his lips and sat back for a moment. "I met Lord Harry Black for the first time before our Wizengamot session. He basically informed me that he was going to cause problems including 'a little friendly stabbing among dignitaries.' I assumed he was speaking metaphorically at the time." Albus frowned though his face twitched a little. "I was wrong."

Hestia Jones summarized, "So we've got the Lord of a dark family publicly stabbing others, associating with known Death Eaters, and now secreting away a valuable source of information?"

Albus nodded and continued. "There is also another thing I discovered from Healer Armstrong. He said that Lord Harry Black was capable of communicating with the Dark Mark."

More wary muttering sprung up. Tonks spoke up to try and prevent them from jumping to too many inaccurate conclusions, "Well, that's not all that surprising. I mean it is a magical snake tattoo and he is a parselmouth."

"He's a what?" James Potter clarified.

"A parselmouth," James Jr. answered with a nod from next to his father. "Harry told me and Uncle PJ he was always surprised animagi don't get grouped in with the same misconceptions. And that if people weren't so prejudiced about a language, maybe the nicer folks with the talent wouldn't have to keep it like some dirty secret."

"Maybe," Sturgis Podmore uncertainly agreed. "But even if it doesn't automatically turn him into a dark wizard, it is a warning sign. And there's an awful lot of warning signs popping up around these Lord Blacks."

"I saw him," Lily interjected. "Running down the hall in St. Mungo's with Bellatrix in his arms. She was really pale and looked dead, but he… he's not evil. He felt familiar."

"You saw him? Wait, you saw her?" James said in surprise. "And you never mentioned it before now?"

Lily had the grace to blush at her husband. "I barely even processed that it was her. I've been trying to figure out why he felt so familiar. When he was staring at me, it was like we were drawn to each other. To be honest, at first I thought I had a monster in my chest, rolling around and kicking to get out."

James leaned back warily asking, "Are you pregnant again?"

"No, heavens no. But I just can't figure out what it is about Ha-Harry," she stumbled over the name for a moment. "The only thing I could think of is that he reminds me of the son we lost, because our Harry would probably be just a little younger than him. And even now, when I hear these accusations, my inclination is to jump to his defense and protect him." Lily scratched her head. "I was hoping it was just some bad shrimp I ate, but… I don't know."

Remus had been squeezing his daughter's leg under the table to keep her from saying anything she shouldn't.

"That's it," James decided turning to his wife. "We're going to get you completely checked out for compulsion curses, memory charms, the whole works."

"I'm fine," Lily said, scowling at her husband.

"You said you felt like you had a monster in your chest," James argued. "Let's just make sure you in fact don't."

Albus smiled and interrupted. "Nevertheless, it is imperative that we contact the Lord Blacks as soon as possible. I was thinking perhaps the Lupins and Potters could talk to them, or ideally arrange a meeting with myself."

Tonks shrugged indifferently, looking to her adoptive father for an answer. Remus explained, "Tonks was brought back into the Black family as soon as Sirius was able to, and I, by extension, have been granted the same courtesy. But even we've been blocked access."

"Floo's closed and apparition's warded," Tonks answered. "And we used to be able to apparate right in. So I'm guessing they intentionally blocked us as a favor."

"Cutting you off and refusing you permission is doing you a favor?" Sturgis asked.

Tonks nodded. "I'm already balancing my responsibilities and loyalties between the Order and the Ministry. Both of which have asked me to exploit my family connection. I can tell you the same thing I told Madame Bones: the connection does me no good in this instance."

"Have you tried simply knocking on the front door?" James asked, not wanting this small mission to fall in his lap.

Tonks shrugged. "Back door is the one I use because of that stupid umbrella stand. And right now the door's got a sign that says 'Do Not Disturb (except in emergencies).' I'm inclined to trust my Lords on this one."

James saw people looking his way and said, "I only went by their family manor once because I was hoping to question Lord Black unofficially. They were… busier than I expected."

"Yes, yes," Albus grinned. "We all saw the pictures of Madame Bones. But if we cannot open a line of communication, then we may have to ask you to 'disturb' them, Miss Lupin."

"Why don't you just send an owl?" James Jr. suggested.

"I'm sure they've warded owl post if they've blocked even keyed in apparition," James condescendingly explained to his son.

James. Jr. shrugged. "Firefly delivered my letter this morning."

"You're writing to them?" James asked his son in disbelief.

James. Jr. nodded. "This was before I heard about the Death Eater, so Harry's probably busy."

"You shouldn't be writing to strangers," James scolded.

"Uncle PJ said he doubted they'd mind," James Jr. explained. "We talked with them and Tonks for half a day. That's not exactly a stranger."

Albus inquired, "Do you mind sharing your Uncle Peter's opinion of them?"

James Jr. shook his head. "He said the Lord Blacks are the type of allies who will likely drive you to horrible ruin or great fortune. But either way, you'll probably have a bit too much fun getting there."

"Just about hit the nail on the head with that assessment," Tonks mumbled.

Albus found himself concurring as well. "I shall send them a missive with Fawkes. But if they are not responsive, I wonder if you might wish to invite them to dinner at Godric's Hollow with your Uncle and the Lupins?"

James was going to dismiss the idea outright but Lily answered before he had a chance. "I think I'd like that whether they reply to you or not."

James groaned and planned to assign himself some overtime.

Sturgis looked at her like she was mad. "Death Eater? Parselmouth? Stabbing? Do these things mean nothing to you?"

Albus jumped in and explained, "I may not know the Lord Blacks well enough to judge the strength of their convictions, but I trust Remus and I trust Tonks. And their willingness to be protective of the Lord Blacks speaks highly of the trust they have in them."

Remus smiled at Albus and nodded at everyone looking his way.

"Now," Albus continued. "I think perhaps we've spent enough time talking about the Lord Blacks. Let's move on to other people of interest. James, why don't you tell us about these Death Eater Bandits?"

Remus had to pat his daughter on the back as she had started choking.

Sirius double-checked and saw Bellatrix was still napping in the sealed and warded guest bedroom. Kreacher had been instructed to relay all communication through Harry and him and to keep them apprised of her state.

He walked down to the muggle room and saw Harry was reading the letter that had arrived while they were turning a spare bedroom into a temporary gilded cage.

"Who's it from?" Sirius asked, plopping down next to Harry.

"Jimmy," Harry answered. He repeated it proudly, "My little brother Jimmy. Writing the older brother he doesn't even know he has for advice."

Sirius groaned. "Please tell me you're not turning into one of them."

"I can't help it," Harry admitted gleefully. "I like the idea of having my very own little brother."

"This is how it always starts," Sirius grumbled to himself.

"And I feel like it's my duty as his big brother to… you know…"

"Love and protect him," Sirius spat out the words distastefully.

"What?" Harry looked at his godfather in confusion. "No. Fuck that. He's got family for that. I'm his big brother. I'm supposed to corrupt him."

Sirius looked at Harry hopefully.

"Send him some booze and porn, like a good big brother does." Harry grinned deviously. "Besides, how do you think James would feel about that?"

Sirius was so proud of Harry at that moment he almost considered admitting it out loud. Luckily he was saved from the ethical dilemma of whether to show emotion or not by an ear-splitting scream from the guest bedroom.

They both leapt to their feet and ran down the hall. They burst into the room and saw Kreacher fretting over Bellatrix Black who was gritting her teeth and convulsing in obvious pain.

"It's… him," Bellatrix whispered when she saw Harry walk into view.

"Crap," Harry said casting a stunner on her immediately.

Bellatrix's violent shudders ceased instantly as she succumbed to unconsciousness.

"This could be a problem," Harry said looking up at Sirius.

"Harry," Sirius said pointing towards Bellatrix again.

Harry looked down and saw her body was still wracked with random spasms, despite her stunned state. "Bugger. Kreacher, go get several pain-relieving potions."

"Voldemort's torturing her through the mark?" Sirius clarified.

Harry nodded. "I was afraid of this. And because it's tied into her soul, even stunning won't help her that much."

Kreacher returned with a half dozen sealed cups of potion. Harry woke Bellatrix and handed her one. "Drink this."

Bellatrix started to reach for the potion but her arm was clearly not stable enough to hold the cup, so she helplessly opened her mouth.

Harry briefly wondered where this situation fell on the weird-o-meter in his life, as he slowly poured the potion into Bellatrix's mouth. It took only ten seconds before her body had stopped shivering and she relaxed back into the bed.

"Thanks," she said quietly.

"No problem," Harry said incanting another stunning charm and sending her right back into unconsciousness.

Harry saw Sirius was watching Bellatrix with an unreadable expression on his face. "We're going to have to do something about this."

Sirius looked at Harry. "What can we do?"

Harry stopped to try and think of any possible solutions. With a burst of inspiration, he rolled up her sleeve to examine the Dark Mark. The tail of the snake was visible but the head was nowhere to be seen.

"Hey," Harry hissed out in parseltongue as he leant down to her arm. "Wake up. You there?"

Harry looked up and saw Sirius was watching him before turning back towards the Dark Mark. "I can see your tail. I know you're there."

"Is he playing hide the snake head?" Sirius helpfully asked. "There was this girl I used to-OWW!" Sirius grabbed his eye. "Dammit Harry."

"I know you can hear me," Harry hissed. "I just wanted to ask you a question."

A few inches below the Dark Mark in a patch of unblemished skin, the image of the snake's head came bursting to the surface. "You are not Master. Master commands." It slithered right back up into the skull and once again only the tail was visible as its head disappeared hidden under the surface.

Harry stood back up. "Crap. He's going to be no help."

"I don't know that much about soul magic," Sirius said with a shrug. "But I know enough that breaking the spell would probably kill her."

"Not necessarily," Harry retorted as he settled into a chair near Bellatrix's bed. He deflated admitting, "But it'd probably destroy her soul… so yeah." Harry sighed as Sirius took the other chair. "Any ideas?"

Sirius shrugged. "You think we could manipulate the spell without breaking it?"

"It might be possible," Harry considered. "But we're probably working on a deadline of the pain driving her crazy. Not to mention I don't think anyone has ever been able to do anything with the mark."

"Healers probably won't be any help, will they?"

Harry shook his head. "Not unless they know more about the Dark Mark than I do, which I'm kinda doubting."

Sirius sat back in thought just observing Bellatrix as he and Harry descended into silence. "Well, historically a rabid stray bitch gets put down, but I don't really want to do that."

"I know," Harry grumbled. "She's hot."

"It's not that," Sirius explained. "It's just this Bellatrix is so different. She's meek. Even as a crazy psychotic murdering bitch she had a zest for life, or evil I suppose. Putting this one down wouldn't be the same as my real bitch of a cousin."

Harry found himself agreeing with Sirius. He couldn't see much of the Bellatrix he knew in this woman either.

Sirius waited a beat before adding, "And she's not exactly hard on the eyes either."

Harry shook his head as they lapsed into another thoughtful silence. After several minutes of quiet contemplation, Harry began to summarize, "Voldemort can torture her indefinitely. Trying to prevent the pain still damages her soul and will eventually drive her crazy. Separating the spell from her would kill her or leave her soulless. But that hardly matters because breaking the spell or manipulating it may very well be impossible."

"Impossible," Sirius repeated. "That sounds like your forte."

Harry rolled his eyes. "You can't honestly expect a solution to magically appear."

Kismet as always heeded the call and in a burst of flame, Fawkes appeared floating gently in front of Sirius. The phoenix warbled a greeting and landed on the edge of the dresser.

Harry glanced at the magical bird before looking up and saying, "You can't honestly expect a Philosopher's Stone to magically appear." He took a couple seconds thinking positive thoughts while Fawkes was tilting his head inspecting him. "Damn."

"It was a good try," Sirius admitted. He walked over towards the phoenix and showed his empty hand. "Hey Fawkes."

Fawkes nodded in greeting, having met Sirius before. He curled his head under his wing and produced a sealed envelope.

"Eurgh," Harry commented. "As hot as phoenixes run at, you know that's a moist armpit."

Sirius took the envelope from Fawkes' beak and held it up to his nose to smell. He quickly whipped the letter away and jerked his head back. "Good god. It smells like moldy old parchment." Sirius took another look at the envelope. "Oh right." Sirius opened the letter and began to read.

Harry walked over to Fawkes and let the bird smell his hand, before he began to scratch Fawkes on the back of his head. "How you doing, Fawkes," Harry said. "Still like being rubbed back here?"

Fawkes let loose a rumbling purr of approval.

"You think you could do us a favor?" Harry asked hopefully. He stopped scratching when Fawkes turned to look at him.

Harry pointed. "Bellatrix is being tortured by Voldemort. You think maybe shedding a tear or two might help? Or some other ancient phoenix pain-relieving secret?"

Fawkes' eyes widened and he just tilted his head at Harry in disbelief.

"I know. I'm surprised I'm asking too," Harry said. "But phoenixes are some of the best healers in the magical world and I don't really want her agony. Well, not right now at least."

Fawkes hopped up into the air and beat his wings as he began to circle the small bedroom. He burst into a brilliant phoenix song that left Harry and Sirius both tingling happily.

Harry glanced over and saw Bellatrix's body was shivering in discomfort from the effects of the phoenix song. Fawkes stopped his magical tune and landed right back on the edge of Harry's chair as Bellatrix's body relaxed.

"Oh yeah," Harry said slowly in a moment of dawning realization. "Death Eater."

Fawkes let out a laughing murmur of agreement.

"So what's Albus got to say?" Harry asked noticing Sirius was done with the letter.

"Here," Sirius said handing him the letter. "You read it."

Harry took the letter and saw it was short but as carefully worded as everything from Albus. Harry asked aloud, "He's not exactly subtle here, is he?"

"I think he's trying to win us over with honesty." Sirius scoffed with a shake of his head, "Like that'll work."

Harry looked over at Fawkes. "You know we can't do this. Does he honestly expect us to sell out a Black who just swore allegiance to the family?"

Fawkes looked almost embarrassed under Harry's scrutiny.

"You didn't expect us to, did you Fawkes?"

Fawkes shook his head in clear response.

"A letter has arrived, Masters," Kreacher announced as he walked in the room carrying a Ministry owl.

"Aren't we just the popular kids today," Sirius commented taking the letter as the owl flew away having delivered its note. "It's from Amy." Sirius read the contents of the letter and added, "Correction. It's from the Director of the Department of Magical Law Enforcement."

Harry glanced at Fawkes. "We may have a response for you after all."

"The Wizengamot is going to have an unofficial but required bit of questioning for Bellatrix Black Friday afternoon at 1 PM. If she hasn't shown up by 2 PM, they have a warrant to search for her in Grimmauld Place, including the destruction of any wards in the way."

Harry raised a curious eyebrow at Fawkes and turned towards Sirius. "We get two days notice to properly hide her away out of the country?"

"Is that what we're going to do?" Sirius asked.

"I doubt it," Harry said while summoning a piece of parchment and a pen. He began to write a response for Albus.

Sirius walked over and saw the letter addressed to the Headmaster. "What are you telling him?"

"I am thanking him for his concern," Harry explained while writing. "But informing him that there is an immediate health risk we must address first. After all, it's not like the Dark Lord will quietly accept one leaving his service. And I'm telling him we look forward to resolving the issue at the Wizengamot on Friday."

"You think he might be able to help us?"

Harry was just finishing the letter and looked up at Sirius and Fawkes. "I think we'd be betraying a Black no matter how well-intentioned his help might be."

"Even if we don't come up with anything," Sirius asked doubtfully. "You think she'd rather constant agony than the annoyance of guilt trips, twinkling eyes, and offers of sweets?"

Fawkes was clearly amused to be sitting in on this.

Harry handed the note to Sirius to look over. "I'm still not sure why she came to us, but you know she had to have considered going to Albus for help. She chose us for whatever reason. And I'm guessing it was partially because we wouldn't immediately run to the high and mighty Albus Dumbledore."

Sirius handed the note back having nothing to add. "I know you've had some problems with him in the past-"

"Hang on," Harry stopped him and handed the note to Fawkes. "There's a spy for Dumbledore in our midst."

Fawkes took the note from Harry, and flicked his wing under his chin in a gesture that was clearly a phoenix insult. He warbled a goodbye that sounded less than friendly and flashed away. After the flames disappeared, the Lord Blacks were alone once more to watch Bellatrix suffer silently.

Harry hadn't ever seen Fawkes do that before. "I think he just gave me the equivalent of flipping the bird."

"As a bird, he might take offense to that," Sirius said. "But what I was saying is that when it comes to answers, Dumbledore is one of the people usually worth asking."

"Yeah, I know," Harry said. "But you're basing that off of your impressions of a different man. And he sees Bella as an asset to be utilized. We see her as family."

"I don't usually like my family," Sirius pointed out.

"Me neither," Harry agreed recalling his own experiences. "But she's still family. And for what it's worth, I'm doubtful he could do anything for her that we haven't."

The two of them went back to their chairs and resumed watching over the woman causing them so much trouble.

Harry was re-reading the letter Amy had sent in an official capacity. He was still surprised at the differences in the way the rules applied to the so-called noble pureblood leaders. Harry's musings were interrupted as Sirius smacked himself in the forehead.

"Of course," Sirius exclaimed. "I know why she came to us. It's because of who we are, the Lords Black."

"Yeah," Harry said. "I got that much."

"No, no," Sirius argued. "I mean she's a pureblood following tradition. My mum used to be Head of the Family, but she was never the Lord. That's why Bellatrix could freely associate herself with another Lord, including pledge herself into his service."

"Voldemort's not even a real Lord though," Harry said.

"Tell him that," Sirius chuckled. "But the point is, now that the Black family has a Lord, or two in this case, we're the only ones who could rightfully reclaim her from her previous pledge. She's never been expelled from the family so she's had to answer to both him and us, until we forced her to deny him."

"So even though she has abandoned him," Harry continued. "When she was loyal, he cast the mark binding her soul to an extent."

"Not a very trusting guy, is he?"

"Nope," Harry agreed. "Not really."

"She's ours," Sirius said fully comprehending the situation. "She was born into the family and raised by it. Our claim and her free will supersede any tenuous claim he could make."

"You're acting like she's a hunk of property," Harry said thinking they were doing the exact thing he was criticizing Dumbledore for.

"Vassal, servant, slave, whatever you want to call it," Sirius said. "We're Lords of a family. And that which is part of the family, belongs to the family, and therefore us, as keepers."

"So the root of the problem is that neither she nor us has ever owned the piece of magic on her arm," Harry exclaimed in frustration. "I think we're back to the point where asking nicely isn't going to help us any."

"In matters of dispute," Sirius recounted. "Lords of equal stature depend on the magic to decide who is right."

Harry grimaced. "Any chance there's a simple spell that does that?"

Sirius shook his head. "The magic cedes to the victor of a duel."

Harry had seen the answer coming but hoped that it wasn't the case. "Peachy. So we just need to defeat Voldemort in a duel." He sighed tiredly not even looking towards Sirius.

"It'd be a Lords' duel," Sirius cheered way too happily. "House of Black versus House of Voldemort. But two against one because of our status."

"This isn't a solution," Harry said shaking his head. "Besides getting killed or getting our asses kicked, it won't change the fact that he's not a real Lord."

"We can take him," Sirius said with more confidence than he felt. "From the sound of it this one's not even as strong as our old one."

Harry groaned as an idea hit him. "Ahh crud."

"There it is," Sirius grinned victoriously. "What do you got?"

"I just realized it doesn't matter that he's not a recognized Lord. And in fact it actually gives him more reason to duel us," Harry ruefully said.

"Perfect," Sirius agreed. "How's that?"

"The Council of Lords," Harry explained. "When I was reading up on the history of the Wizengamot, the Council of Lords was the ruling body before the establishment of the Ministry. With the Ministry's inception, they became the legislative and judicial branch and were then officially called the Wizengamot."

"Am I getting an explanation or a history lesson?"

"The point is the old rules of the Council still apply. And if a Lord chooses to meet a lesser family head in a Lords' duel, a victory by the lesser would grant him the official title of Lord."

"So he'd really be a Lord if he defeats us?" Sirius clarified.

"If we make it a Lords' duel, yeah," Harry nodded. "And technically it'd put a Voldemort seat on the Wizengamot too as a noble line."

"Oh that's priceless!" Sirius laughed. "We have got to do this. Even if we lose, we're fucking over the Wizengamot."

"If we lose, we're probably going to be dead, you realize."

Sirius shrugged. "I wanna go out with a bang."

Harry sighed. "I can't believe I'm actually considering this, but let's look at it logically…"

Sirius felt his adrenaline racing in ways that good old-fashioned robbery had never incited. He was cataloging every aspect of their environment worth noting.

They were in the middle of Badgin Alley, a small magical district in Wales.

Four Death Eaters were unconscious with bruises, lying in a pile off to their right. The fifth Death Eater they'd sent off with instructions to fetch his Master as the Lord Blacks had some urgent business with him.

The sixth and final Death Eater of the failed raid was writhing under the boot of Harry, who was chatting excitedly with the man's Dark Mark.

Just last night, Sirius had managed to talk Harry into this hodge-podge of a plan. In between painkilling potions, they'd uncovered this attack Bellatrix wasn't supposed to know about but did.

Harry had been exercising his magic all day. He drilled into Sirius' head the fact that they needed to work together to have any chance to win this. Even Sirius had agreed that dueling Dark Lords without a plan was a bad idea.

The unconscious Death Eaters were warded off from the growing crowd beginning to gather in Badgin Alley. Sirius just hoped Voldemort would show up before the aurors did.

Half a dozen pops sounded and six more masked Death Eaters appeared. "Showtime," Sirius whispered towards Harry as they got up to approach them.

"Crucio!" the man in front called out aiming straight for Sirius.

A rock off to the side flew up and blocked the curse, while Harry and Sirius didn't even blink continuing to walk towards the new arrivals.

"We don't have time to deal with servants," Sirius bellowed. "Where is your Lord?"

A Killing Curse was cast and yet another rock flew up to intercept the spell. Harry's invisible magical arms leapt into action, yanking the caster forward. The man's legs both snapped at impossible angles breaking them loudly. "That spell was intended to kill me. You know by law, I can torture you for days. And in ways that would make you long for your Lord's tender mercies."

Harry ripped the man's sleeve off with only a thought and immediately began talking to his Dark Mark. "Seeing as how your Master isn't here, do you think you could get the marks on these other people to jolt?"

The Dark Marks responded and the other Death Eaters all jumped, disturbing their initial shock at discovering a parselmouth.

"The Lords Black," a whisper carried down the Alley from the other direction.

"Lord Voldemort," Sirius called out loudly as he and Harry turned their backs to the remaining Death Eaters.

Another Killing Curse was sent at Harry's back and the downed Death Eater with broken legs jerked up into the path of the deadly spell. Harry let him fall to the ground dead, turning his attention back towards the darkness of the Alley in front of him.

"Or rather Voldemort, since calling oneself Lord does not make it so," Harry corrected Sirius. He peered through the darkness and saw the glowing form of an extremely powerful wizard. "I wonder Tom, if there had been a G in your name, would you have called yourself a God?"

"You are even more foolish than I'd been led to believe," Voldemort hissed out making his presence known as he emerged from the shadows.

Another curse was sent towards Harry's back and another downed Death Eater was thrust into the path of it.

"Your servants are costing you servants," Harry commented. "You might want to tighten their leashes."

"Why is it you two traitors are so eager to die tonight?" Voldemort asked looking around for signs of a trap.

"Bellatrix Black was a Black long before she made the mistake of pledging herself to a false Lord. You knew the magic would never see you as a proper Lord, so you ensured your slaves' loyalty with a rather ingenious piece of soul magic hidden behind a serpent tattoo."

"I don't have time for this," Voldemort said calmly. "I had hoped to see you by my side-"

Sirius interrupted him and firmly intoned, "As her Lords, we demand control of the Mark on her soul."

"You come to me with demands," Voldemort snapped. He clenched a fist as his magic came bubbling to the surface. "I am the Dark Lord Voldemort! And I will teach you to fear me before I squeeze the last breath from your frail broken bodies."

Harry shook his head at Voldemort's predictability. "You know your wizarding history, Tom." Harry held out his wand in front of him and forced his voice to carry to all ends of the Alley. "The House of Black is challenging the House of Voldemort to a Lords' duel for control of the mark on Bellatrix Black's soul."

Thick ancient magic began swirling in the air awaiting the response from the Dark Lord. The crowds were watching in silence and even the Death Eaters still alert were transfixed by the scene before them.

"Draw your wand," Sirius ordered, shifting into a dueling position directly in front of Harry. "Or leave like a coward."

"Are we going to have to chase you?" Harry lackadaisically mocked, while ignoring the nausea in the back of his throat. "Or would you like to earn your self-proclaimed title of Lord?"

The answer was given without any sign or warning. A sickly pale yellow curse exploded from the wand of the Dark Lord Voldemort. The magic surrounding them all began to hum in eager anticipation of a victor.

Sirius' eyes widened at the sheer power of the spell heading towards him. He swallowed rather loudly wondering just how this had seemed like a good idea.

Harry felt the moment the challenge was accepted and gulped almost as loudly as Sirius. He placed his hand on his godfather's shoulder, preparing to move them both. "Here we go. Try not to die."

Chapter 13

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

"Gah!" Sirius shrieked as Harry apparated them both five feet to the side. The ground where they had been standing dried and crackled instantly after the curse hit.

Sirius looked at Harry as the younger man thrust his hand out, a solid shield appearing in place. A loud clang and crack made Sirius flinch as Harry yanked them to the ground. The solid shield held, but just barely. "What do you mean try not to die?"

"Less talk," Harry said gritting his teeth. Another super-charged purple spell slammed into the shield Harry was holding, shattering it to dust. "More cursing."

Harry grabbed Sirius' shoulder again and apparated them out of the way of a searing jet of blue fire.

"Actually," Harry said turning Sirius around to face the Dark Lord. "You need to learn something. Put up a shield."

Sirius saw three cannon shots of a semi-dark bludgeoning curse barreling down on them. He cast a humming magical shield, reinforced it, and hunched down to make a smaller target.

Harry prepared himself and heard Sirius' shield tinkle as it broke like the thinnest sheet of glass. The spiraling bludgeoning curse hit dead center in the solar plexus of the crouching Sirius Black.

The dragon hide armor was put to the test, but absorbed the lion's share of the spell. The force was still enough to send Sirius careening backwards into Harry, and both of them careening backwards sliding to a stop in a small wooded area on the opposite side of the alley.

"Fuck me," Sirius swore as a dark green barely visible hex zipped through the air towards the two of them.

A nearby rotted log jerked diagonally, blocking the curse but spraying the two Lord Blacks with wet wood.

Two metal spears shot through the air at both Harry and Sirius before they could even get to their feet. Two heavy stones blocked the spikes' path, sending one veering off towards the tops of the trees, while the other flipped forward and embedded itself into the ground in front of them.

"I thought you called yourselves Lords," Voldemort taunted. "Can you not-" He stopped suddenly and apparated away as one of his conjured spears zoomed through the place he had been standing. It made a loud echoing THUNK as the spear embedded half a meter into a wooden post.

"Come on, Sirius," Harry said as a half dozen pieces of debris began orbiting protectively around them. "I got the defense, you get the offense. Heavy and fast curses."

Sirius was a bit twitchy beginning to finally comprehend what they'd signed up for but centered himself and put on his game face. "We got this." He began twirling his wand, gathering energy as the tip started to glow. His wand began to whistle quietly in eager anticipation.

The two of them walked calmly from the small copse of trees, while a half dozen rocks and logs circled them dangerously.

Voldemort was standing there, holding his wand lazily at the side, squinting at the two Lord Blacks and the various solid objects moving randomly around them. "What magic is this?"

Sirius said nothing as he whipped his wand underhand and sent the nonverbal spell that had been building up arcing through the air towards Voldemort. It weaved left and right bobbing slowly before accelerating suddenly on a straight path to the Dark Lord.

The solid shield Voldemort pushed into existence was a step too late and barely deflected the curse as it glanced off his shoulder. The Dark Lord stumbled but did not fall, only exhaling loudly when his right shoulder purpled yet never tore.

Harry knew it was coming and made no effort to block the spell fired behind him as a red jet of light flew right past his ear and nowhere near Sirius.

"Dammit," Harry swore softly at the miss.

Sirius was about to cast another spell when Harry jerked him down and the neon green of a Killing Curse sailed right over them both, slamming into the trigger-happy Death Eater behind them.

Sirius grunted as he hit the ground. "I thought you'd block-"

"That one wasn't aimed at us," Harry explained while keeping them covered as they rose.

"Could've fooled me," Sirius muttered.

"No one touches them until I'm done," Voldemort shouted, staring down the Death Eaters assembled behind Harry and Sirius. "If any of you cost me this duel, it will be on your head."

"If he's off aim even a centimeter," Harry said urging Sirius to stay focused. "There's a reason."

Sirius shot off three rapid fire spells that the Dark Lord deflected with ease. "Told you it wouldn't work."

"Meh," Harry grunted knowing that if the servants of one of the Lords interfered, then that House forfeited the duel. "It could've happened if their aim wasn't so horrid."

Another two spells came rocketing from Voldemort's wand and Harry got two planks into their paths. They exploded in fire, showering the Lord Blacks with burning cinders. The dragon hide cloaks just sloughed off the wreckage while the Dark Lord cast a complicated oculamagi spell over his eyes making them glow a bright red.

Sirius let loose a sickly decaying curse at the ground the Dark Lord was standing on.

Voldemort apparated straight backwards, returning fire with a hail of slicing curses, and then pausing to watch them hit.

Harry got rocks in the way of the curses headed towards them, letting the ones that were going to miss, fly harmlessly through the air around him.

With a diagonal slash, Sirius shot off two bone-breakers at the Dark Lord's right shoulder and left knee.

Voldemort slid a half step to the side and paid no attention to the two spells just missing his shoulder and flying between his legs. Another flurry of darker slicing curses designed to cleave through magical shields came this time speckled in white.

The largest remaining pieces of debris again protected Harry and Sirius while the other slicing curses flew past. Two of them connected with Harry's invisible magical arms, severing the magic cleanly at the point of contact.

Harry fell to a knee from the backlash of his own oversaturated magic. "Fuck. He figured that out pretty damn quick." The sudden magical shift was more short intense pain than slow ache and it left Harry winded.

Sirius abandoned the longer incantation he'd started and just began focusing rapid fire pellet shots at the Dark Lord. Each whip of his wand let out a crack of angry magic and zipped off a small, icy projectile.

Voldemort called up another solid shield that they hit with a ping, barely denting the surface. He hissed in annoyance as one of Sirius' shots connected with his lower leg.

"Stay with me, Harry," Sirius called, running out of juice from his relentless pellet spree.

"Enough!" Voldemort boomed loudly, slamming his fist into the ground. A deep rumbling shockwave of force knocked Sirius off his feet and Harry back down as he had begun to rise.

"You are not without your talents," Voldemort admitted in what he felt was a compliment. "Join me. You are powerful wizards. I will make you stronger."

Sirius snapped out a single pellet from his wand in response.

Voldemort held his hand up and let the nuisance spell smash into his palm. It stung and broke the surface of his pale skin, but was not deep.

Harry sensed an opportunity to catch his breath and quickly downed a pepper-up potion, while floating a dose to Sirius.

The three duelers all were watching each other carefully, taking a few moments to observe their opponents and plot out their next actions.

Voldemort was staring at Harry, focusing his red glowing spelled eyes on the younger Lord Black. He noticed a faint echo of magic and asked, "Where did you get that scar?"

Even though Harry highly doubted it would be a problem, he was still greatly relieved to feel no twinge of life or activity in his curse scar, no matter his proximity to this Dark Lord. "Just some old over-confident bastard," Harry answered with a smirk. He immediately sensed the Dark Lord's silent attempt at Legilimency and ejected the probe with excessive force.

"Watch your mind and your eye contact," Harry warned to Sirius.

Voldemort hissed and flinched from the abrupt violent mental push. He hoped dividing his Legilimency probe between the Lord Blacks would make them subtle enough to not be noticed. He encountered no Occlumency shields at all and caught a single snippet from each of them before being thrown out and losing his connection.

He took a closer look around at the crowds gathering and continued to internally stockpile spells. He saw his Death Eaters warily assessing the contingent of aurors that had just arrived at the tavern down the alley. "Go. Take them with you."

The Death Eaters able to move quickly grabbed their unconscious mates, leaving the three dead ones behind. They apparated away before the aurors could stop them.

"So this was your grand plan?" Voldemort said, airily waving his hand at all the destruction they had caused. "Tempt me with a Lords' duel, hope to last long enough for the aurors to arrive, and then what? Concede while they foolishly attempt to trap me? They are not strong enough and the Lords' duel prevents their interference. What could you honestly hope to accomplish with this futile exercise?"

"We don't give a shit about the aurors," Sirius answered as the steam from a pepper-up whistled out his ears. "This is merely a family matter for us."

"If it is death you seek," Voldemort announced, watching the aurors fail in their attempts to erect wards over the Lords and the area between them. "Then death I shall give you."

The Dark Lord voiced no spell and made no motion other than to clench his fist tightly in front of him. A kaleidoscope of magic erupted from his hand, expanding into a giant wave, each color a different spell, a different curse, and a different way to hurt or kill.

Harry grabbed onto Sirius' shoulder and tried to apparate away. He slammed into an anti-apparition jinx he'd yet to notice and was left staggering from the attempt.

Every piece of debris Harry could reach was frantically thrown at the myriad of violent spells contained in a single rainbow wave of magic. The dirt on the ground was splashed up to try to disrupt curses when rocks couldn't be found. But the efforts were futile. Half a dozen spells ripped through both Sirius and Harry's bodies lifting them off their feet and carrying them ten meters through the air. The most damage was done to the exposed areas of skin while the dragon hide was pushed to its limits before cracking and shredding.

Harry was knocked senseless and he moaned in protest wondering what had happened. He let out a labored breath as the memories came back to him. He saw the green of a Killing Curse headed for him and his magical arms quickly propelled him into the air just avoiding the spell that smacked into the ground below him. He landed on his feet only to see the Dark Lord had already cast another Killing Curse at his other opponent.

Harry heard Sirius begin to moan in pain just before he dove right on top of his godfather. Using his momentum to roll them both away from the deadly spell, Harry earned even louder cries from Sirius as both of their thrashed bodies were jostled.

Harry's magic reacted instinctively grabbing a bunch of debris to protect them. No longer was it circling around them exposing his magical arms to harm. Instead the debris was hovering right in front of them, shielding them from the hail of curses that the Dark Lord sent their way.

Sirius was levitated off the ground and Harry slung the older man's arm over his shoulder, holding the weakened man up. They were both on their feet now, and Harry's shields were diverting or blocking most of the Dark Lord's spells. The ones that couldn't be blocked, Harry was able to run or dodge away from successfully. Focusing only on the defensive, Harry was whispering at Sirius to wake up, knowing that Voldemort could hear him.

The Dark Lord was two thirds of the way into summoning a pool of hellfire, when a sudden pop alerted him to the fact that his anti-apparition jinx had been countered without his notice.

Through the shield of debris, he could see only one Lord Black.

Sirius had been dazed from Voldemort's rekindled onslaught but quickly regained control of his faculties. Harry had been pinching him and Sirius heard the stilted way Harry was whispering. Sirius continued to play possum while gently breaking down the Dark Lord's anti-apparition jinx. When he felt it break he didn't even bother to look up. He simply apparated directly to the Dark Lord's right. Not wanting to waste a moment with wand waving or a voiced spell, Sirius used two open hands to slam Voldemort's bruised and purpled shoulder with wandless concussion charms.

Voldemort hadn't even seen the attack coming before he was blasted sideways through the glass window of a china shop's teacup display. His shoulder that had taken the brunt of the blow had split open and was coating his entire arm in blood.

Harry apparated right behind Sirius and gathered fresh pieces of rock, floating in formation waiting to block the next spell headed their way.

"That," Voldemort hissed dangerously while stepping out from the broken storefront, "was a mistake."

Sirius fired off a pair of dark burning curses that just fizzled out in the air surrounding the furious Dark Lord.

Voldemort huffed in pain as he pressed his hand over his bleeding shoulder. The blood flowing down his arm darkened until it was black and ceased to flow. Voldemort stared down at the two Lord Blacks without an ounce of fear. "It won't happen again."

An orange spell came shooting out Voldemort's open palm while he snapped his wand igniting a long fiery whip. The largest log exploded when the orange spell connected and the whip snaked through the air destroying two more of the rocks and sending the shards raining down on Harry and Sirius.

Harry cast a magical shield just in time, while Sirius sent off a bludgeoning and a spearing curse with another happy whistle from his wand.

Voldemort was inching closer and working his magical whip through every piece of protection Harry could grab. The two spells from Sirius smacked into the Dark Lord with a flash of light, but didn't even slow his forward progress for a moment.

The Dark Lord snapped his wand with a flourish releasing his hold on the magical whip that sliced through the air and wrapped around both Lord Blacks.

It took Harry more effort than he would have liked to dispel the fire binding that had singed both himself and Sirius. All the while the Dark Lord just kept laying on spell after spell, randomly switching his targets from Harry to Sirius and back again.

Voldemort saw this as a challenge in more ways the one. He wasn't putting everything he had into each spell, instead focusing on quantity. But he wanted to prove to all watching how futile opposing him was. He was actively destroying each and every attempt at a physical shield, faster than Harry could thrust them in the way of the spells. For every spell he bothered to verbalize, two more silent ones were cast without wasting a breath. More than two spells a second for fifteen seconds, and Voldemort was connecting cleanly every fourth or fifth spell.

Harry was doing all he could to defend, but the Dark Lord was just too quick for him to keep up.

Sirius hadn't been able to cast anything significant in response as he was forced to defend from the numerous spells that Harry couldn't. Harry had warned Sirius that even in this world, he expected the Dark Lord to be faster and stronger than either of them. But they had numbers and a few other advantages in their favor, so Harry figured they had a good chance to win. Another stinging hex hit deep enough to draw blood on Sirius' wand arm, and he began to understand why Harry hadn't been as confident as he was.

Harry was summoning shards of the broken storefront, the trees, the rocks, everything within reach and furiously tried to keep up with the Dark Lord's pace. He knew he was missing a third of the spells now but he was focused on blocking the most dangerous ones. A metal blade was spinning through the air towards Sirius that Harry just barely deflected away in time. He hadn't even seen the dark slicing curses coming before two magical arms were severed and he fell to the ground, screaming unprepared for the painful backlash.

Sirius saw Harry fall and quickly changed tactics. He went on the offensive and fired a cutter followed immediately with a dark crucifixion curse aimed at Voldemort's heart.

Voldemort had been timing his spells, planning on Harry's reaction. He hefted a solid shield in his open hand and batted away both of Sirius' curses with barely a thought. He lunged towards Sirius and put his all into the next curse, snarling, "Crucio!"

Sirius wanted to dodge. He wanted to get something in the path of the curse. But the sheer velocity and hatred emanating off the spell didn't even give him time to blink before it slammed him, driving him into the ground. His entire body burned in pain on a level he'd not even imagined, completely unaware that he was screaming his throat raw.

Harry hadn't even caught his breath when he heard Voldemort cast a spell with more intensity than anything in the previous five minutes. He looked on in horror as his godfather's body began smoldering the moment the Unforgivable connected. The scream nearly tore at Harry's heart and he knew Sirius wouldn't last long under that curse. Harry's magical arms were moving as fast as he could think as a chunk of rock slammed into Voldemort's wand hand and two other arms pulled Sirius away and safely behind Harry.

The screaming had stopped and pitiful moans replaced it, but Harry knew Sirius was just about down for the count. Harry needed to give Voldemort something else to think about or he would have to sincerely consider cutting their losses and running. He wanted to protect Bellatrix, but he wasn't about to choose her over Sirius' life.

No longer seeking out debris for shields, Harry's arms were now looking for weapons. Every decent sized rock was picked up and thrown at the Dark Lord at high velocity. Half a dozen solid projectiles coming from different angles connected with Voldemort before he could get up a large enough physical shield.

Pressing the advantage, Harry began to cast spells designed to destroy and eat the shields Voldemort kept invoking. He'd heard a crack and suspected he'd broken the Dark Lord's leg, but wasn't about to let up.

Voldemort stepped back from the sudden attack, frustrated as he alternated between shielding himself from rocks, spears, and broken glass, while fending off the spells headed towards him. His anger and frustration reached its boiling point and he began cursing Harry right back, trading off the occasional rock or weaker spell, in exchange for sending a curse in return.

Harry was doing his best to stay on the offensive, but it wasn't long before Voldemort's superior skill made up the difference. A dark slicing curse aimed for one of Harry's magical arms was avoided, but it clipped him on the cheek, splitting the side of his face open. He saw Sirius was still down and just hoped the Dark Lord was tired enough to make a mistake.

In one smooth motion Harry slipped his ash wand back into its arm holster while drawing his old holly wand from the holster on the other arm.

Voldemort was done taking chances and saw Harry had lined up with Sirius. He flicked his wand sideways then straight shouting out, "Avada Kedavra!"

Feeling a bit mischievous Harry made no move from the path of the curse and shouted his own spell, "Densaugeo!"

Just as Harry had planned the two spells collided in midair and linked together, feeding back into their casters' wands.

The surprise showed on Voldemort's face as the near brother wands combined to create the Priori Incantatem effect.

A steady stream of magic was pouring from both duelists' wands connected in the middle of them and blossoming outward. A crackling iridescent dome of magic surrounded both men, cutting them off from the outside world, and pitting the pair against each other in a magical battle of wills.

Harry knew exactly what was happening and pressed his advantage, focusing all of his energy onto forcing the growing central ball of magic in the linked stream to flow back towards Voldemort's wand. Harry's magical arms folded themselves back inside so as to allow Harry to dedicate his complete focus to the task at hand.

Voldemort understood well enough that their wands had linked and they were now engaged in a challenge of willpower. The sheer volume of magic going into the wands and into the massive webbed cage surrounding them was blinding to the oculamagi spell on his eyes. He could feel the magic in the link slipping towards him, but all he could see was white where the spells had collided.

Voldemort didn't know why or how this phenomenon happened, but he could tell Harry knew it was coming. Voldemort concluded this because Harry had been cocky enough to cast a teeth growing curse, indicating that the spells may be revisited upon the caster. He knew he couldn't afford to lose this test of will, and tried to force the spell back towards Harry.

The Dark Lord knew it wasn't working but he couldn't see what was even happening. When he caught a glimpse of Harry, he saw no magical arms visible anywhere. Quickly deciding he shouldn't be wasting magic either, he focused his own hatred at breaking the oculamagi spell on his eyes. He wasn't going to waste a drop of his magic and he desperately needed to see clearer.

Harry was pushing the oversized magical glob back, almost far enough to reach the Dark Lord's wand, inciting the spell regurgitation when suddenly Voldemort shouted in triumph and his eyes stopped glowing red. Harry realized the Dark Lord had managed to cancel that spell while still holding off Harry's will. The pressure on Harry nearly doubled and the magical balls reversed direction heading closer towards Harry's wand tip.

Harry dug deep inside looking for that extra something and stopped the progress of the magical marker on the linked spells. They'd reached a tentative stalemate, as the bulging magical balls would drift forward a half meter, and then right back.

A haunting and eerie phoenix song began to echo around the golden dome. Some braver members of the crowd watching including aurors and members of the Order were standing right up next to the edge of the dome staring at it in wonder and unable to cross it.

Harry chanced a glance over his shoulder and saw through the dome that Sirius was no longer on his back, but had gotten up to his knees. The brief lapse in concentration cost Harry and the largest central glob moved even closer to Harry's side.

He gritted his teeth and halted its progress, pushing it back towards the Dark Lord as much as he could.

The wands in their hands were spewing excess sparks in all directions scalding both duelists. The sheer volume of magic being channeled was heating the wands up as they burned against the hands clenching them. Smoke rose from their sizzling hands but neither Harry nor Voldemort would ever contemplate conceding. They stared each other down, not allowing their concentration on the linked spells to drift.

Harry took the first step forward, shortening the stream of magic and pushing the beachball-sized glob back towards Voldemort a small amount.

Voldemort saw the ball grow bigger and get a little closer. He responded by taking a step towards Harry, gaining even more ground than he had lost.

It was by unspoken agreement that they both started to slowly step closer, shortening the linked stream and increasing the pressure on themselves.

The sizzling dome of magic protected them completely, flashing solid as the intensity of the battle increased. Harry could feel his strength leaving him, but refused to lose this battle of wills. Voldemort may be faster and more powerful, Harry thought, but his will was stronger. He would not lose this, no matter what Voldemort was on the other side.

Voldemort was focused exclusively on pushing the growing ball of magic back towards Harry.

"Oooh tingly!" Ginny Weasley exclaimed as she suddenly found herself floating in the middle of a massive magical glob. She heard a hiss of surprise and turned to see a frightened and sweaty Dark Lord in the midst of a very tense duel. She slowly turned her head to the other side and easily recognized Harry, despite the bloody mess covering his cheek and neck.

She looked back at Voldemort and Harry once more before announcing the decision she had made. "I'll come back later." Her ghostly form disappeared leaving only the bright glowing magic of their linked wands in her wake.

Voldemort was disturbed and shaken by the ghost's sudden appearance and his focus began to stray.

Harry saw his opportunity and sprinted five steps until he was barely three meters from the Dark Lord. The jiggling mass of magic ballooned and was now reaching its breaking point. The haunting sound of the phoenix cry was cresting at a fevered pitch.

Voldemort braced for the sudden jolt on his magic but held firm.

The strain of forcing himself to halve the distance between them was crushing Harry. He fell to one knee but kept his wand arm steady as his hands continued to burn.

Harry was trembling from the effort, sweat pouring off his forehead. He looked up at the Dark Lord as the magical glob began to teeter right up against Harry's wand tip. Harry saw the look of a victorious man standing proudly over a defeated foe on his knees.

Harry's stern look of concentration slipped for just a moment, allowing a ghost of a smile to cross his face. He saw the Dark Lord's pupils widen in fear as the dormant magic in Harry sprung to violent life. A mere two invisible magical arms exploded from Harry's body grabbing opposite sides of the Dark Lord's head and wrenching it with every ounce of magic Harry had.

The division of Harry's focus from the battle of wills was not without its costs. The Priori Incantatem effect flooded rapidly into Harry's wand. His bloody burnt hand was still clenched around the holly wand when the channel filled beyond its limit and exploded into splinters. A ghostly haze of spells erupted and began to dissipate almost immediately.

The muffled bloody pop of the wand's combustion was barely noticeable as the dome of magic surrounding the duelers softly fluttered off and the ear-splitting crack of the Dark Lord's neck snapping like a twig echoed throughout the entire alley.

Everyone watching the duel in rapt awe had gone silent as death when they could suddenly see the two other combatants clearly. Lord Harry Black was on his knees looking like he might collapse at any moment. And the Dark Lord Voldemort was floating a meter off the ground. His entire body hanging limply, his wand seared directly into the flesh of his palm. The Dark Lord's red eyes were swirling in restrained fury despite the unnatural way his chin was pointed up and over his shoulder. The people behind the Dark Lord could see shards of bloody bone sticking out at the base of his neck.

Harry took a deep breath and shuddered as his magical arms jerked again. Another series of snaps and crackles announced more torn muscles and broken bones as the Dark Lord Voldemort's head now faced completely in the wrong direction.

Sirius was the first person to react, jumping to his feet and charging into the fray to help his godson. He tried casting a Killing Curse but was unable to in his current state. He then aimed a decapitation curse at the unmoving body of the Dark Lord. It missed completely. Growling in frustration, he finally fired a blasting curse that connected with the Dark Lord's thigh, exploding with blood and sending the man flying from Harry's grip. Voldemort's body landed in a crumpled heap and Sirius aimed another blasting curse at him.

The aurors again failed to erect any apparition or portkey wards surrounding the duelists as the magic of the Lords' duel hadn't reached completion.

Harry had fallen to his hands and knees in sheer exhaustion, but he still wasn't surprised to hear the Dark Lord whisper a trigger word in parseltongue, "Return."

The portkey activated whisking away the paralyzed and broken body of the Dark Lord just before Sirius' second blasting curse could connect.

The ancient magic in the air called forth by the duel came to fruition and had identified a victor.

Harry and Sirius felt a rush of foreign magic, giving them a slight burst of energy.

Sirius limped over to Harry who was in the process of wrapping his bloody burnt wand hand with gauze. He pulled Harry up to his feet as they both felt the adrenaline leaving their systems.

Sirius saw a number of people headed towards them and knew they weren't ready to deal with questions right now. He wrapped an arm around Harry with a tired smile and said, "I don't know about you, but I could use a nap."

Harry chuckled a bit deliriously but held on, letting Sirius apparate them both back to Grimmauld Place.

The pair arrived in the foyer and crashed to the ground, unwilling to expend any energy on balance.

"Oww," Harry winced landing on his right hand, aggravating the holly splinters that were all that remained of his first wand.

"Sorry," Sirius said, panting from exhaustion. "Kreacher!"

With a pop, the house elf appeared and looked at both hurting Masters in worry. "What happened? Was it those filthy mudbloods?"

"Nope," Sirius answered rolling to his feet.

"I bet it was muggles," Kreacher said paying little attention as he rubbed his chin in thought. "I'll fetch the baby traps and the hammers."

"It wasn't muggles," Sirius said louder, noticing Harry was picking splinters out of his blistered and bloody palm. "This would be the handiwork of the Dark Lord."

"The Dark Lord?" Kreacher said, shaking his head in dismay. "But why would he…"

"He was torturing a Black," Sirius explained.

"Well the Black probably deserved it," Kreacher retorted. "The Dark Lord is the greatest, most powerfulest, wonderfulest wizard ever."

Harry blinked reliving a few scary Dobby flashbacks.

Sirius frowned, "When I have to choose between family and the Dark Lord-"

"You choose the Dark Lord," Kreacher answered for him.

"I wouldn't be a very good Lord Black if I did. Family comes first," Sirius corrected, "Dark Lord second."

"But he's the Dark Lord!"

"I think I might bump the Dark Lord a little lower than second," Harry commented wincing as he tried clenching a fist with his right hand. He ordered Kreacher, "Go get us a couple of pain relieving potions."

"If the Dark Lord wanted you hurt," Kreacher helplessly supplied. "Kreacher doesn't think you should be-"

"Oh for pete's sake, forget it," Harry said unwilling to deal with an immorally conflicted house elf when he was so close to passing out. "We need to check on Bellatrix anyway. We'll get them ourselves."

The quirky house elf was frowning and grumbling to himself, "Kreacher doesn't think Masters should be cheating out of punishments. Kreacher takes his punishments and Kreacher likes them."

Sirius helped Harry up and they slowly gimped their way up the stairs. "Do you need St. Mungo's?"

"Not this second," Harry said before noticing Sirius was moving as slowly as he was. "Do you?"

Sirius rubbed at his side. "I might have cracked a rib, but it's probably just bruised. I figure let's sleep on it and see how we feel in the morning."

Harry smiled blissfully at his godfather. "I was worried you were going to force me to a healer this instant like every other overbearing self-appointed parental influence in my life."

"You're a big boy, and I'm not that mature," Sirius admitted, clearly quite happy with both of those facts. They reached the top of the steps and stopped to take a breath. "Any guesses on what a baby trap is?"

"I'm quite sure we don't want to know," Harry said picturing a combination of a cage and bear trap.

The two Lord Blacks walked into the warded guest room and saw Bellatrix was still trembling in pain.

Harry and Sirius shared a worried look. Sirius grabbed a pair of pain relieving potions while Harry was staring at her Dark Mark. The skull was no longer present on her lower forearm. In its place was a shield with a sword and two stars flanked by a pair of greyhounds. Below the shield was a banner reading Toujours Pur. It was the Black family crest.

"Huh," Sirius said in slight surprise after drinking his potion and handing a dose to Harry.

Harry knocked the vial back and swallowed. "We might want to look into changing that motto."

Sirius nodded. "I say ditch the French and use pig Latin at the very least."

A sliver of movement behind the tattoo banner caught Harry's eye and he realized it was the tail of the snake.

"Hey," Harry hissed out in parseltongue.

The snake's head popped up from the unblemished skin just below the crest. "You are… you are Master?"

"Yeah," Harry replied. "Now I am. And so is he."

The snake head turned towards Sirius and looked back at Harry. "So he is."

"Stop hurting her," Harry hissed in command. "I may talk to you later, but for now, do nothing to her. Okay?"

"That doesn't sound like fun," the snake replied doubtfully. "But as you command."

Harry saw the snake disappear back under the surface of her skin only to reappear above the top of the crest. It coiled up and tucked its head in to take a nap, locking into place atop the shield.

Bellatrix's body relaxed and was resting peacefully for the first time in days.

Harry looked at his watch and saw it was after two in the morning. "Alright. We can get ten hours of sleep but we've got to take her to the Wizengamot at one."

"Let's put off St. Mungo's until after the hearing," Sirius suggested. "It'll make us look better and give us a good reason to keep things brief."

"Good plan," Harry said after a loud yawn. "I guess you do have your uses."

"Please," Sirius chided. "If you weren't holding me back, that whole mess with Voldemort would have been over so much quicker."

"You're right," Harry agreed. "It would have been over much quicker."

"That's not what I meant," Sirius protested.

"Oh before I forget," Harry grinned stopping in front of his bedroom door. "Did you notice the cute and dainty way your wand whistles?"

"That's not-"

"Good night, Sirius," Harry said walking into his bedroom and closing the door.

"It's not a whistle!" Sirius insisted, yelling through Harry's door. "You hear me, Harry? It's a manly sound of success. Not a whistle!"

Harry stripped off all his clothes and couldn't even bother to clean off the dried blood. He fell into his bed and pulled the sheets up.

He heard Sirius' bedroom door close and a final muffled yell. "It's not a whistle!"

Harry allowed his worries to fade and happily wriggled into his pillow. His last conscious thought before sleep claimed him was 'I'm really gonna feel this one in the morning.'

Author's Note: See? I didn't end with a cliffie this time. It happens on occasion. And I'll just allay any worries right now and say we've got a lot of fic to go still. We're maybe a little over half-way or so through this fic. I love hearing what you all think. Reviews make me want to write faster. It may be a cheap ploy but it's still true. Thanks for all the kind comments and constructive feedback.

Chapter 17

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Author's Note: It took me a bit longer than usual but this chapter is just about double-sized anyway. First thing I should say is that there will NOT be any significant Deathly Hallows spoilers in here. I myself have only read about half the book. And I decided I want to finish writing this before I read the rest of it. I've read the spoilers, so don't fear spoiling anything in a review, but just for those wondering, there won't be hardly any Deathly Hallows incorporation here. Maybe I'll drop in a veiled joke for those familiar with it, but no spoilers.

And one thing I will say is that when I end a chapter on a cliffie, I'm going to definitely try and get the next chapter out within a week. (That wasn't foreshadowing at all. Ahem. Right. Moving on.)

Ginny floated down to check out the kitchen and found that it wasn't empty.

Bellatrix looked up and caught the gaze of the tentative ghost. "Hello," she greeted.

"Hi," Ginny succinctly replied.

Neither was sure what to make of the other. After an awkward silence they both began at the same time, "So…"

"Sorry," Ginny apologized first. "Go ahead."

"No, no," Bellatrix shook her head. "I'm not even sure what I was going to say but it probably would have been something dumb. Please, what were you saying?"

"Right," Ginny said knowing she too was just trying to fill the air. "I was just gonna say, sleeping with Moony, eh? How's that going?"

"Hmm," Bellatrix wondered. "I guess it's been… productive?"

"Well that's…" Ginny paused thinking most males would not take that as a sterling endorsement on their sexual prowess. She settled on finishing, "…good."

"Don't get me wrong," Bellatrix explained. "The process is pleasant."

"Pleasant," Ginny repeated.

"Pleasurable even," Bellatrix said. "That's a better description. It's just… I mean I've had sex with people that hate me before."

"Naturally," Ginny agreed thinking how limited Bellatrix's options would be if she didn't sleep with people that hate her.

Bellatrix frowned and continued, "But I guess with Remus, it's like he hates himself just as much."

"You don't mind that he's a werewolf?" Ginny inquired wondering if Bellatrix was letting her membership in the cruel and racist club expire.

Bellatrix shrugged. "I suppose I'd rather he wasn't, but so would Remus. I'm just glad my baby-daddy is someone the Lords Black like. I'll take the sperm however it comes."

"Huh," Ginny chuckled uneasily at the pun. "That's funny."

Bellatrix sighed and exasperatedly said, "You know I'm fine with you hating me for no reason, right?"

"Oh good," Ginny said in relief. "I mean I kinda felt bad, considering everybody hates you. And I didn't really want to pile on but… it is you."

Bellatrix looked closer at Ginny. "I didn't kill you, did I?"

Ginny shook her head.

"Because that might actually explain a few things."

"Nope," Ginny assured her. "You didn't kill me. I know who killed me. And Harry killed him."

"Anyone I know?" Bellatrix asked.

Ginny quickly quieted. "Don't think you ever met him."

"Alright," Bellatrix agreed recognizing the ghost's reticence. "Let's change the subject."

Ginny floated there for a moment and suggested, "Or I could just leave."

"Wait," Bellatrix pleaded. "I…"

"Yes?"

"I wanted to ask you something, and please, don't take this personally. I don't mean to offend you."

Ginny shrugged. "I already hate you."

"Good point," Bellatrix replied. "And like I said don't take this personally, but… are you, that is, I guess… Alright, I'm just going to say it. Are you a Weasley?"

Ginny harrumphed. "What's so bad about Weasleys?"

"Oh-kay," Bellatrix backed away. "That answers that question."

"Maybe there haven't been quite so many homicidal psychotic bitches in the Weasley family as in some families, but…"

"Do you not remember your mother at all?" Harry jokingly asked from the door.

Ginny turned back towards Harry. "Hey now, she wasn't… homicidal."

Harry looked at Ginny and said nothing.

"Okay there was that one time," Ginny admitted. "But that shouldn't count."

Harry looked at Ginny curiously. "Are you implying your mother was a psychotic bitch?"

"You didn't live with her through menopause."

Harry winced imagining how well Molly Weasley would have accepted that. "Point taken."

"I was just wondering because you look like a Weasley," Bellatrix explained. "And there's so damn many of you I wouldn't be surprised if your parents couldn't keep track of them all."

Harry chuckled.

Ginny frowned at Harry. "I thought you loved the Weasleys."

"With as much as he loves and as many as there are," Bellatrix retorted. "It's almost mathematically impossible for him not to have at least once or twice."

"Hey," Harry intelligently defended.

"I'm not talking about whoring himself around like a whorey whore," Ginny snapped. "This is just a phase until he comes to terms with my death."

"Really?" Bellatrix asked skeptically. She looked at Harry and asked, "Is that why you're such a slut?"

"He's not a bigger slut than me," Sirius jumped in as he walked up behind Harry.

Harry just shook his head. "We're going to get a little work done. We'll be back this afternoon. You're not going anywhere, are you?"

"I'm going to go that muggle store to buy some pregnancy tests," Bellatrix said. "But other than that, I'll be here."

"Be careful," Harry said. "Those two Death Eaters are still camping out across the street last I checked."

"Peed on them this morning," Sirius asserted.

"And while they seem content to just observe us," Harry explained pointing at himself and Sirius. "I'm not sure you're going to get extended similar kindness."

"Although," Sirius happily suggested. "If you decide that you want to die-"

"Let's go," Harry interrupted grabbing onto Sirius apparating them both away with a crack.

Bellatrix turned towards Ginny. "Looks like it's just you and me."

Ginny looked at Bellatrix curiously before she too felt a tug and was sent careening through the ether towards wherever Harry had apparated off too.

"Or just me," Bellatrix corrected to herself. She began to wonder over how quickly she was able to clear a room. She took a careful sniff of her own armpits before realizing what she was doing. "I just want anyone invisibly watching me right now to know that that wasn't what it looked like. But I won't explain it, until you reveal yourselves."

Bellatrix was a mixture of relieved and disappointed when no one came forward.

"Why wait until tonight?" Sirius said looking through his magical omnioculars. "We could probably take care of this before dinner."

Harry saw Ginny had stayed visible and tagged along. He answered, "Because he's got a mission tonight and I'd rather save the larceny until after our dinner with… them."

"Tell me again why you're robbing this guy?" Ginny asked, pretending to lay down on the edge of Harry's chair.

"Because he's a Death Eater and we've never heard of him," Sirius answered.

"What's his name?" Ginny inquired, being careful not to yell right in Harry's ear.

"Alan Weston," Harry replied.

"Never heard of him," Ginny agreed. "So why him?"

"Because we're manly men and we like challenges," Sirius assured her looking at the property with his omnioculars.

Harry flipped a twig at Sirius and explained, "Because he's got better wards here than a crappy looking place like that should have. Which to me says there's something worth stealing in there."

"I think we can call it official," Sirius announced. "No house elves and I still haven't been able to make out a painting yet."

"Did you get any fun names from your interrogation of Bella, besides of course the mysterious Alan Weston?" Ginny asked pointing towards the veiled property she couldn't see.

"Probably the most interesting one was a name I didn't get," Harry said.

"He counts," Sirius moaned.

Harry was enjoying Sirius' frustration and looked over at the ghost. "It appears in this world Severus Snape never joined the Death Eaters."

"What?" Ginny asked. "Really?"

"He counts," Sirius repeated.

Harry was quite amused. "Apparently, they turned him down."

Sirius went from grumbling to alert and indignant immediately. "You never mentioned that part!"

"I enjoyed it more knowing you didn't know," Harry said with a snicker. "I never even considered that the Dark Lord could say no."

Sirius was torn between staring down Harry and laughing out loud to think Severus tried to join the Death Eaters and got rejected.

"Apparently, it drove him straight to Dumbledore," Harry said. "In fairness, he was still in school at the time so Dumbledore may have just been close by."

"That's awesome," Sirius exclaimed happily.

"Well I'm glad to hear you think so," Harry said with a grin. "Because I told Lily you were hoping to talk Potions with him over dinner. She made sure that you'll get to sit next to Severus."

Sirius' face fell. "That's not even funny, Harry."

"The rumor is that when Snape heard the news, he actually smiled," Harry calmly explained. "If that's true, then you're probably his best friend."

Sirius' mouth twitched. "Okay, maybe it's a little funny."

Ginny entertained herself by poking her ghostly finger through Harry's shoulder.

Sirius acted unconcerned and asked, "You were kidding, right?"

Harry glanced at Sirius, said nothing, and turned back towards the wards of the property with a smug smile.

"Ha-ha, point made," Sirius rambled. "No Snivellus though, right? Right? Just tell me, dammit!"

Harry could not stop smiling at the mere sight of the first real home that he remembered. Since he had last seen the castle, he'd gained a new appreciation for ward work and Hogwarts was a real treat. The Hogwarts wards reminded Harry of Swiss cheese made of steel. The wards were as solid as any in the world, excusing the obvious and gigantic holes. It wasn't long before the wards were just too bright and Harry was forced to cancel his oculamagi spell.

"Hey Harry?" Sirius tried to sound jovial but the worry was apparent in his voice. "You're not going to break down and cry like a sissy, are you?"

Harry stopped walking and turned to his godfather.

"Because I mean when you become a pathetic blubbering mess and start calling her Mum-"

Harry cast a silencing charm around them and put a hand on Sirius to keep him from walking away. "Stop. Look at me, Padfoot."

Sirius turned to look at Harry. He saw how humorless Harry's expression was and suggested, "If you want to tell them the truth…"

"Do you want to tell them?" Harry asked, already knowing the answer. "This is your secret too."

Sirius paused almost afraid to be the cause of Harry's theoretical emotional distress.

"Relax. I know I've always been indifferent to telling the Potters who we are," Harry explained. "But let me reiterate what should have been abundantly clear by now. You, Sirius, mean a lot more to me than James and Lily do."

"Lily and James," Sirius softly corrected. "It sounds nicer saying her name first because she's a better person."

"Lily and James," Harry repeated with a grin, while keeping his hand on his godfather's shoulder and looking him right in the eye. "Lily and James are not my parents. My parents died a long time ago. My parents were a couple of your best friends." Harry pointed up towards the castle. "Those two people barely know you. They had to grieve for a lost baby and have since raised a couple more kids in a family that never existed in our old world. Treating them like my parents is an insult to my parents' memory."

Sirius was about to respond but Harry put up a hand to stop him.

"I highly doubt my real parents would begrudge me if I did treat this Lily and James like parents," Harry explained. "But it matters to me. And while I'd like to get to know Lily and James, they are not and never will be my parents. Nor will they ever be as important to me as my godfather, the person my parents chose to look after me in their absence."

Sirius' eyes were getting a little watery as he couldn't keep the smile off his face. "I love you, kid," Sirius exclaimed hugging Harry as tight as he had the first time he'd seen him in this world.

"I love you too," Harry said hugging Sirius back. He pulled back and looked Sirius in the eye again. "Now do us both a favor," Harry grabbed Sirius' chin to make sure he was paying complete attention to him. "Act like a fucking man, you little bitch."

Sirius pretended to be offended as Harry spun him around.

Harry slapped his godfather on the ass and said, "Besides, it looks like your new best friend is headed this way."

Sirius' eyes widened and he turned back to Harry fearfully. "Why is Snivellus walking this way? Why Harry, why?"

Harry just smiled saying nothing and canceled his silencing charm.

Severus spotted the two men ahead of him and was trying to avoid eye contact.

"Listen," Sirius explained pointing straight towards Severus Snape as he approached. "I don't know hardly anything about Potions and Harry here's a very cruel liar. I don't even like Potions."

Severus had been hoping to avoid them completely when Sirius addressed him with his absurd declarations. Severus responded in disgust, "Don't talk to me. Ever." He then veered around the two Lord Blacks and continued stalking in the direction he had been headed.

"He was just walking to the greenhouses," Harry happily said to his godfather. "Kind of an odd way for you to greet him, don't you think?"

Sirius felt as much like an idiot as he felt relief that Harry had only been joking earlier. "You're a dick."

Harry snickered. "Exactly what were you thinking when you saw that Snivellus was carrying flowers?"

"I saw my lunch flash before my eyes," Sirius answered turning to walk towards the Entrance Hall. "Oh, here they come."

Lily Potter, James Potter Jr., and Albus Dumbledore were all walking out to greet the Lords Black.

Harry stopped and whispered, "You really think wearing a Dementor's cloak would have sent the wrong message?"

"You passed out after wearing it for three minutes," Sirius reminded quietly from the corner of his mouth.

"Three and a half," Harry argued.

"Yeah," Sirius decided. "That's the wrong message. And you owe me for this."

"Greetings," Albus loudly said as the two Potters and he approached. "Lord Black and Lord Black. I'm delighted to see you accepted Professor Potter's invitation."

Harry could feel his mother's approach and tried to pretend there was nothing out of the ordinary. "Please Headmaster, for tonight, I'm Harry and he's Sirius."

Sirius noticed Harry slinking away and slapped him hard on the shoulder in a friendly gesture, while adding, "But unless you count his back, he's not really hairy. And I am rarely serious."

"Oof," Harry groaned, partly from the smack and partly from Sirius' line. "Can't you not crack a name joke, just once?"

Albus' eyes were twinkling as he added, "If it makes you feel any better, I've never been more than two-thirds bus. Further proof there really is no truth in advertising."

Jimmy, Harry, and Sirius all turned towards the Headmaster in silent disbelief.

Albus saw the looks he was receiving and how Lily seemed transfixed just at the sight of Harry. "Yes well, I believe you have already met our Head Boy, James Potter, and this is his mother, our Professor of Muggle Studies, Lily Potter."

Lily felt the monster in her chest rising up and didn't realize she was staring until Jimmy elbowed her and whispered, "Mum!"

"I'm sorry," Lily said suddenly paying attention again. "It's a pleasure to finally meet you Harry, Sirius," she greeted and shook both their hands.

"You too," Sirius said, enjoying Harry's silent discomfort.

"If the stories my son has been telling me are true, Harry," Lily smiled warmly, "then I'd hate to be your mother."

"What?" Harry blurted out before he could stop himself.

Lily kept the pleasant smile on her face as she explained, "The scars, the adventures, the danger? She must have been worried silly."

"Oh," Harry said, trying to act casual and failing. "Yeah, well she handled it pretty well considering-"

Sirius coughed and interrupted Harry, noticing Harry was sweating already.

Harry glanced at his godfather and helpfully explained with a smile, "She died when I was one."

"Oh," Lily stopped smiling and felt bad for being so insensitive.

Harry saw Lily's face fall and tried to make her feel better, "My dad too." Immediately after Harry said it, he wondered why he thought that would make her feel better.

Lily found herself pitying and sympathizing for Harry and added to the fun. "My firstborn son died."

Everyone turned to her in surprise.

Lily saw them look at her and quickly explained, "He was one as well." She belatedly realized that this was not the best way to lighten the mood.

The group of five were all exchanging looks at the awkward direction of the night's first conversation.

Sirius finally broke the silence. "I had a goldfish once."

"Sirius, stop," Harry jumped in before his godfather could get going.

"Okay," Sirius agreed not really wanting to dredge up painful memories of Goldie.

"How about a tour?" Albus said cheerfully changing the subject.

"We're not going to be eating with the students, are we?" Harry said as they all began to follow Albus. "Because I'm not big on being on display and Sirius could very well spend the whole time looking inappropriately at the seventh years."

"No," Albus chuckled, apparently unconcerned about an older man taking advantage of his students. "We'll be dining in a private chamber connected to my office. Though we are expecting James Potter and Remus and Tonks Lupin to join us when James' and Tonks' shifts end. I believe you have met them a few times. And Sarah Potter was called away with Madame Pomfrey to St. Mungos, but she may be able to join us as well."

"Oh good, James," Sirius said. "I think he's starting to warm up to me."

Jimmy made no effort to hide his derisive snort as he walked next to Harry.

Lily felt the need to defend her husband and explained, "You remind him too much of his best friend." Lily paused and observed Sirius for a couple seconds. "And now having met you, I can see the resemblance is uncanny."

"Really," Sirius said turning away to look at the castle as they slowly walked. "I hear that's pretty common among relatives."

"I suppose you do kind of look like him," Lily continued. "But I was referring to the way you carry yourself and your attitude. Sharing a name doesn't help matters either."

"Quite the co-inky-dink," Harry said pausing to look around and avoid the subject. "So this is… a hallway?"

"Yeah, tour?" Sirius said stopping to face Albus.

Albus was smiling mischievously and said, "I was going to explain to you the history of the Entrance Hall, but when you both kept walking I thought I'd see where you were leading us."

"Oops," Sirius said looking at Harry who had been also walking through Hogwarts forgetting that they weren't supposed to know their way around. "I thought I was following you."

"And I thought I was following you," Harry said nodding at Albus.

"It is always interesting the places our feet will take us," Albus assured them. "And you were quite correct. This is a hallway."

"Fascinating," Harry said looking around.

"Actually, it is an interesting story as you'll notice the shift in color here," Albus began to explain while pointing at the wall. "The stone in this section of the hallway is only about seven centuries old. Contrary to popular belief, many-"

"Oww!" Jimmy yelped out attracting everyone's attention as he rubbed the area of his arm that had been pinched by an invisible arm.

Albus had stopped and looked towards Jimmy while glancing at the others. "Is something the matter?"

"No, I…" Jimmy trailed off at the look from Harry and quickly corrected. "Sorry! I just remembered I need to talk to Harry privately about a project. And with dinner and everything, I figured I should get it out of the way now."

"Perhaps we all could be of assistance?" Albus offered.

"No," Jimmy insisted. "That's a bad idea because…" He looked to Harry for help.

Harry rolled his eyes and jumped in. "Jimmy had some research questions about the uniqueness of magic and my magic in particular. I don't want to be a sideshow freak, so I agreed to help him understand singular magical phenomena as long as we avoid specifics. You guys go on with the tour. We'll catch up."

Albus frowned. "I really would rather we-"

"Surely the Head Boy won't be getting lost," Harry interrupted. "If your unease comes from my secretive nature, just have Fawkes keep an eye on us."

Albus tilted his head down to look at Harry and the very nervous looking James Potter Jr. without the buffer of his glasses. "I am sorry to say I cannot just order Fawkes to-"

He was interrupted by the flash of fire and sudden appearance of the phoenix in question.

"Looks like the flying puppy comes when called," Harry said with a smile.

Albus looked on in surprise when his companion didn't seem to take offense. "Fawkes?"

Fawkes was staring at Harry and flew over to his shoulder, nodding at Albus.

Harry reached up a hand to pet the phoenix only to see the bird was tilting to its side, clearly lifting its leg like a puppy.

"Don't even think about it," Harry said pointing at the bird.

Fawkes put both legs down and gripped tightly, pinching Harry.

Harry winced while acting overly masculine, as if he was unaffected by a minor pinch. "Great then," Harry gasped quietly as Fawkes tightened his hold. "Jimmy, you said something about an unused classroom you picked out?"

"Yeah," Jimmy agreed with a hop in his step. "Follow me."

"We'll wait for you in the library," Lily called out towards her son.

They hurried down the corridor and around a corner. Jimmy was going to continue down towards the dungeons when Harry jerked on his arm and said, "This way."

Harry stopped and saw they were clear. "Did you bring the invisibility cloak?"

"I'm trying to go with the flow like your letter said," Jimmy explained. "But I don't have an invisibility cloak. My dad does but I can't afford one."

"He didn't give it to you?" Harry asked in shock. "That's wrong on so many levels."

Jimmy shrugged. "He seems to think I'd just use it to get into trouble."

"Yeah," Harry agreed. "But with the cloak you wouldn't get caught so it's not really trouble."

Jimmy chuckled. "I don't think Dad would go for that argument."

"Make sure no one's coming," Harry instructed as he unshrunk his satchel and pulled out his own invisibility cloak. "I just brought one, so we're going to have to huddle."

Harry still had Fawkes on his shoulder and pulled the cloak over the three of them. Jimmy inched closer but still the cloak didn't even reach their knees.

"That's not gonna work," Harry stated.

"I can be disillusioned."

"No, that's too obvious when you're running," Harry said.

Jimmy took a step back and asked, "I'm going to be running?"

Harry took a moment to think about it and shrugged. "I wouldn't rule it out."

Fawkes vanished in a burst of flame from under the cloak only to reappear right on top of it and clamp back down on Harry's shoulder. The cloak settled down almost to their ankles.

Harry looked up through the haze of the cloak at the mischievous bird and smiled. "That'll work. We'll just have to hunch a bit."

They slowly began to sneak their way down the hallway.

"Hey Harry?"

"Yeah?"

"How come Fawkes wasn't offended when you called him a flying puppy? I thought phoenixes were proud creatures."

Harry looked up at the bird on his shoulder. He explained, "Fawkes wasn't offended because he knows I like phoenixes and just said that to annoy him. And he also knows that acting like it doesn't bother him annoys me right back. But I know how much it really irritates-OWW!" Harry shrieked as the phoenix's claws dug into his shoulder.

"Shh," Jimmy said from Harry's other side. "Someone's coming."

Two young girls came walking around the corner and stopped at the sight of a mysteriously floating phoenix.

Harry tapped Jimmy on the shoulder and they slowly continued walking down the hall towards the two girls.

"Are you seeing what I'm seeing?" The first girl asked her friend in glasses.

The second girl with glasses took off her spectacles and wiped them clean on her robe. She put her glasses back on. "Phoenixes are birds. Of course they can fly."

"Yeah but usually they have to flap their wings!"

The girl with glasses squinted at the approaching creature. "That is odd."

Harry and Jimmy silently walked right past the two girls who were just staring at Fawkes in fascination. The girls felt special knowing how few people were lucky enough to see a phoenix floating so close.

Harry held up his finger telling Jimmy to be quiet. As soon as they were past the girls and Fawkes' back was facing them, Harry loudly intoned, "There's a lot you don't know about phoenixes."

"Ahh!" the first girl shrieked in fright as she began to run down the hall.

"They speak English!" the one in glasses exclaimed chasing after her friend. "And in a surprisingly deep voice!"

"Ahh!" was her friend's only response.

Harry was holding onto Jimmy who was cracking up next to him. He could feel Fawkes amusement as well. "Come on. Don't get the giggles on me."

They managed to make their way to down to the second floor girls' bathroom that was widely known to be haunted.

"Your adventure for me is to sneak into the girls' bathroom?" Jimmy asked worriedly. He indignantly added, "And not even one of the high traffic ones?"

"Shh," Harry said. "I don't particularly want to talk to Myrtle so keep it down."

Once they were in the room Harry cast a locking charm on the door, ensuring privacy. He gave Fawkes a brief warning and whipped the invisibility cloak off. "No," Harry explained after double-checking that the bathroom was empty. "I thought I'd take you somewhere legendary. And you know, hopefully not get either of us killed."

"Legendary?" Jimmy perked up. He watched Harry reach down to a sink and hiss in parseltongue at it. Jimmy's voice cracked a little as he asked, "Killed?"

Harry took a step back and smiled as the sinks began shifting to reveal a huge pipe. "This, my friend, is the entrance to Salazar Slytherin's Chamber of Secrets."

"A girls' bathroom?" Jimmy repeated incredulously.

Harry shrugged. "I'm not one to judge, but I figure there's a story behind it."

Jimmy walked up to the edge and saw no end to the pipe in the darkness.

Harry looked down the hole and explained, "It's a test of faith. It looks like a never-ending hole, and anything you test it with will act as if it's a hole," Harry added when Jimmy tossed an old bar of soap into the pipe.

"But if you have faith that the platform is there, and you take a full step right on to it, it's there." Harry saw Jimmy getting focused and held up a hand to stop him. "Don't step on the platform until you're sure."

Jimmy took another deep breath and looked straight at Harry, refusing to even look down the pipe when he stepped forward.

Harry was going to remember for a long time the face that Jimmy made when he tumbled head first down the pipe. He listened for Jimmy's shrieking to reach the end. He looked at Fawkes, "You want to ride with me?"

Fawkes shook his head.

"Didn't think so," Harry said. He shut his mouth and squeezed his nose as he slid down the massive pipe.

He let his body sway with the motions as he slipped down the dusty, grimy pipe. Listening carefully and remembering the fall, Harry held his arms out and slowed himself down just as he reached the bottom. He managed to gracefully land on his feet right in the middle of his first step forward.

Harry grinned brightly. "Didn't have enough faith, did you?"

"There never was a platform, was there?" Jimmy said in resignation.

"Certainly not with that attitude."

Jimmy cast a cleansing charm on Harry without prompting. "I gotta say, as secret chambers go, so far, I'm unimpressed."

"We got a few pipes to walk through," Harry said drawing his wand and taking the lead. "And do me a favor."

"Yeah?"

"If you see anything moving, close your eyes, and go fetal. Alright?"

Jimmy had been walking with Harry and stopped right where he was. "Excuse me?"

"As a favor to me," Harry urged.

Jimmy quickly thought back to what he knew of Salazar's not so mythical chamber. "Isn't this chamber supposed to house a monster of some sort? And I know some words can get twisted through time but monster is a pretty clear one."

Harry reluctantly nodded. "Hence the close your eyes and go fetal."

"What are we doing down here anyway?"

"Well…" Harry admitted. "I kinda don't think the monster is here. And I figured I'd just take a peek and see if it is."

"We're here looking for the monster?"

Harry turned back at Jimmy and nodded, pointing to the side.

Jimmy moved away from the door while Harry hissed another parseltongue password. Jimmy verbally agreed, "Closing my eyes and going fetal sounds like a pretty good plan."

"Hey Fawkes?" Harry called out as the phoenix flew up. "Keep an eye on the kid, would you?"

"I'm not a kid," Jimmy argued. As Harry walked through the circular serpent like door, Jimmy turned to the phoenix and whispered, "Anything happens and you get me out of there. If I die, it's your fault."

Jimmy hurried to catch up with Fawkes hanging on to him. "I'm not a kid, Harry."

"You do realize you're Head Boy at a school for children?"

Jimmy silently pouted.

"Relax Jimmy," Harry said as he spotted an old decaying massive shed skin. "I call you a kid the same way I call Fawkes a…"

"A flying puppy?"

"I used that one already," Harry paused still thinking about it. He snapped his fingers in success, "An Augurey with a combustion problem."

Jimmy winced, "Oww Fawkes. Redirect that anger at him not me. Him." Jimmy almost tripped and looked to the ground. "What is this? Some kind of fungal growth?"

Harry glanced at his unofficial brother.

"It covers almost this entire pipe," Jimmy stated as he bent down to break a piece of it off. "And it doesn't tear at all."

"It's not a fungus," Harry assured him. "You don't recognize this?"

"Its texture looks like a repeating pattern."

"It's skin, Jimmy."

"Skin?" Jimmy repeated doubtfully. "No way. This thing is thick and huge. Not even the largest Horntail gets this size. And usually only snakes…" Jimmy trailed off taking a step back. He looked all the way down the pipe in both directions realizing just how big the faux fungal growth was. "Harry?"

"Yeah?"

"You wouldn't really put my life in danger, right?"

"Of course not."

"So this isn't the shed skin of basilisk big enough to use us as toothpicks, right?"

Harry paused before answering, "I wouldn't really put your life in danger."

"Harry."

"Besides, basilisks can't use toothpicks. They have no arms."

"This one might! It's probably big enough to have evolved."

"Don't be silly," Harry said getting to the last door before the main chamber. "But don't forget that 'close your eyes and go fetal' plan either."

"You're supposed to be assuring me and comforting me. Not scaring me."

Harry stepped into the main chamber and saw the rows and rows of carved serpents. "Sure thing, kid."

Jimmy held his tongue while Fawkes gripped him tighter. "I get it, Fawkes. I'm pretending it doesn't bother me." He looked down the hall at all the carved snakes. "Whoa."

"I know," Harry softly said, looking around for any signs of recent life. "A lot of work for something he didn't want anyone else to see."

"This really is the Chamber of Secrets," Jimmy said walking up to one of the hooded snake statues.

"And that really was a basilisk skin, so keep it down," Harry said approaching the giant bust of Salazar himself. Harry resisted the urge to roll his eyes as he hissed, "Speak to me, Slytherin, greatest of the Hogwarts Four. Open your giant gaping maw, you bloated arrogant blowhard."

Jimmy was unable to contain the girlish shriek he let out when the mouth of the giant head started to open. He sprinted away to hide around the nearest statue, closed his eyes, and assumed a fetal position.

Harry saw Jimmy dash around the corner and glanced into the opening of Slytherin's mouth. He quickly decided he'd seen enough.

"Oh god, oh god, oh god," Harry started chanting as he sprinted past where Jimmy was peeking between his fingers. "Run! Go! Green light!"

Jimmy shot to his feet and was sprinting with everything he had until he finally caught up with Harry, who turned to him and said, "Red light!" Harry skidded to a stop as Jimmy kept running.

Jimmy slowed down and turned around in confusion. He saw Harry leaning forward catching his breath. "What… what…"

"You've never played red light, green light?"

"What?"

"Just wanted to see if you were faster than me," Harry panted out. "You definitely are when you're scared, that's for sure."

"No monster?"

Harry shook his head. "Nah. It's gone. There's a layer of dust everywhere. It hasn't been here for years."

"Are you sure?" Jimmy asked carefully peering around Harry.

"Yup," Harry said. "I saw a spider in Salazar's giant nostril as it rose. No spider would be anywhere near a basilisk."

"Oh," Jimmy said, a little disappointed. "Is that it?"

"That's it."

"Huh," Jimmy said. "I was expecting more."

"Yeah, sorry about that," Harry agreed leading the way back out of the chamber. "Next time, near death. That's a promise."

Jimmy was beginning to feel the adrenaline leave his system and wasn't so sure how he felt about that promise. "You said something about payment?"

"Only the most valuable goods for this particular institution," Harry said. "Two bottles of firewhiskey and the last three issues of Pumpin' Kin."

Jimmy snickered as he stepped over the giant shed skin. He cast a pair of severing charms and grabbed himself a single scale as a souvenir. "I'll take the firewhiskey. You can keep the magazines."

"Are you sure?" Harry asked skeptically. "A male your age should never turn down porn. That's just unhealthy. If saucy pureblooded cousins aren't your thing-"

"It's not that."

"You know there's blokes in there too," Harry explained. "I don't need to know nothing."

"Stop eyeing me Harry and no," Jimmy confidently ordered. "I don't need them because I got a subscription. There's a guy at the post office who forwards that stuff for a galleon."

Harry felt those brotherly feelings of pride stirring inside him. "Good work, kid. Good work." They reached the entrance again and Harry looked up. "You mind giving us a lift, Fawkes?"

Fawkes condescendingly glared at Harry.

"I've got a broom in case you were feeling moody," Harry explained. "I wasn't using you or forcing you to be our flying flaming mule."

Fawkes chirped and lifted Jimmy up into the air. Harry grabbed on as the phoenix flew them up and out of the tunnel.

Harry passed Jimmy the two shrunken bottles of firewhiskey and decided to forego the invisibility cloak. "Tell no one about this, got it?"

"I got it," Jimmy said confidently as they exited Myrtle's haunted bathroom. They'd walked about ten seconds before Fawkes hopped off Jimmy and onto Harry's shoulder.

Jimmy tentatively requested, "Can I… can I ask you something, Harry?"

"Sure," Harry said taking a right towards the library.

"Do you have the hots for my mum? Because it's never gonna happen."

Harry stumbled but regained his composure. "Good god, no. There is no chance in hell that would ever happen."

"What's that supposed to mean?" Jimmy asked. "She's a very lovely witch."

"Stop and think about what you're arguing," Harry said patting him on the back to assure him. "Trust me. I'm as attracted to your mum as you are."

"Okay," Jimmy accepted, "creepy but okay. So then why the hell did you get that lovesick drooling idiot look when you met her? And why did she get it too?"

Harry got the feeling he was pretty much cementing his own special place in hell. "What can I say? It's not like I can turn this sex appeal off like a light. This body just looks good whether I want it to or not."

Jimmy cringed. "I'm sorry I asked."

The pair of young men and the phoenix walked back into the library and found the rest of their group.

"And this is the library," Jimmy instructed waving towards the stacks pretending to be a tour guide.

"What do you call these strange box shaped things?" Harry inquired.

"Those are called books."

"Books," Harry repeated. "I've heard of those."

"Harry," Sirius pleadingly greeted. "You missed some absolutely enchanting stories."

"Lord Harry Black," Albus introduced. "I would like you to meet my Deputy Headmistress, Professor of Transfiguration, Minerva McGonagall."

"Pleasure," Harry said shaking his old Head of House's hand.

"Sirius was asking some interesting questions about animagi forms," Minerva said shaking his hand.

"Purely hypothetical, of course," Harry said.

"I was just telling him about the common misconception that animagi forms are restricted to the animal world," Minerva stated.

"I keep telling Sirius his form is probably a brick."

"Hypothetically," Sirius added.

"Hypothetically," Harry agreed.

Minerva shook her head in amusement. "I have not heard of inanimate objects ever being an innate form, but there have been numerous insects and a few other magical entities that have taken the place of a more traditional form."

"Well I was thinking of a real shiny brick," Harry explained as if it would make a difference.

"Speaking of food," Sirius said, "we about ready for dinner?" Sirius nodded to Harry and added, "I informed them that we had plans later this evening and would have to leave by nine."

"Bricks make you think of food?" Jimmy asked when it seemed no one else was going to.

Sirius just nodded. "Dementors too."

Harry nodded in understanding. "Yeah, Sirius' cooking is really bad."

"Why don't we head to my office and wait for the rest of our guests," Albus suggested. "I believe the Lupins and Mr. Potter are due any moment now."

"I cannot believe you!" Harry shouted at James Potter.

"No, no," James insisted. "You're not listening to me."

"Oh I hear the words coming out of your mouth, they just don't make any sense," Harry retorted.

"I can prove it to you," James argued, unaware his voice was getting louder.

"Gentlemen, please," Albus interjected trying to calm the two men down.

"Oh you think you can prove it?" Harry said looking his father up and down. "Even at your age?"

"Alright, that's it," James snapped throwing his napkin down and getting up. "Let's go. You and me. Right now."

"No!" Lily shouted over the two men. "We're trying to have a nice dinner here."

"Sorry, honey," James said dropping his head in respect.

"See?" Harry triumphantly exclaimed. "Even your wife knows the Hawkshead is an inherently flawed defensive formation."

"If the other team is doing any kind of looping," James continued in spite of Lily's protests, "then there's no way a Ploy is getting past and it eats up Parkin's Pincers like nobody's business."

Sirius sighed. He knew Harry and James were very different people. He knew Harry would rub James the wrong way just as he had rubbed James the wrong way. And yet even still, two very different men could always find common ground arguing about Quidditch.

Rather than risk losing Harry, Sirius knew how to nip this discussion in the bud. "Personally, I like Quodpot better."

James stifled a gasp and looked right at Sirius, narrowing his eyes. "You would."

"Don't listen to him," Harry assured the others at dinner. "He doesn't like Quodpot better. He just doesn't want us talking about Quidditch."

"Thank you, Sirius," Lily said. "I'll have to remember that one."

Sirius saw Remus and Tonks were both enjoying his frustration. He figured he'd try and stir the pot some. "So Remus, how do you like working with the Weasley twins?" Sirius turned towards James as he explained, "You know, making a career of jokes and pranks."

Remus was amused as he looked between the two and answered. "It's actually very similar to any standard retail outlet. Fred and George have shrewd business acumen to go with their imaginations."

James looked inordinately pleased when that answer made Sirius frown.

"But it definitely is a lot more fun," Remus continued and saw Sirius grinning while James frowned. "And I've had some input on a few new ideas and a few improvements on old ideas that the twins have taken and run with. So keep your eyes out for the Moony line of mischief making."

Lily smiled and shook her head at her youngest son. "Something tells me you'll have some of his first products."

Jimmy didn't feel like mentioning that he frequently snuck out to Hogsmeade to visit Remus at work and just smiled innocently.

"Nothing I should be worried about I hope," Albus said looking towards Remus.

Remus shook his head. "Of course not, Headmaster. There's not a single one that's against the school rules."

"Yet," Tonks added as she finished off her chicken.

Albus gave up on subtlety and asked, "And what of our other guests? Were you a couple of merry pranksters in your youth? Something tells me if you two went to school together, you got into more than a small amount of trouble."

Harry turned to Sirius. "As much as you might like to think you look that young," Harry grinned. "I think it's that I look that old."

Sirius swatted at Harry's head and explained to Albus, "Believe it or not, I've got better than a decade on ickle Harrikins here and, yes I dabbled into the pranking arts a time or two."

"A decade, really?" James asked, knowing Albus was fishing for information. "So are you cousins or brothers? How are you related?"

Harry saw Sirius glance at him and answered with a grin, "I think brothers sounds pretty fitting, considering the family magic sees us both as Lords. And to answer your question, Albus, no. I wasn't big on pranking although I like to think I caused my fair share of havoc in school."

Tonks began to choke on her water and Remus had to pat her on the back as she coughed.

"An understatement, perhaps," Albus said. "You know in his day, James here was quite the prankster."

James Potter this time began to choke on his drink. Sirius could not have been smiling wider if he tried.

"Oh yes," Albus continued watching both Harry and Sirius very closely. "James, Remus, and your cousin of the same name, Sirius, were quite the troublemakers."

"Really?" Sirius said turning towards James. "I'd love to hear about them. I've gotten some stories about Sirius from Remus, but I'd imagine as Headmaster you'd offer a unique perspective."

"We don't need to go down that road," James interceded.

"Oh but we want to," Sirius replied with a sickeningly sweet smile.

"Harry," Jimmy whispered. "Harry," he tried again as he poked Harry in the side.

Harry snapped out of his momentary daze and turned to the Head Boy. "Hmm?"

"You were staring again," Jimmy explained.

"I was not," Harry whispered back despite knowing he had been. He leaned back as Lily Potter leaned forward across the table towards him.

"Can I talk to you?" Lily asked softly. "Privately?"

Harry glanced over to see James was cringing while Albus was recounting an old prank of the Marauders. He motioned to Sirius that he was going to step out, before he answered Lily. "Yeah, sure."

Lily stood and set her napkin down. "If you'll excuse us for just a moment."

Harry shrugged indicating he wasn't sure what this was about and followed her out of the chamber and into the Headmaster's office.

"Two things," Lily began.

Harry looked at all the portraits pretending to be snoozing and interrupted her. "You mind if we go for a walk or something? I always feel like I'm in trouble with fifty or so old Headmasters watching me."

Lily saw the portraits all turn away or huff, despite pretending to be asleep. "Yeah, I know what you mean." She led him out the office and down the stairs. "Two things," she began again. "First is… I'm not sure how to put this delicately so I'm just going to say it. Are you trying to bewitch me?"

Harry winced having expected this. "Nope. Not trying to bewitch you. Why do you ask?"

Lily led them down towards an empty classroom that had a view of the lake. She walked over to the open window where she could feel the evening breeze. "I don't know. But you stir up all kinds of strange feelings inside me."

Harry knew he was risking becoming a target for indoor lightning but still said, "You're a married woman, Mrs. Potter."

Lily frowned in irritation. "I didn't mean it like that."

Harry continued wincing inwardly and asked, "How did you mean it then?"

Lily sighed and looked out the window. "You know exactly what I'm talking about. I've seen the way you act and you're feeling it too."

"I'm not sure what you're-"

"A mother knows these things," Lily interrupted him, not noticing Harry's brief look of fear. "Raise a couple of kids and your bullshit detector will get finely honed."

Harry quickly tried to mask his emotions when he realized Lily was speaking of her two children.

"This thing," Lily said motioning between herself and Harry. "That you obviously don't want to talk about. You know what it is?"

Harry was keeping his distance from her, hoping it would mute the effects. "I, uhh, I may have a theory."

Lily looked at Harry. "Would you care to share this theory?"

"I'd rather not."

"Tell me your theory."

"Okay," Harry conceded. "Well," Harry knew she wasn't his mother, but it still felt wrong outright lying to her. He was just hoping to not set off her bullshit detector. "I think it means… you're a really good parent."

"What?" Lily asked in confusion.

Harry swallowed the lump in his throat. "It means you're very in touch with your maternal instincts or extrasensory perception. You're very affectionate, caring, and understanding."

"I'm a married woman, Lord Black," Lily interrupted with a grin.

"Right," Harry said feeling perfectly comfortable, just merely drowning in surreal guilt. "It's this study… that I read… in some healer's office."

"Who?"

"Vandelay," Harry answered immediately. "Art Vandelay."

Lily nodded, storing the name in her memory. "I've never heard of Healer Vandelay."

"Oh he's not the… It wasn't his office, I mean." Harry was making nervous hand gestures. "He did the study that I read. And it was his research on magical bonds that… led to my theory."

"I'm listening," Lily urged.

"I don't remember the exact wording," Harry continued. "But the gist was that whenever a magical mother gives birth to a magical baby, the bonds of gestation remain in a unique magical connection."

"Uh-huh," Lily nodded.

"Yeah," Harry said, finally accepting that he'd lied so much today that it really shouldn't matter if he lied for the rest of the night. "It's how witches know exactly what their babies need, when to feed them, all of that… it's just a big magical umbilical cord."

"Really," Lily asked skeptically.

"Yup," Harry said. "But it's invisible. Undetectable even." Harry was nodding more than was healthy. "Invisible and undetectable."

"A great big invisible-"

"And undetectable," Harry added in with a smile.

"And undetectable… magical umbilical cord."

Harry nodded.

Lily briefly thought back to her first baby that was taken from her and tried to imagine what he would look like if he were still alive today. She was attempting to reconcile the image in her head with the young man across from her but she was unable. "Do you think I'm your mother?"

Harry shook his head vigorously. "No, no. You misunderstand. I wasn't saying my great big invisible undetectable magical umbilical cord is connected to you. The point was… I mean…Part of Vandelay's study was on how that bond deteriorates through time. He had a section that I found especially interesting on how orphans, separated from their parents at a young age, get that link severed, and for that reason it doesn't deteriorate."

"Okay," Lily said, following this strange explanation.

"This is how many good parents, or mothers who have been mothers many times over, can just sense or spot an orphan."

Lily nodded finding herself agreeing with this.

"I've been an orphan since I was one, so I've got this invisible magical umbilical cord flying and flailing all around me."

"Is this like your arms thing?"

"Kind of," Harry nodded. "But no. The arm thing is unique to me as far as I know. Orphans everywhere are just spraying invisible undetectable… orphan juice… all around them."

Lily put a hand on Harry to stop him. "Do you need a hug?"

Harry was immensely grateful that she seemed to be buying this and was going to say no when his mouth opened and out came, "Okay."

Harry sighed happily as Lily wrapped her arms around him and hugged him. He knew he didn't deserve this considering the crock of shit he was feeding her, but he wasn't going to pass on the opportunity.

Lily didn't mind the foreign entity furiously writhing inside her so much and sat back in the windowsill. "So I'm just a really good parent?"

Harry felt happy that he'd stolen a hug and got right back into his lies. "Well yes and no."

"Hmm?"

"Discussing my theory out loud just now," Harry continued. "I've been refining it some. And I realized that severing the invisible and undetectable magical umbilical cord would go both ways."

"Oh," Lily said realizing where Harry was going.

Harry nodded. "And since you lost your son when he was so young and the bond was strong, you've got one flying and flailing around too. Spraying your own… juice."

Lily's face saddened as she was once again reminded of the child she lost.

"And I'm guessing having Sarah and Jimmy helped settle it down some, but it'll probably always be there to some degree looking for… Harry."

Lily looked over at Harry with tears in her eyes. "So you do feel it as well."

Harry bit his lip and thought he'd mix in some truth. "I doubt what I feel is the same thing you do, but yeah, I feel it."

"What does it feel like to you?" Lily asked earnestly.

Harry took a deep breath and admitted, "Whenever you're near, or when I see you, I can't help but to think about my own mother. And the life with her that I missed out on."

"Oh you poor thing," Lily said getting up and opening her arms. "Give me another hug."

"Okay," Harry softly agreed, embracing his near mother once more.

Lily let out a pleased sigh and wiped her eyes dry. "Come on. We should get back before they send out a search party."

Harry got up and followed her out of the classroom and back towards the Headmaster's office. "You said there were two things?"

"Hmm?"

"At the start, you said there were two things. What was the second?"

"Oh," Lily said with a mischievous smile. "The other was that you have something in your teeth. Go like this." She made a show of rubbing her front top incisors.

Harry did as she asked.

"You got it," Lily agreed and resumed her walk towards the gargoyle guarding the stairs. She stood the side and waved Harry on the revolving staircase first. She followed behind him and just before Harry entered the side dining chamber Lily stopped him. "Oh and Harry?"

Harry stopped and turned to Lily.

"Someday," Lily said with a firm nod. "I want the truth." She patted Harry on the cheek and walked back into the dining area. "Sorry about that. Have we missed dessert?"

Harry walked back in and took his seat in between Sirius and Jimmy.

"Everything okay?" Sirius asked looking at Harry.

Harry couldn't keep the smile off his face. "Yup." He turned towards the other guests and asked, "What are we talking about?"

"James here," Remus happily summarized, "was telling us all about how close he is to nabbing the Death Eater Bandits."

"Really?" Harry drew out the word in exaggeration. "I've read about them in the paper. What can you tell me?"

James rolled his eyes. "The Daily Prophet has been practically declaring them heroes, as if being the target of a burglar was proof that the victim is a Death Eater."

"Not true?" Harry asked curiously.

James shrugged. "From what I can tell, it's very possible they have all been Death Eaters. But the ones we'd ask are all conveniently out of town and often their neighbors, servants, or wives are the ones who report the robberies."

"And you think you may be close to catching the Bandits? Or is it Bandit? How many are there?"

"The wand signatures are all over the place and those are never unique enough to catch someone, but we think there are at least two different people," James said. "And Albus, I didn't mention this to you, but I think the Bandits might have been in our home."

"Godric's Hollow?" Albus asked curiously. "Did they take anything?"

James shook his head. "That's just it. Nothing was taken but they left the family safe wide open, like a warning."

"Hey!" Jimmy perked up. "I got punished for that."

"No, you argued your way out of punishment," Lily corrected.

Jimmy frowned. "Well you made me feel guilty about it."

James shook his head and explained, "My belief is that they broke in, opened the safe, and then… something happened. Something that angered them about Death Eaters or maybe they'd thought I was a Death Eater and suddenly realized I wasn't. Either way, it had to have been a Potter who opened that safe or else someone with a lot of talent for breaking into things."

"Can't it be both?" Tonks said mischievously.

"You know we should probably get going," Sirius said loudly.

"Yes, we should," Harry agreed standing up quickly. "Thank you all for a lovely dinner."

"I'm sorry Sarah wasn't able to join us," Lily said. "We should do this again some time."

"Our schedules can be pretty hectic," Harry responded in an effort to avoid answering.

"I need a quick word with you," Tonks said waving them away.

"Thanks again," Sirius said as he followed Harry and Tonks out the side chamber.

Tonks waited until they were away from the portraits and whispered into Harry's ear, "I think the Unspeakables know something. They didn't even care that all of the leads I followed on the mysterious large breasted blonde woman were dead ends. It's like they knew they would be."

"You think you're going to get into trouble?" Harry whispered back and looked at her curiously.

Tonks shrugged off his concern. "Just giving my Lords a heads up."

Harry and Sirius said their goodbyes to Tonks and walked the path down to Hogsmeade, aiming for the Hog's Head.

"Did you come through on your side of the bet?" Harry asked.

"Of course," Sirius replied, glancing briefly behind him and pulling out a small device from his pocket. "I nicked this thing off his shelf."

Harry looked at the small contraption. "You stole his Put-Outer?"

Sirius frowned and looked at the little clicker. "I thought it was called a Deluminator."

"Don't be facetious."

"Well what did you snag, oh high and mighty one?"

Harry reached into a hidden pocket and pulled out a ratty hat. "This."

Sirius looked at it in shock. "The Sorting Hat! You stole the Sorting Hat?"

"You think he'll notice?"

"You can't steal the Sorting Hat. That's just… no. Uh-uh. Foul. Against the rules."

Harry laughed and vanished the hat. "Relax. I was kidding. I didn't steal the Sorting Hat, but I'm not going to pull out what I did grab."

"Well then you lose," Sirius triumphantly announced.

"Here," Harry said, pulling open a hidden flap. "This is what I actually grabbed."

A muffled voice could be heard coming from a portrait that had been crammed into a tight space. "This is illegal! You won't get away with this!"

"You stole a portrait?" Sirius asked semi-impressed.

"Phineas Nigellus portrait to be exact," Harry said. "And I replaced it with an identical empty frame."

"You mean…"

Harry nodded. "We get a little loyalty out of him, transfer him into a different frame, one that's linked to the one currently hanging in Dumbledore's office, and we'll have our own personal spy into the heart of Hogwarts."

"And not bound by the usual Headmaster portrait rules," Sirius agreed. "That's good. But mine was still better."

"Your Put-Outer?"

"It's a Deluminator!"

"Fine," Harry sighed. "Since I'm better than you at everything else, I suppose I can be humbler and let you pretend you won this time. I'll buy drinks."

"Thank you," Sirius agreed. "Besides, you didn't have to listen to the unabridged history of the suit of armor near the owlery. Twenty minutes on a suit of armor!"

They walked into the Hog's Head and waved at Gin behind the bar. "Don't get too drunk," Harry whispered. "We've got work to do tonight."

Harry looked back towards the small ash wand on the other side of the ward set. "Dammit."

"We'll get it on the way back," Sirius assured him.

"I know," Harry agreed. "Give me your unicorn hair wand. It's better than nothing."

"Okay," Sirius agreed handing it over. "But it doesn't like you."

"No wands like me," Harry grumbled.

"Well maybe if you hadn't overloaded and exploded your first one…"

"Shut up," Harry said. "And flood the next anchor."

Sirius bent down to one knee and funneled his magic into the stone. The wards flared up to life and Harry used several magical arms with ward stones to open a hole big enough to step through.

"So Remus says the Parselcrotch shirts are selling more than all our other shirts combined," Sirius said calmly making conversation as Harry climbed through the hole.

Harry pulled his ward hole over towards Sirius and let him step through. "You've got to let that go. There's no shame in being worse than me at something."

Sirius frowned as he let the funneling stop and Harry pulled his ward hole back with him.

"Or everything I guess when you really think about it," Harry said as they turned towards the next ward set.

"No one likes a braggart," Sirius grumbled raising his wand to the wards.

"Wait!" Harry stopped him. "Look closer. There's two there."

Sirius squinted. "Can we do both at once?"

Harry considered it and said, "It'll be easier to do them separately."

"Can you make us some space?"

Harry shook his head. "Nope. They're linked in multiple spots." Harry aimed Sirius' wand at himself and thought better of it. "You shrink me. Your wand doesn't like me that much."

Sirius cast a shrinking charm on Harry first and then himself. The small gap between the two linked wards was now plenty of space for their relative size.

"Can you lift the first one?" Sirius asked getting closer to the ward.

"Yup," Harry said pulling out his ward-jack. He slid the metal slat through and began to pump it up and down. The edge of the ward lifted out of the ground and was slowly ratcheted up. "Second one won't stop animagi."

"Can we lift it?" Sirius asked as he slid under the first ward's edge and stopped across from the next.

Harry crawled under the edge and spun the ward-jack around. He let the first ward fall and withdrew the ward-jack. He looked closer at the next one. "Not from this side."

"That's what I figured," Sirius said. "And I'm not sure I can carry the jack through."

"Stick it in a bubble," Harry said. "Your wand too."

"I transform with my wand," Sirius argued.

"I know you can," Harry said. "But better safe than sorry."

"Alright," Sirius said accepting the magic-muting ball with the expanded space inside. He stripped off all of his magical possessions and loaded them and the ward-jack into the ball. With a pop, Sirius had transformed into his dog form and picked up the sealed magic-muting bubble in his mouth. He glanced up at Harry, saw his godson nod, and trotted straight through the ward. Right as he crossed it, the ward flared to life momentarily.

"Whoa," Harry said.

Sirius dropped the bubble from the other side and transformed back. "What was that? Did it trigger?"

Harry shook his head. "No, it didn't trigger but something reacted."

"Are we screwed?" Sirius asked warily.

"I… I don't think so," Harry slowly answered. "But let's take a moment here. Do you see anything from your side?"

Sirius opened up the bubble and withdrew his wand and the jack. He charmed his omnioculars and peered through them. "It looks standard from this side."

Harry frowned. "Yeah, same here. Which worries me."

"Want me to try and jack it?"

"No," Harry said. "Not yet. There's more to this ward than meets the eye which means we need to be careful."

"You know this would be so much easier if you just learned the animagus transformation."

"Good thinking, Padfoot. Let me go grab a book and start studying right now."

Sirius looked closer at the ward. "No anchor stone, right?"

"Right."

"And it didn't react to me, only the bubble right?"

"Mmm-hmm."

Sirius saw Harry was thinking deeply and left him to it.

After a minute or two of silence, Harry asked, "Any ideas?"

Sirius looked at Harry and gulped in surprise. "Uhh… Harry?"

"What?" Harry said. He then noticed Sirius looked smaller. "Why are you shrinking?"

Sirius shook his head. "I'm not shrinking, Harry. You're getting bigger."

"What?" Harry said noticing the wards behind him and in front of him were much closer. "Ah crap. Why didn't you cast a stronger shrinking charm?"

"I cast a fine shrinking charm," Sirius defended. "You were the one who said we shouldn't take Norton's."

"Albus would've spotted it right away," Harry said. He stood up straighter as the two ward walls began to close in on him. "And we've got more pressing issues right now."

"Alright I'm jacking it," Sirius said moving for the ward-jack.

Harry feared what that might do to the ward but was running out of options. He tried to cast a shrinking charm on himself with Sirius' wand. He shrunk slightly, but the excess magic flared from the wand dangerously nearly triggering both wards. "Okay do it. But do it quick."

Sirius slid the ward-jack right through and began to ratchet as fast as he could. "Dammit, Harry. Stop growing."

"Hurry," Harry pleaded using his invisible arms to put slight pressure on both sides of the rapidly approaching wards.

Sirius huffed. "Those wards aren't fatal, right?"

Harry sighed as he was now forced straight up and lacked the room to even turn around. "They both look like lockdown, but this one in front we know is a wild card."

"Fuck," Sirius swore knowing that lockdown would mean they could easily be trapped inside the wards. "That's as high as the jack will go. Apparition, portkey, anything?"

"No, those wards are all solid. Dammit," Harry swore as he felt both wards pushing on his back and front. "If I even bend my knees, we'll probably get locked in."

"Do something!"

"I'm thinking, I'm thinking," Harry pleaded as the wards pushed tighter as the shrinking charm on him continued to slowly wear off. He was now more than three times as tall as Sirius.

"Fuck, fuck," Sirius was chanting as he saw the wards pushing and bending around Harry's growing form.

"Ahh," Harry groaned under the weight.

"Ahh!" Sirius was shouting with him. "Just… just… I don't know."

"I can't," Harry whispered unable to fight the wards pull. He grunted, kept his eyes closed, and silently pleaded for help.

Sirius raised his wand, prepared to simply obliterate every ward around them. "Shield yourself with your arms!"

"They're all that's been keeping the wards off me so far. I can't even move them," Harry wheezed. "I just…"

"Hang on," Sirius said looking around wildly. He finally decided to aim off to the side of Harry and focused his thoughts on the mysterious ward. "Avada Ke-"

And then it happened.

Chapter 18

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Author's Note: Aren't I a good author? I leave you with a minor cliffhanger and less than six days later, the next chapter. That's not bad. No promises on when, but I wouldn't expect another chapter until next weekend (not this weekend, but next). Maybe sooner, maybe later. Thanks for all the reviews. We're getting a few more clues to the plot and a few more indications that there really is a plot here.

"Avada Ke-HOLY CRAP!" Sirius' wand fizzled as the unfinished spell went nowhere.

"Ahh!" Harry was exclaiming as he clenched his eyes shut and kept growing closer to normal size. "Ahh… ahh… uh?" He trailed off as he opened up his eyes and saw the wards passing harmlessly through his suddenly translucent body. "This is new."

Sirius lowered his wand and stared up at the semi-transparent ghostly form of his godson. "Harry! Oh god, Harry. I'm sorry."

"I'm not dead," Harry replied back to the still tiny Sirius. Harry waved his transparent hand and arm through the wards without even feeling a tingle. "Am I?"

"What the hell happened?" Sirius asked stepping back from the ward before he countered the shrinking charm on himself. "You're a ghost!"

"That couldn't have killed me," Harry said frowning. He was poking himself and saw his body reacted normally to his own touch. "There's no way."

Sirius reached forward and his hand passed right through Harry's arm. "You're cold."

Harry stepped towards Sirius and swung his arms through his godfather touching nothing.

Sirius shivered at the sensation. "What did you do? Accidental magic?"

Harry scratched his ghostly head. "I've never heard of anything like this. I mean I was trying to think of ways around the wards and pleading for help. The only thing I could think of was with the animagi ward in front of me-"

Sirius gasped and stepped back.

"What?" Harry said looking down and turning around. "What'd I do now?"

"That's it!" Sirius exclaimed. "That's what… oh this makes perfect sense!"

"What does?"

"You're a ghost!"

"But I never died."

"No, no," Sirius corrected. "You're a ghost! Your animagus form is dead Harry!"

Harry frowned. "That's not a form."

"I told you, you killed your form," Sirius cheered. "That's why the mist was grey and you kept seeing yourself hazy. You're a bloody ghost!"

"But that doesn't…" Harry stopped. "I mean that… I couldn't… My animagus form is a ghost?"

"McGonagall was even talking about magical entities other than animals," Sirius happily continued. "Ghosts are all in-between and that's why you didn't get black or white mist. That's why you were sometimes invisible. Oh this is so freaking cool."

"But I still look like me," Harry pondered.

Sirius shrugged. "You're wearing the same clothes but you look like a ghost to me."

Harry walked right up to the next set of wards and slowly stuck his arm straight through them. "This is sweet! Hardly anyone wards against ghosts."

"Oh come on," Sirius grumbled. "That's cheating."

Harry got down on his hands and knees and submerged his head down into the ground without interference. There was a brief beat before his head came right back up. "That was unpleasant."

"It hurt?"

"No," Harry said shaking his head. "But it looked like dirt mashed up to my eyelids."

"What were you expecting?"

"I'm not sure," Harry said rubbing his ghostly eyes. "But I definitely cannot see through solid objects."

"Why would you think you could?"

Harry frowned. "Well pardon me if I'm not exactly experienced at being a ghost. Can they even pick things up?" Harry asked while trying to grab the grass and ground below him.

Sirius shook his head. "Poltergeists can, but I don't think ghosts can do all that much."

"But I'm sitting on the ground," Harry said. "And I was walking on it earlier."

Sirius shrugged. "Are you sure that's what you were doing?"

Harry jumped to his feet and walked over to Sirius. "Yes, Padfoot, I'm walking on the ground."

"You could just be floating in the way normal Harry would expect to walk. Try and float off the ground," Sirius suggested urging his godson on.

Harry figured it was worth a shot. His face tightened into a look of concentration but nothing was happening. He sighed. He stuck a fist into the air and jumped up, only to land right back on the ground. "Is there a manual for this stuff?"

Sirius grinned as a thought came to him. "Well, you could always ask-"

"OH! MY! GOD!" Harry exclaimed in sheer terror. "Oh crap. Oh Jesus fucking Christ."

"Just remembered her, eh?"

"I swear to all that's fucking holy, Sirius," Harry snapped, stomping right up into the elder man's face. "If you breathe one word of this to Ginny, just one word, I'm carving out your testicles with a melon-baller."

"She's bound to find out eventu-"

"No she isn't!" Harry shouted. "You're not hearing me too clearly. She will NEVER find out about this."

"Harry-"

"NEVER!"

Sirius just started to laugh at Harry.

Harry would catch Sirius' eye and the older man would just laugh harder.

Harry sighed. "She's right behind me, isn't she?"

Sirius just laughed louder at the depressed look of resignation on Harry's face.

Harry slowly turned around. He kept turning until he had gone in a full circle and was back facing Sirius. Harry fell to the ground in a mixture of exhaustion and exultation. He put his hand over his chest. "I think I had a heart attack," Harry opened his eyes in surprise and began to rhythmically push on his chest. "Though I would feel more comforted if I actually had a heartbeat."

Sirius just continued to laugh at Harry and was pointing at him.

"What?" Harry finally asked, thinking Sirius was laughing a bit too heartily.

"You did all the animagus exercises, right? The preliminary study?"

"Yeah," Harry nodded having gone through them with Hermione.

"Alright then," Sirius happily responded. "Tell me, what's the first step towards transformation after you've identified your form?"

"You have to map out the skeletal structure differences and then… musculature…" Harry trailed off and suddenly realized. "Oh."

Sirius started laughing again.

"Ah crud."

Sirius was nodding in mirth.

"None of those exercises are going to help," Harry realized. "My structure is the exact same… I… How the hell do I transform?"

Sirius was still tickled and knew there was one more realization still to come for Harry.

Harry's ghostly form managed to pale even further. He gasped, "How do I change back?"

"There it is," Sirius gleefully announced.

"I might as well be dead," Harry mumbled remembering the horror stories of inexperienced animagi getting stuck in their forms. "And I'm getting hungry."

"Relax Harry," Sirius assured him. "I can fetch Moony and we can reverse it forcefully. I think."

Harry exhaled in relief despite not really breathing. "That's right. You're going to have to teach me that spell. I get the feeling I'm going to need it."

"I could try it on my own," Sirius admitted. "But that's not an easy one-person job, and you're not exactly a weak wizard."

Harry nodded. "Yeah, we'll do that but before we do, you've got some work to finish."

"Aww man," Sirius grumbled. "Now I've got to do everything myself."

"Quit your whining," Harry happily scolded. "There's just one more ward set and it's liftable."

Sirius nodded his assent and brought the ward-jack over to the final inner ward set. He slid it in and began ratcheting it up while Harry walked on into the mid-sized house.

"You could at least keep me company," Sirius muttered.

"I'm scouting ahead," Harry called back. "I can tell you where to go."

Sirius was down on his knees, silently agreeing with Harry but electing not to voice it. He glanced back through the illusionary veil protecting them from outsiders and saw no one had snuck up on them. He laid down on the ground and rolled underneath the final ward set once it was high enough.

He left the ward jimmied up and drew his original wand as he walked up to the front door of the house. "Harry?"

Harry stepped right through the wall to the side of the door. "There's not a lot. But I found something we'll want to take."

"Just one?" Sirius said slipping on an unlocking glove and opening the front door.

"One in particular," Harry corrected. "There may be a few other things worth our time."

"Let's get this over with," Sirius said looking both directions in the sub-standard home they were robbing. "I'm feeling a little vulnerable being the only one between the two of us who can die at the moment."

"Follow me," Harry said leading Sirius towards the back of the home. "There are wards over it that are masked themselves."

Sirius found it humorous that Harry as a ghost still had to walk everywhere. "Are you sure this is the right guy and right place?"

"I had a snake confirm the Dark Mark, and Bellatrix says he's an obedient Death Eater and has been for a couple decades," Harry said pointing over his shoulder. "It's the blank patch of wall here."

Sirius eyes slid right over the area Harry indicated, feeling a strong urge to look elsewhere. "It's just most places we rob are a lot nicer than ours. And this place doesn't feel like the type owned by a lowlife with a vault full of gold to fall back on."

"Well I'm not sure how much in here would be worth fencing anyways," Harry shrugged. "I just want what's back there."

Sirius' line of sight slipped right over the wall again. "Can you at least turn around and point it out?"

Harry shook his head. "Nope, I can't."

Sirius looked at Harry curiously.

"The same protections that are making your eyes slide all over the place work on me too," Harry explained. "But I think I know a way around them."

"I'm listening."

"Turn towards the wall on the right," Harry instructed. "Now walk sideways, keep watching the wall in front of you. Okay… stop."

Sirius stopped and was looking at the wall, knowing he shouldn't turn around yet.

"Wait for my signal. There are some strong befuddlement hexes in here backed with compulsion charms. It wouldn't take much to… get…" Harry said stepping backwards towards the wall. He glanced over his shoulder and was hit by the compulsion. Harry's ghostly form turned and started to walk down the hallway.

"Harry?"

"Yeah?" Harry answered turning around. "What's up?"

Sirius turned just slightly to see a completely oblivious Harry standing at the end of the hallway before whipping his head right back towards the wall in front of him. "You're such an idiot."

"And you're a wanker."

Sirius turned enough so that he could glare at Harry.

"What did I do?" Harry said, glancing to the wall behind Sirius. "You know there's some wards behind you."

"You don't say," Sirius grumbled. "Come on Harry. Think it through."

Harry glanced at Sirius and then saw his vision slide from the warded section of wall. "We're trying to get in there, aren't we?"

"Yes," Sirius exasperatedly agreed.

"And I got hit by its defenses and that's why I'm standing over here," Harry said in dawning realization.

Sirius nodded eagerly.

"I'm coming," Harry said, turning sideways to avoid looking at the wall. He slid over next to Sirius. "I'm good. So what's the plan?"

Sirius resisted the urge to bang his head against the wall. "You came up with the plan. You hadn't gotten around to sharing it with me."

"Well that explains why your panties are in a bunch," Harry said. He looked at the wall where Sirius was staring and began to step backwards. "Let me try something."

"Can you at least tell me what you're doing so I can remind you next time?" Sirius asked without turning around. "Harry? Harry!"

"I'm here," Harry said stepping right behind Sirius. "I got a plan. Might even be the same one as first time, I just can't look at it from this side." He stuck his hand right in front of Sirius' face. "See my hand?"

Sirius flinched at the hand in his face at first but leaned back and looked at Harry's translucent hand. "Yup."

"Get it in your mind and keep it there," Harry said as he began to step backwards. He waited until he was all the way in the wall before he located the hidden shelf. He stuck his hand straight through the wall, sticking out into the hallway while making sure his body stayed inside the wall. "Now Sirius, keep thinking about my hand. Whenever you're ready, you whip around and hit my hand with a blasting curse. Don't think of anything other than my hand, alright?"

Sirius spun around and sent a sharp reducto straight through Harry's hand, blowing away a large chunk of the very near wall.

Harry shrieked and jumped backward at the sudden explosion, but was pleased to see Sirius looking at him through the large hole in the wall.

"You okay?"

Harry nodded while rubbing his eyes. "Man being a ghost is killer on the eyes."

Sirius grinned. "So what do we got in here?" He lifted a few chunks of plaster and wood away revealing a relatively plain box that had been charmed indestructible.

"That's it," Harry said pointing at the box. "That's what makes hitting this place worthwhile."

Sirius opened the box and saw a gold locket with the letter S engraved on it. "Is this magical?"

"Salazar Slytherin's locket?" Harry explained. "Yeah, I'd say so."

Sirius lifted it up to better examine it. "This is Slytherin's?"

Harry nodded.

"Just holding it gives me the heebie-jeebies," Sirius said putting it back in the box, and getting ready to put it in his trunk.

"Don't take the box," Harry stopped him. "I know we can remove most tracers and mask others but this wasn't protected by amateurs."

"Fine," Sirius said pulling out the magic muting ball and slipping the locket into it. "But I'm not leaving here empty-handed."

"There's a closet with clothes about your size," Harry suggested.

"This is not the home of a man with taste," Sirius snootily retorted. "No, I want that," He finished and pointed down the hall.

Harry stepped out from the wall and saw where Sirius was pointing. "That?"

"Yup," Sirius assured him.

"Do you even know what that is?"

"Not exactly," Sirius said. "But it's big. And I want it."

"That's a washer/dryer combo, Padfoot."

"I still want it."

Harry looked at his godfather curiously. "Do you even know what a-"

"Yes," Sirius answered before Harry could finish asking. "When I was a kid and my little brother was still a baby, the nanny would give him fresh sheets from a muggle dryer. They always smelled better and were warmer than magicked ones. As soon as the she left the room, I'd steal his warm sheets and give him my old ones."

Harry looked at Sirius oddly. "That's beautiful, Sirius."

"Little bugger used to cry and cry every time I did it," Sirius explained. "Regulus once told me that was his first memory."

"You were quite the brother."

"Yeah, I went through a bit of bedwetting stage too, so it was a win-win situation."

"How did Regulus win?"

"He didn't," Sirius said with a frown. "I won twice."

"Go shrink your washer/dryer combo," Harry said with a shake of his head. "And do you want to portkey or apparate out of here?"

"Why not just go back the way we came?" Sirius asked as he wiggled the metal appliance taller than him away from the wall.

"Because I don't trust that unknown ward, and we can take the portkey and apparition down from inside."

"Portkey then," Sirius said as he shrunk the machine down. "I can transform and take a portkey."

"Go to Moony's and fetch him," Harry said. "And I'll meet you where we did our scouting from, up the hill."

Sirius finished storing away the washer/dryer combo and began checking the closets and hallways as he walked back towards the front. "You can't do anything as a ghost, can you?"

"To the best of my knowledge ghosts can't apparate or take portkeys," Harry explained in frustration. "And I don't particularly want to walk ten kilometers to a bus station."

Sirius kept looking for plunder as Harry directed him towards the anchor stones for the portkey ward. "Still haven't figured out invisibility or floating?"

Harry shook his head. "I've no clue."

Sirius had quietly brought down the portkey ward and resumed his haphazard search for things to take. He decided there wasn't anything else worth stealing and walked out to retrieve the ward-jack he had left out front. He stuffed everything into the magic muting ball that he transfigured to look like a chew toy. He cast the 'After Dark Mark' just inside the front door before turning a twig into a portkey to the wooded area across the street from Remus' place.

Harry waved at Sirius as he popped into his dog form. "Don't make me wait too long."

Sirius picked up the ball in his mouth and stepped onto the spelled twig, disappearing from Alan Weston's front porch.

Harry continued to try and move solid objects in spite of his incorporeal state but failed. He walked over to where he'd left his wand and was disappointed to see he couldn't do anything with it either.

He felt exposed out in the open and unable to do anything. He quickly walked up the hillside to the spot where he would wait for Sirius and Remus.

Harry sighed hoping against hope that Ginny wouldn't make an appearance before the two older Marauders could arrive. He plopped down onto the ground and leaned back against a young tree.

Harry's back started to itch when he remembered he should not have been able to lean against a tree. Harry's subconscious appeared to be having a laugh and when that thought crossed his mind, he fell backwards through the tree.

Harry leaned up on his elbows and saw the thin trunk was coming out his stomach. "Lovely," he muttered as he laid back down, resigned to waiting.

Harry wasn't sure how long he lay there looking as if he fell from the sky and got skewered by the tree. He'd been trying to think of all the disadvantages of his animagus form when he heard Remus' voice, "What do you think would happen if we cast the spell right now?"

Harry quickly rolled to his side, not even wanting to give them the opportunity. "Don't even joke about that. I'm already dancing a fine line of death here."

"A ghost," Remus said shaking his head. "That's… freaky."

"I didn't even get a girlish shriek or a gasp that I might be dead?" Harry asked dusting himself off out of habit.

"Oh, he shrieked," Sirius happily explained. "We were silenced as we walked up ensuring Moony didn't wake the neighbors."

"That was hardly a shriek," Remus argued.

"Come on," Harry said urging the men on. "Hit me with your best shot. And we can pretend you already cast the fake spell tricking me into thinking I was stuck as a ghost. I broke down, I cried. You laughed at me and are now going to cast the real spell. Go."

Sirius put his hands on his hips. "This is why no one likes you even though we pretend we do."

"Forget it, Padfoot," Remus chided. "Let's just do this and leave the scene of the crime. Please."

Remus and Sirius moved into position and cast the animagus reversal spell at the same time.

Harry stood there and felt the spells connecting with him. He tried to relax and urge the spell on, but his magic was instinctively resisting it. Finally with a bit of push from the two spell-casters, Harry felt momentarily like a balloon pumped past its limit and with a pop was suddenly corporeal again.

"Thanks guys," Harry said, surprised that the transformation hadn't hurt more.

Sirius and Remus dropped their wand arms in exhaustion. Sirius complained, "I don't remember it being that difficult back in school."

Harry still had Sirius' unicorn hair wand and simply summoned his own unicorn hair wand from where he stood, having already confirmed the two outer sets wouldn't trigger. He snagged the wand out of the air as sure as if it were a snitch, and tossed the other wand to Sirius. "You guys okay to apparate?"

"I've been doing all the work tonight," Sirius tiredly complained. "Give us a lift."

Harry saw Remus looked as beat as Sirius and grabbed onto both of them as he apparated to Diagon Alley. The three men quickly walked into the Leaky Cauldron and flooed back to Grimmauld Place.

"I suppose we owe you an explanation," Harry said as Remus dusted the soot off himself.

"Save it for tomorrow," Remus said turning to walk down the hall. "I'm going back to bed."

Harry saw Remus head towards Bellatrix's room and turned to Sirius. "He wasn't at home, was he?"

"Nope," Sirius said. "Didn't you wonder why it took me so long?"

"I figured you were just making me sweat."

Sirius rocked his hand from side to side. "Maybe a little. But it was also because I walked in on Bellatrix extracting the baby batter. You know the Lord stuff is awful useful in this place when it comes to locked doors."

Harry winced at the imagery. "I'm sure Remus was happy about that."

"He was more scared than anything when he noticed me," Sirius happily admitted. "It took him over five minutes to even realize I was there."

Harry blinked at the implications of that innocuous comment. "They didn't notice you?"

"Bellatrix saw me walk in. She waved. I wasn't in any hurry."

"You're a sick man."

"Yes Harry," Sirius agreed. "I am at that."

Harry saw the calm acceptance on Sirius' face. "Can I get that locket?"

"We're not going to sell it tomorrow?"

"Nope," Harry told him. "We can't sell that thing. I'm going to put it behind a Fidelius before I go to bed."

Sirius reached into the storage space and withdrew the locket. He held it out for Harry before pulling it back. "You're going to share the secret, aren't you?"

Harry took the locket and right away sensed the piece of split soul inside it. "Yes, I'll tell you."

"How much you think it's worth?" Sirius asked curiously.

Harry considered telling his godfather the whole truth but did not want to make an issue of opposing Voldemort again, particularly when any discussion of horcruxes would more than likely require mentioning a certain skull. He decided to give Sirius the Dumbledorian truth. "Any founder's object is going to be worth a lot, but this is also a piece of a larger puzzle. And getting them together would be priceless."

"Really," Sirius said. "Maybe we should look for more pieces."

Harry looked away from the locket and at his godfather. "You want to?"

Sirius shrugged. "If they're as valuable as you say, then I wonder why you don't. You know what the other pieces look like or where to find them?"

Harry gave it a moment's thought. "Yeah, I got a few ideas."

"So why don't we?"

"No reason not to," Harry agreed. "But let's take a couple days to rest first."

Bellatrix was so excited she screamed "Yes!" and clapped her hands eagerly for over a minute. She did the spell four more times, with each positive result making her happier than the time before.

She cursed softly the fact that she'd used up all the muggle pregnancy tests she had bought. She'd gone through seven the first day before Harry informed her that perhaps she should wait until she had sex again before peeing on another stick.

She cast the spell again and grinned even wider. She knew things would be easier if she could get into her Lords' good graces, so she was trying to embrace her muggle and werewolf loving side. She decided she'd go buy more muggle pregnancy tests just to be sure.

She was so excited that she scampered down the steps and right out the front door. She did not think to inform her Lords or Kreacher that she leaving. Nor did she consider leaving a note or bother to cast a glamour over herself.

She was simply giddy just thinking about the child forming inside her. She took a left down an alley that was a shortcut to the corner market.

No matter how distracted Bellatrix may have been, she would always recognize the rippling muting shudder of portkey and apparition wards going up around her. She had her wand out and cast an invisible shield as she spun around.

A dark purple spell collided with her shield, shattering it on impact and knocking her backwards off her feet.

Bellatrix immediately covered her midsection thinking of her daughter and put up another shield. Two curses splashed against it, but it held.

She rolled away from a dark red jet of light and put up another shield. She was hurriedly trying to locate all of her attackers or at least get a better idea of how many there were.

She counted two disillusioned blurs and no one behind her.

Two shouts of spells rang out sending two solid spears towards Bellatrix's head and body.

She dove behind a dumpster for cover. Immediately she strengthened the dumpster and charmed it to be mildly resistant to magic. She took a moment to conjure a small puck of dark magic.

"Give up, traitor," a nasal male's voice ordered.

Bellatrix twirled her finger over the rim of the puck and it started to smoke. She peered right around the edge of the dumpster and ducked back as a spell ricocheted off the metal. She slid the puck straight down the alley. The two Death Eaters just stared at the innocuous looking puck sliding between them when it exploded in a flash of light.

They were coated in liquid layer of blood from the modified vampire-hunting spell. The spell was most often used to set a trap for vampires by coating people with blood. And the blood from the spell also had the side effect of slight flesh-eating capabilities.

As soon as the flash exploded, Bellatrix heard two matching screams and jumped to her feet. She began to sprint down the other end of the alley, hoping to get away. Her first step took her straight into the path of a yellow curse. She instinctively snapped another shield into place as quickly as she could. The lung-punching hex shredded her shield and knocked her backwards off her feet again.

She scrambled over to a pair of dustbins and was ducking for cover.

The two blood-covered Death Eaters behind her were approaching rapidly, rejoining the fray.

She was pinned down, unable to do anything but defend. Her shields were slowly but surely weakening, and muted curses were connecting to her extremities. She was staying especially protective of her head and midsection, making sure nothing could damage her pregnancy.

Bellatrix was running out of time and ideas.

Sirius and Harry both stepped out of their bedrooms at the same time. They caught each other's eyes and closed their doors behind them.

"Did you pay attention?" Harry asked softly.

"Yeah," Sirius said. "Blue eyes."

"Blue eyes," Harry warily agreed.

"Brunette."

"Strawberry blonde."

"One sister, she lives in Inverness."

"Only child, grew up in Wales."

"Late thirties, or looking great for forties. No kids, widowed."

"Grad student, mid twenties. Single."

Sirius nodded. "Alright then."

Harry nodded back and opened his bedroom door. "It's safe, Ashley. I killed the spider."

Sirius opened his. "No worries, Caroline. I cleaned up the broken glass."

Caroline came out of the bedroom, looking at Sirius oddly. "You know if you had to hide something, you could've just told me. I'm not your wife and I'm not your mother."

Sirius pulled her close and gave her a loud smacking kiss on the cheek. "As long as we're clear on that."

"I left my number on your bed," Ashley said as she wiggled past Harry.

Harry glanced over and remarked. "It looks like you carved it into the head board."

"Like I said," Ashley said with a saucy grin. "I left my number on your bed. Give me a call some time."

Caroline looked at Ashley curiously. "Do I know you?"

Ashley turned and caught Caroline's eye. "I don't believe so…"

"Sorry," Harry jumped in. "Sirius, this is Ashley. Ashley, this is Sirius. And Caroline, was it?"

"It was," Caroline said nodding at Harry and turning towards the young woman who looked incredibly familiar. "Your name's Ashley, huh."

"Guess you two don't know each other," Sirius happily announced and began to urge Caroline out the door.

Caroline let Sirius push her gently, but she moved out of his way right in front of Ashley. "Your name's Ashley not… Emma, by chance?"

Ashley paled and took a step back. "Who told you that name?"

"For Christ's sake," Sirius muttered as he looked away.

Caroline put her hand up to her mouth in shock. Her eyes started watering as she explained, "It was what I named my baby shortly before the adoption agency took her away."

Ashley whimpered, squeezing her hands together in hope. "You're… you're Jane Austen Doe?"

"Oh Emma," Caroline exclaimed lunging forward to hug the younger woman.

"Oh… Mum," Ashley cried, gripping Caroline tighter.

"Oh Lord," Harry grumbled.

Sirius shouted, "Oh come on!"

"I'm so sorry, Emma," Caroline said in between her sniffles. "I was only thirteen and Daddy was up for re-election. I wasn't ready to raise a child and I just couldn't give them my real name."

"I can't believe I've found you," Ashley said, not wanting to let go. "I spent over two thousand pounds on private investigators trying to locate you."

Sirius was standing next to Harry, who could only gape at the scene. "This is ridiculous," Sirius complained, waving his hand towards the tear-filled reunion. "Do you have any idea the odds on something like this?"

Harry turned to Sirius and looked him straight in the eye. "We've been given a gift, Sirius."

Sirius shook his head in disbelief. "I'm not supposed to long for normal days. That's not me."

"Welcome to my life," Harry asserted having come to terms with these kinds of things happening regularly.

Sirius calmed down and nodded in acceptance. "So what do we do with this gift?"

"We sleep with hot chicks, Sirius," Harry said gripping his godfather's shoulder in commiseration. "We sleep with hot chicks."

Sirius sighed. "If we must."

Harry saw Caroline and Ashley turn away and walk down the stairs arm in arm. "I think we've been forgotten."

Sirius flashed a thumbs up. "Give me ten minutes and they'll be forgotten too."

Harry saw the two women let themselves out and closed the front door behind them. He turned to Sirius, "Did I hear Caroline shout yes and then give you a standing ovation? Impressive."

Sirius shook his head. "I thought that was you."

Harry snapped his fingers. "Remus stayed over, didn't he?"

"Yeah," Sirius said before pausing. "But he had to leave for work real early. That must have been after he left… Oh."

"Oh," Harry said catching on. "You know maybe we should try and teach Moony a few moves. Or get him some numbing creams maybe."

"You up for some lunch?" Sirius asked. "I'll even pay for my half."

"With a sweet offer like that, how can I say no?"

Sirius and Harry walked out the front door, heading for the deli.

"You know I think Remus might be developing feelings for Bellatrix," Harry commented.

Sirius winced, walking in step with Harry. "I wonder if she's even capable of feelings of the good variety."

"I feel like I'm kicking a puppy when I say this," Harry admitted. "But she's really not been that bad."

Sirius rationalized, "He's only developing feelings for her because he didn't have to deal with that psychotic evil bitch killing me and separating me from you and him."

"True," Harry said. "And yeah, I hated her as much as Voldemort for killing you. But I think her boobs also play an important part in why Remus is developing feelings for her."

"Oh yeah," Sirius recalled. "Them. Although, you know, that other night he was spending an awful lot of time on her-"

"Sirius," Harry interrupted looking at him in disgust. He shook his head in disappointment. "Don't spoil it for me. Wait until we get a pensieve."

"Sorry," Sirius said without conviction. He kept walking in step with Harry before stopping suddenly. "Hey Harry?"

Harry belatedly noticed Sirius had stopped and turned around. "Yeah?"

Sirius pointed down the alley. "Is that Bellatrix pinned down in the middle?"

"Looks that way," Harry said calling his wand to his hand and extending half a dozen eager magical arms. "Watch our back, please."

"Gladly," Sirius said. He saw Harry nod at him and the two blood covered individuals closest to them were slammed with bludgeoning charms from Sirius and stunning spells from Harry. Both Death Eaters were down and out for the fight. Sirius turned around and guarded their rear while Harry calmly strolled down the alley towards the other Death Eaters.

Pieces of trash and debris littered throughout the alley ensured Harry had lots of ammunition. Six pieces were floating in formation around the Lords Black, all waiting in anticipation of a spell to deflect.

Harry held his wand firm, but was casting nothing. He just focused on blocking everything and acting confident and unconcerned.

The curses flying towards them began to lessen in number and in lethality. Harry stopped next to where Bellatrix was huddled down, holding a rag to a cut on her forehead. He looked at her curiously. "Do you have anything to say for yourself?"

"Sorry," Bellatrix admitted, feeling inordinately safe at the appearance of her Lords. "I was just so excited I forgot to put on a glamour."

"Excited?" Harry inquired.

Bellatrix nodded happily. "I think I'm pregnant. I was just going to get some muggle tests."

"Congratulations," Harry said while hurling a dustbin into the path of a dark red spell. "Let's hope it doesn't have horns."

Bellatrix sighed and waved airily. "Can we go soon? I'm bleeding. And with child."

"Let me talk to these former associates of yours," Harry said walking past her towards the remaining Death Eaters. "Shouldn't take too long."

There were three Death Eaters all standing their ground from separate positions in the alley. They stopped attempting to curse Harry when it became apparent they weren't going to be able to hit him without changing tactics.

"So you can attack and kill Bellatrix," Harry stated while watching the three Death Eaters. "But you're not supposed to touch me or Sirius? Interesting."

"We're here for her, not you, Lord Black," the man furthest back firmly agreed.

"Hey Sirius?" Harry called out without even turning around. "Anytime you feel like making a pick…"

Sirius sent out a spray of stunning charms towards the man on the left, halfway back.

Harry flung a pair of empty soup cans through the air, smacking into the nearest two Death Eaters and sent stunning charms at the Death Eater on the right.

Two more knocked out simultaneously and the Death Eater in the back knew he was now alone. He tried to apparate away and slammed into an unexpected ward. He staggered backwards at the magical block and Harry swiftly ran up to the wizard.

A few rocks were thrown at the man who was ably defending himself from Harry's projectiles.

"Your arms can't touch me," the Death Eater proudly boasted, showing off an amulet under his robe. "I'm protected from summoning and banishing."

"Is that so?" Harry said walking up confidently. The chain around the Death Eater's neck snapped the amulet floated towards Harry. Another invisible arm grabbed the Death Eater by the throat, lifted him off the ground and slammed him bodily into the wall.

"This thing is kinda nifty," Harry said while inspecting at the amulet. He looked up at the man suspended in air, struggling against a force he couldn't even touch. "What? Don't tell me you're surprised."

Harry grinned dangerously as he got closer to the remaining conscious Death Eater. "You really think I'd need to pull everything out of my bag of tricks," Harry whispered while several different colored spells hovered dangerously around them both. "Just to beat that old bastard you call Master?"

Harry looked over at the green spell floating right up next to him. "That's a killing curse," he explained while it zoomed right up to the Death Eater's face before stopping and dancing over his cheek, never quite touching him.

"But this is a memory charm," Harry said lifting his wand up and incanting, "Obliviate!" Harry stunned the man and left him with just a blank in place of the last few minutes.

The mysteriously floating spells all dissipated into nothingness.

Sirius brought over the other unconscious Death Eaters and commented, "I didn't know you could have that many spells going."

Harry shook his head. "That was all show. Just simple colored light. If those were all the spells they looked like, I'd probably have passed out by now."

"Oh," Sirius said. "Could've fooled me."

"That's the idea," Harry agreed piling the five Death Eaters together. "Always act like you know what you're doing and people will think you do. Where's Bellatrix?"

"I took her home," Sirius said. "But now I have to buy a dozen muggle pregnancy tests."

"And somewhere an angel just got her wings."

"Ha-ha," Sirius grumbled. "You're coming with me. What are you doing with these guys?"

Harry stunned them all again and shrunk them down. He picked them up and slipped them in his pocket. "Considering the aurors haven't come storming in, I'm guessing the Death Eaters warded the area from detection as well."

"Those silly Death Eaters and their silly wards," Sirius said shaking his head. "They didn't even notice when I put up my own apparition and portkey wards."

"Let's just grab some sandwiches when we get the pregnancy tests," Harry suggested.

Sirius was thinking quickly but coming up with nothing. "Dammit. Sandwiches and pregnancy tests. There's a joke here, I know it."

Harry couldn't help but to enjoy his godfather's frustration. "Give it up Sirius."

"No…" Sirius whined. "I… I… I hope I don't get an EPT in my BLT."

"Too late," Harry argued. "It doesn't count."

"Oh come on."

"And it wasn't funny."

"Now you're just talking crazy."

The man was trudging up the path to his modest home. Five days he was gone on the Dark Lord's mission. He knew he was just seat-filling for the sake of looking like a larger and more professional organization during some completely pointless talks with several vampire clans.

As usual, no promises were made but they agreed to revisit the issue in six months.

He was almost to his door when he finally realized what was bothering him. His portkey ward was down and it hadn't been when he left here.

He drew his wand and quietly ran up to the front door. He opened the door and peered in, seeing the last thing he expected to see.

Alan Weston relaxed as he walked fully into his house, staring at the Mark left behind by the Death Eater Bandits. He looked in both directions of his house and saw nothing amiss when he suddenly remembered what was kept here. He ran through his kitchen towards the back hall and saw the giant gaping hole. "Fuck." He looked down the hall and saw his washer/dryer combo was gone too. "You gotta be kiddin' me."

He felt a glimmer of hope when he spotted the charmed box next to several broken pieces of drywall. "Damn," he swore when he opened it and found it empty. He threw the box onto the ground in frustration.

He walked past the empty spot where his laundry machine used to be and right towards the fireplace. He tossed in some floo powder and it flared green. He then tossed in some red-speckled powder and the flames turned from green to a mixture of green and black. He stuck his head in and announced, "We need to talk."

He pulled his head back up and dusted himself off.

Without a sound a man heavily cloaked in black appeared in front of the fireplace. "Welcome back."

"The Death Eater Bandits robbed here," Alan quickly summarized. "The locket's gone."

"You're sure," the man in black questioned.

"Be my guest," Alan waved him towards the hall. "They weren't subtle."

The man gracefully stepped over the wreckage and peered into new hole in the wall. He was looking left and right for any weaknesses as to how it could have been located.

"I thought you said Voldemort himself couldn't get in there," Alan commented.

"He couldn't," the man assured him. "But these are thieves. This is what they do. And it's not as bad as it sounds."

"It isn't?"

The man in black shook his head. "The Death Eater Bandits have been openly mocking the Voldemort's symbol. They are opposed to him. And the fact that they were able to locate the horcrux and steal it, points to the idea that they know what it is."

"But we still lost it," Alan added. "And I lost my dryer too. Savages."

"True, we lost it. But Voldemort didn't gain it. And I doubt he will. The Bandits might even listen to reason if I explained the situation."

Alan agreed and nodded his head. "So what should I tell the Dark Lord about this?"

The man in black walked towards the front of the home, stopping to look at the After Dark Mark. He waved his wand in a silent practiced motion. A web of mist swirled up and around the mark. The mist blurred suddenly and imploded on itself in a small explosion of dust, completely eradicating the magical mark from existence.

"Don't tell him anything," the man instructed. "If he's focusing all his efforts on the Lords Black right now and forgetting about me, all the better."

"He is," Alan stated. "He even called Lord Harry Black 'that fucker' one time causing much confusion for Larson. The resulting conversation looked like an Abbott and Costello routine. Especially if Costello ever cursed Abbott so badly that he bled out his ears and needed three weeks to heal."

"That sounds like him."

Alan just nodded. "Substituting fear for power. On the sheep, it can be effective."

"But it's horrible for marketing. Any other news of note?" the man inquired as he walked out the front door to inspect the wards.

"Nope," Alan informed him. "He's still researching parallel dimensions and worlds beyond the natural one."

The man in black shook his head in disappointment.

"It's been a while since we fed the Ministry anything and it might be worth convincing them that I'm one of their deep cover informants," Alan said with a mocking voice.

"Go ahead and tell them about the vampire meeting," the man in black instructed. "We should keep them thinking that they're accomplishing something."

Alan saw the man in black looking back and forth in surprise. "What is it?"

"Two of them came to this point."

"They spotted your ward?"

"One crossed here, probably animagus, but that still shouldn't be possible for anyone other than the two of us or…" The man trailed off in thought and looked back at the ward. "The other bandit… disappears?"

"He went back?"

"No, neither of them ever went back. They took your portkey ward down and left that way."

"Should I feel shaken and violated that they've broken into my home and shattered my sense of security?"

The man in black looked at him curiously. "Do you? Because if you need a hug, I know a guy."

"No," Alan admitted. "I just wish they hadn't taken my dryer."

The man in black was staring in the spot wondering what the strange echoes of magic he could sense meant.

Alan gave him time to look around before finally asking, "So what do I tell Dumbledore?"

"Do you think anyone else is spying for Dumbledore?"

Alan shrugged. "He knew about the vampire meeting before I told him, but that might have just been whispers in pubs that spread to the wrong ears."

"Maybe," the man in black considered. "Goodness knows Snape is always trying to needle that information out of his old roommates."

"That man has the subtlety of a mountain troll in a shopping mall."

"I think you underestimate trolls," the man in black argued. "For now though, let's err on the side of caution. Tell Dumbledore the results of the vampire meetings and… and… And yeah, go ahead and tell him that the Dark Lord is researching parallel dimensions. That should help your credibility."

"So no one is going to find out I got robbed?"

The man nodded. "No one but us. It gives me some leverage for when I track the Death Eater Bandits down." He saw the look on Alan Weston's face. "Oh get over it. It was a dryer."

Alan was all set to whine about how it was more than just a dryer. "That," he began, only to see the man in black disappear as silently as he arrived.

Alan sighed. "Fucker."

Chapter 23

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Author's Note: Look at that! I got an update in less than two months after the last. Okay, that's not really worth cheering about. But if you want something that is worth cheering about, try this: the hysterectomy went off wonderfully and with the uterus went all of my Mom's cancer. There was a post-op wrinkle with some diabetic gastroparesis, but that's under control now too. Food is being digested, the uncontrollable puking has stopped, all good things. She's doing well, fully capable of taking care of herself. Well, close enough to fully. I still have to help her change light bulbs, take her trash to the dump, and generally lift heavy objects or reach things on the top shelf. But she'll be back in her classroom and teaching again in just over a week.

This also means I really will have most of my free time once again. Hopefully this chapter marks the beginning of regular updates once more. I'm not prepared to promise an update (as I hate when those promises aren't kept), but it's not unreasonable to look for the next chapter in a week or two. Hopefully. All reviews are read and appreciated. Any questions you have, I will try to answer (unless you just want the ending spoiled, no luck there). Big thanks to the folks who help me iron out the rough stuff: IP, Jim, Chuck, Rob, and everyone else. And thanks to everyone for their patience these last few months. Now let's see if we can't finish up this fic in the next few weeks.

Harry and Jimmy walked down the path from Hogwarts silently. Harry wasn't saying anything, and Jimmy was trying his best not to jump in front of Harry and shake the answers out of him.

"Hey Harry?"

"Not now."

Jimmy nodded in understanding and kept quiet for about five seconds. "Can I ask when?"

Harry glanced over and answered, "When we're drunk."

Jimmy frowned. "I'm not sure I-"

"When we're drunk," Harry repeated forcefully.

"Okay," Jimmy agreed. He held his tongue for almost ten seconds this time. "Are you going to obliviate me?"

Harry winced. "The odds of your memory staying intact are better if we're drunk."

"Works for me," Jimmy happily jumped onboard with the drinking plan.

"And if I'm drunk," Harry helpfully added, "the odds are also higher that a memory charm won't stick for long."

"Sounds good," Jimmy agreed, keeping up with Harry's brisk pace.

Harry admitted, "I suppose the same could be said of the odds that I'll memory charm a little too much. Like a year or three."

"That's not so good."

Harry shrugged with a smile as they reached the main street in Hogsmeade. They both slowed down when they spotted Sirius chatting up a couple of ladies in the middle of the village.

"Is that…?"

"Yeah," Harry slowly answered.

As they got closer they saw Sirius was pushing a mentally challenged-looking man with thick bulbous goggles and a red plastic helmet around in a wheelchair.

Harry glanced at Jimmy worriedly. "Sirius is so going to hell."

Jimmy opened his mouth and then closed it. He feebly argued, "There could be a completely rational explanation for that."

Their conversation was interrupted by a sudden exclamation from the helmeted blonde in the wheelchair. "I was born Lucius Malfoy, Junior!"

"Okay," Jimmy conceded. "You're right. Hell it is. But probably a funny hell."

"Lord Black," Harry loudly greeted as he and Jimmy walked up.

"Lord Black," Sirius cheerfully replied.

"Hell-low!" the special needs man shouted.

"Hello," Sirius and the two ladies with him happily echoed back.

"I was born Lucius Malfoy, Junior!"

"Okay," Harry agreed before turning to address his widely smiling godfather. "Sirius?"

Sirius made an exaggerated show of looking at his watch. "You know what? It's probably time I got Squibby back to his secret room at St. Mungo's. You ready to go home, Squibby?"

"Hell-low!" the man bellowed affirmatively.

"It's been a pleasure meeting you Nancy, Sophie," Sirius bid goodbye with a nod. "Say goodbye, Squibby."

"Hell-low!" he said.

"Goodbye, you cutie," the two women said bending down to squeeze the wheelchair bound man's cheek. "Such a heartbreaker you are."

"I was born Lucius Malfoy, Junior!" he shouted as Sirius wheeled him away.

Harry and Jimmy followed behind Sirius, both slightly shocked and impressed by the depth of Sirius' depravity.

They passed by a young girl, running around frantically and sniffling. "Sugarplum? Sugarplum, where are you?"

Once they were around a corner and out of sight, Harry finally asked the question. "Okay, first, wow. And second, what?"

"I told you I'd wait for you in Hogsmeade," Sirius said.

Harry shook his head. "No. You didn't."

"Oh," Sirius frowned pulling the helmet and goggles off the blonde man's head. "I suppose that explains why you were taking so long." Sirius hunched down in front of the patiently sitting man. He spread two fingers and closed his eyelids, releasing a dark control spell. He looked up towards Harry and admitted. "I got a little bored waiting."

Harry and Jimmy merely observed curiously as Sirius reversed the transfiguration on the quietly idle blonde man in the wheelchair, turning him into an adorable golden retriever puppy.

Sirius set the puppy on the ground before shrinking and pocketing the helmet, goggles, and wheelchair. Sirius picked up the puppy and looked it right in the eye. "You did real good."

The puppy responded with several happy licks of Sirius' face.

Harry and Jimmy followed Sirius as he walked back out from the alley.

Sirius lifted the puppy high in the air. "Anybody lose a puppy? Anyone?" Sirius spotted the crying girl down the street, but avoided making eye contact as he yelled louder. "Anyone lose a puppy?"

Harry and Jimmy saw the girl's face explode in joy. "Sugarplum!" she shouted running towards Sirius.

"Does this adorable little furball belong to you?" Sirius said squatting down and holding out the puppy.

"Oh Sugarplum," She yelled grabbing and hugging her doggie around the neck. "Where did you run off to?"

Harry saw Jimmy was as tempted to anwswer as he was.

"And how did you get off your leash? I double-knotted it," the girl questioned her doggie.

Jimmy had to look away and cover his mouth.

"You know," Sirius suggested. "Some puppies behave better and return when called if you don't keep them on a leash at all."

"Woof!" The puppy happily agreed.

The girl turned to Sirius in surprise having forgotten he was there. She lunged forward and hugged Sirius. "Thank you for saving Sugarplum. You're my hero." She let go of Sirius and ran the other way, holding her puppy tight.

Harry and Jimmy stood there quietly as Sirius looked inordinately pleased with himself. "It feels good to be a hero."

Jimmy snorted while Harry turned towards the Hog's Head and grumbled. "Let's get this boy liquored up."

Sirius flashed a thumbs up and hurried to lead the way. "You know Squibby McNosonofmine was the first born of Narcissa, a Black. That makes you Squibby's Lord too."

"Nice subtle name," Harry replied before whispering to Jimmy. Jimmy nodded and said, "So my brother tells me your wand whistles."

Sirius stopped and spun around. "It does not whistle!"

Jimmy glanced at Harry who just mouthed, 'Wait for it.'

Sirius looked at Harry in confusion. "What did you tell…"

Harry saw Sirius had paused. Harry repeated quietly, "Wait for it."

"Hang on a second," Sirius yelped in realization. "Did you say… did you say… wand?"

Harry rolled his eyes. "He's drunk already because a sober Sirius isn't this quick."

"Oi!" Sirius exclaimed before pausing. "I wouldn't be so drunk if you hadn't made me wait so long."

Harry glanced significantly at Sirius before turning back towards the pub at the end of the alley.

"Of course I was sober when I made the decision to wait, so never mind. Brother, huh?" Sirius asked with a grin falling in step next to Jimmy. "Did Harry give in and tell you or did he just mess up and say the wrong thing?"

"I don't mess up," Harry retorted without even turning to face them. "He had the map."

"The Marauder's Map?" Sirius excitedly asked. "I can't believe your old man let you have such an 'evil and dangerous' tool."

"Remus gave it to me," Jimmy answered before narrowing his eyes at Sirius. "How do you know about it?"

"Know about it?" Sirius repeated indignantly. "It's in my handwriting."

Jimmy stopped in sudden realization. He hurried to catch up to the Lord Blacks. "Wait, you're Padfoot? That Sirius Black?" Jimmy jumped in surprise exclaiming loudly, "You're the one who kidnapped my brother!"

Harry spun around and cast a silencing charm on Jimmy. "Okay. You're done talking until we're behind a privacy ward."

Sirius grinned at Jimmy. "And you're way off base."

Harry cast another silencing charm, this time on Sirius. "If I have to stun either of you, it's going to mean a midget detention."

Jimmy shook his head despite having no clue what that meant, only that it sounded unnatural and appeared to have genuinely frightened Sirius.

The two silenced wizards followed Harry into the bar making faces at his back the whole way.

"Hey Gin," Harry asked grabbing her attention. "You got a private room we could borrow for a bit?"

Gin Weasley quickly closed the latest issue of Witches Weekly that she had hidden inside a supply catalog. "Umm…"

Harry saw her blushing and smirked. "What were you reading?"

Gin was not about to admit that she was checking out topless photos of Sirius and Harry from when they were getting healed in front of the Wizengamot. "No private room, but you can go in back and throw up a couple wards."

"Thanks Gin," Harry said and turned towards Sirius and Jimmy. Sirius was watching Jimmy stare dreamily at the woman behind the bar.

Gin flashed a warm smile at the youngest Potter. "Hello James."

Jimmy tried to greet her back but only looked silly mouthing words underneath a silencing charm.

Harry glanced at Jimmy and translated. "He said 'Hi Gin. Your breasts look like a pair of pregnant house elves in that halter top.'"

Jimmy shook his head vigorously and gesturing his innocence.

Harry made a face of confusion at Jimmy. "She Fawkes like a porn star? What the hell does the Headmaster's phoenix have to do with anything?"

Gin groaned as she jerked her thumb towards the back room. "Go in the back. Maybe try and find a sense of humor while you're back there."

Jimmy took a step forward trying to silently apologize to Gin but slipped on a conveniently placed patch of ice. He flipped forward over a stool and slammed his face on the bar with a fleshy splat. Jimmy's mouth was open in a silent scream. An unmistakable whoomph soundaccompanied Jimmy's legs and bottom half lifting off the ground as the charm on the bar top triggered.

Gin winced and thought she saw tears forming in Jimmy's eyes. Sirius who had by then countered his silencing charm, helpfully voiced, "That looked like it hurt."

Harry nodded in certain agreement. "Can we get a bag of ice and a bottle of firewhiskey?"

Gin handed them over towards Harry while Sirius helped Jimmy waddle towards the back.

Sirius canceled the silencing charm on Jimmy and put up some sturdy privacy wards. Harry entered the protected area and saw Jimmy looking at him with a weak smile. "Tonks warned me I should wear a cup around you guys."

"Catch," Harry instructed pretending to chuck the bag of ice towards Jimmy. In truth an invisible hand was carrying it and deftly dodged around Jimmy's attempt to catch the ice. It tapped Jimmy on the nose and hovered just in front of his face.

Jimmy snatched the floating bag of ice and put it on his cheek. "You're mean."

"He is," Sirius agreed, carrying back the three cleanest glasses he could locate. "Very mean."

Jimmy moved the ice from his cheek to his crotch and let out a sigh of relief. "You think maybe Gin didn't notice me hitting my face and getting nutted?"

Harry shook his head sadly. "Kind of doubt it."

"She probably noticed your tears too," Sirius added.

Jimmy indignantly explained, "It was just the fumes in my eyes. I wasn't crying."

"Fumes," Sirius repeated in admiration. "That's a good one."

"I know," Jimmy agreed. "When I was a kid I used the old 'bug-in-the-eye' excuse but no one ever believes that one."

Sirius grumbled at the victorious grin on Harry's face. "Shut it."

Jimmy accepted the floating half-filled glass of firewhiskey and took a sip. He swallowed painfully but managed to keep himself from coughing.

"Extra obliviate juice in yours," Harry said with a wink.

Jimmy looked in his glass and challengingly smirked at Harry. He tipped the glass back and finished off the rest of it in one gulp.

Sirius and Harry saw Jimmy pale for a split second as he dropped the bag of ice. He coughed violently once and his head was surrounded by a fireball. A cloud of smoke dissipated revealing Jimmy's reddened face. The top of his head was smoldering as dark vapors trickled out his nose, ears, and mouth.

The two Lord Blacks shared a look of immense amusement.

"He's such a Potter," Sirius happily exclaimed as Jimmy was patting his hair, stamping out any fire.

"Whoa," Jimmy said as he took a step. "I feel dizzy."

"That can happen," Sirius agreed with a chuckle.

Harry's magical arms grabbed a chair and maneuvered it right behind Jimmy. "Have a seat."

Jimmy nodded gratefully and glanced at the chair behind him. He turned back to Harry and pointed. "You're not gonna move it on me, are you?"

Harry held his hands up, promising not to.

Jimmy bent his knees and sat back in the chair just as it was yanked out from under him. He fell on his bum hard enough to rattle the nearby shelves. "Oh come on," Jimmy complained wondering how he'd managed to get beat up and drunk in a span of minutes.

Sirius cheerfully displayed his wand. "He didn't move it."

"Should have guessed," Jimmy grumbled pulling the chair closer and gripping it tightly as he sat down. "I thought I heard a whistle."

"Hey," Sirius whined, showing his first wand. "This isn't the wand that whistles. This is my old one."

Harry turned to Sirius, holding back his laughter.

"I mean my wand doesn't whi-" Sirius snapped. "Oh, screw you both."

"Hey," Jimmy happily realized. "That'd be incest," he exclaimed waving his hand between Harry and himself.

"Not exactly," Harry corrected.

"But it would be gross," Sirius added.

"What do you mean?" Jimmy asked curiously.

Sirius answered without hesitation. "I know sword-fighting may look manly and all-"

"Not you," Jimmy interrupted. "Harry, what do you mean?"

Harry was slightly curious about what Sirius was going to say but answered, "Your older brother, Harry, died a long time ago. I'm Harry Potter, just a different one."

Jimmy scratched his head in confusion. "Like a cousin?"

Sirius took a drink of his firewhiskey and sighed. "This could take a while."

Gin glanced at her watch and realized it'd been a couple of hours since the three Potters and Blacks took over her store room. "Hey Moe?"

"Yeah?"

"I'm gonna step in the back. Give a shout if anyone comes in, would you?" She heard a grunt of assent from Moe as she stealthily crept down the back hall. The eerie quiet pointed towards silencing charm and she was hoping to avoid interrupting a touching family moment.

She crossed through an outer edge of wards and heard voices snickering and laughing between whispers.

"Shh! Come on, come on. Hurry up, she's coming."

Another snort of amusement was released before a different voice. "I'm almost done."

Gin whipped her head around the corner with a stern frown on her face. Her eyes widened at the sight.

Sirius was capping a magical marker and spun around smiling innocently. The illusion of innocence was broken as he moved out of the way revealing an unconscious seventh year Hogwarts student. Jimmy's head was tilted to the side while a long string of drool connected the corner of his open mouth to his shoulder. He had been stripped down to his boxers and written across his chest was a message: I slept with Gin Weasley and all I got was one lousy memory charm (and a little itching no one can explain).

"Please tell me that's not permanent," Gin said with a tiny sigh.

"That's not permanent," Harry and Sirius happily replied in unison.

She rolled her eyes. "You could make an effort to lie to me, you know."

"You look really pretty in that top," Harry effortlessly lied. "Not even a little skanky."

"Real nice," she grumbled.

"You've lost weight, haven't you?" Sirius added with a waggle of his finger.

"Watch it," Gin warned with a harsh poke of Sirius' shoulder. She grabbed the permanent marker from his hand. A twist of her wand and the drooling prone form of Jimmy Potter floated up and turned around, slumped over his belly on the chair. A slow drip of drool stretched to the floor while he continued to snore.

Gin tugged the waistband of his boxers down and signed her name right across his pale exposed butt cheek. She pulled his drawers back up and smiled at the Lord Blacks. "Adding a touch of authenticity."

Sirius smirked at her. "You just like making the seventh years blush."

"Such is the lonely life of a young gorgeous bartender next to a school full of hormonal teenagers," Gin forlornly explained. She started to walk back to the front of the Hog's Head and added, "If you get him inside the Hogwarts grounds, you can call for Sully. He's a house elf who takes students back to their beds safely and quietly."

Harry picked up Jimmy with a pair of invisible arms while Sirius brought down the rest of wards. The mostly naked slumbering form of the Hogwarts Head Boy missed out on the applause his exit of shame earned him while Harry and Sirius waved good night to Gin.

They paraded Jimmy down the street towards the path to Hogwarts. As soon as they crossed the primary wards, Sirius beckoned, "Sully!"

The house-elf appeared wearing two patchwork oven mitts that had been stitched into a pair of overalls. He used a dirty rag to wipe his forehead before stuffing it in his back pocket. "You called Sully?"

Sirius pointed at Jimmy. "We have-"

"Mm-hmm," Sully interrupted and agreed.

"Gin said-"

"Mm-hmm," Sully reiterated.

"He needs-"

"Mm-hmm, he sure does," Sully agreed.

"Actually," Harry jumped in. "I-"

"Really?" Sully asked looking at Harry curiously.

Harry blinked and began to wonder if this house elf was using Legilimency. "I was going to say-"

"Mm-hmm," Sully replied affirmatively.

"What?" Sirius asked.

"I was just," Harry stopped and non-verbally told Sully to shut up. "I was just thinking that instead of Sully taking Jimmy back up there, perhaps he should ask McGonagall to come down here."

"That's plain mean," Sirius retorted with a smile. "Do it, Sully."

"Mm-hmm," Sully agreed, snapping his fingers and disappearing with a loud pop.

Harry gently dropped Jimmy on his back with his arms and legs spread out. "Come on," Harry said with a jerk of his head. "Let's get back under our own wards and I'll tell you those things I wouldn't before."

Sirius crossed the edge of the Hogwarts' wards before Harry and apparated back to Grimmauld Place. He headed straight for the kitchen as Harry apparated in behind him. "I want some fruity pebbles and you said you'd tell me what you wish you hadn't told Albus."

Harry followed Sirius into the kitchen and poured himself a glass of water. "It's not that I wish I hadn't told him. I wanted to know if he knew about something and he didn't, which meant I inadvertently gave him a pretty big clue. So now he's got some research to do before asking me semi-uncomfortable but inevitable questions."

Sirius took a spoonful of his late night cereal, chewed loudly, and swallowed. "Are you going to keep talking in vague generalizations or are you going to actually explain this thing you've been hiding?" Sirius took another bite of pebbles.

"Sorry," Harry replied. "Force of habit."

"Crappy habit. Understandable, but crappy."

"Yeah," Harry agreed. "Thing is, I asked Dumbledore if he'd heard about horcruxes."

Sirius swallowed the food in his mouth and furrowed his brow. "Those things you, Ron, and Hermione hunted?"

Harry nodded. "How much do you know about horcruxes?"

"Dark evil magic thing, right? Something you had to do before you could face Voldemort. Soul magic, maybe?"

"Close enough. The gist of it is that there's this little bonus ritual thing you can do when you commit a real proper cold-blooded murder. Killing of that kind damages your soul and you can take that split chunk of soul and stick it into an object."

"I'm remembering now," Sirius recalled. "You said something about how as long as one of his objects exists, then he can't be completely killed, only his body destroyed."

"Exactly," Harry agreed and attempted to subtly segue. "Now remember how I said those founders' items were pieces of a larger puzzle?"

"Sure," Sirius answered. "You said… oh god, Harry."

"Yeah?"

"You mean to tell me…"

"Yup."

"The larger puzzle is Voldemort's soul?" Sirius said incredulously. "You're kidding, right?"

"Maybe a little," Harry carefully answered.

"How much?"

"None at all."

Sirius frowned. "How did I not see this?"

"Truthfully?"

"Yes."

"You're not that smart."

"I'm not an idiot," Sirius complained.

"I know. You're a smart guy," Harry happily offered.

"Thank you."

"Just not that smart."

Sirius knew he should have seen that one coming. He thought back to the locket they found and the traps around the Grindelwald zombie. "But you said the pieces together would be more valuable…"

Harry defended, "I think to the right buyer they'd be extremely valuable. Priceless, almost."

"We can't fence the Dark Lord's soul. There's bound to be a rule about that somewhere."

"Has anyone ever tried? I mean just because no one's managed it yet," Harry answered a little too quickly.

"Hang on."

"What? Okay. Yeah. I'm hanging on," Harry resisted the urge to whistle. "And I'm acting perfectly normal too."

"Hang on."

Harry mimed zipping his mouth shut and stood there avoiding Sirius' eyes.

Sirius was trying to pick up on the cause for Harry's continued distress. "What aren't you telling me?"

"Alright," Harry agreed knocking back the rest of his water and wiping his mouth on his sleeve. "Voldemort made six horcruxes because of arithmantic properties of seven. Six separate objects plus him makes seven. We've got Slytherin's locket and Ravenclaw's cube already. The diary I expect is buried in the blood-warded safe at Malfoy Manor, and Hufflepuff's cup is in a cursed tomb in the desert. The Slytherin ring was not where it was supposed to be and we tripped some wards there, if you'll remember."

Sirius nodded and saw Harry was waiting on him. "I count five. What's the sixth?"

"The sixth?" Harry admitted with a sigh. "The sixth in our old world was his familiar, an especially large snake named Nagini."

"It's not Nagini here?"

Harry shook his head. "According to Bella he's never had a familiar, but I think the basilisk from the chamber now lives in the woods behind the Riddle house."

"Comforting thought. So is it the basilisk or do we have no idea what the sixth horcrux is?"

"It's not the basilisk," Harry replied calmly. "I know exactly what the sixth horcrux is but I don't know where to look for it."

"What is it?"

Harry frowned. "You remember that hidden cursed patch of ground and tree at Godric's Hollow where nothing appears to ever grow again?"

"I knew it!" Sirius slammed his hand down happily. "I knew I died a special hero. So he made a horcrux when he killed me?"

"Ah… no," Harry answered with a shake of his head. "You fought back and through some incredible stroke of luck might have even been a threat to him. That's probably not a clean enough murder. And it's nowhere near as cold-blooded as slicing open a defenseless baby."

"He killed you to make the horcrux?" Sirius whined. "Man you get everything."

"Yeah, he killed me," Harry admitted. "But he killed me to turn your skull into a horcrux."

"My skull?" Sirius repeated as if testing out the words. "My skull is a horcrux?"

"Pretty sure, yup."

"I can just imagine him—eurgh," Sirius shuddered. "I feel dirty. Like I can feel him inside me all writhing around…"

"My thoughts exactly. The fact that your skull is horcruxiotic is a lot like Voldemort's having sex with you."

Sirius mentally reviewed his earlier choice of words. "Shut up."

"Are you picturing it too?"

"Stop it," Sirius ordered while banishing all mental images from his mind. He looked at Harry earnestly. "You know this isn't as bad as I first thought."

"The sex with-"

"Not that," Sirius interrupted. "Gathering these horcruxes. I mean as founders' objects they're worth a hefty coin, but knowing what they also are…" Sirius shrugged. "Money, power, fame, we can turn these into just about anything we want."

Harry was considering what Sirius said. "If word were to get out we could use Voldemort to drive the price up."

"We're not selling them to him," Sirius scoffed before uncertainly adding, "Are we?"

Harry shook his head. "You know that and I know that. But our prospective buyers don't need to know that."

Sirius smiled brightly in agreement catching onto the potential of the situation. "You really want to hold the Ministry hostage and name our own price?"

"Not really," Harry said with a smile in return. "But it's definitely something to think about."

Sirius eyes widened as he realized they had a guaranteed 'get out of jail free' card as well as a legitimate defense for their 'necessary' thieving in the unlikely event of their capture. He knew this was one set he definitely wanted completed. "You ready to tackle the Malfoys or are we going to the desert?"

Harry saw Sirius wasn't even fazed and had already gotten back to business. "We still don't know where the skull is or where the ring went. So desert first and then Malfoys. Teleporting fire scorpions are much easier to deal with than a dark wizard with an overdeveloped sense of self-worth."

"Tele-what what?"

"Teleporting fire scorpions. There's lots of fun stuff around the tomb." He paused to scratch his chin. "Then again, the Fidelius hidden bunker was a bit different in this world."

Sirius finished off the last bite of his now soggy cereal. He levitated the bowl to the sink where it began to magically clean itself. He saw Harry looked relaxed. "Were you keeping all that from me because you thought I'd be upset to hear my skull is a horcrux?"

Harry shrugged wondering why he'd been so hesitant.

Sirius pushed off the edge of the counter and walked out of the kitchen. "Merlin, you're such a woman sometimes."

Jimmy let out a whimper of pain as his older sister scrubbed his chest.

"Stay still," Sarah ordered, dipping the scouring brush in the magical solution.

"You're practically grating away my skin, like a hunk of cheese," Jimmy whined. "So excuse me if I'm a little twitchy."

"Merlin, you're such a woman sometimes," Sarah muttered under her breath. "Maybe next time you'll remember not to let pretty girls write on you with permanent magical markers."

"I didn't let anyone-" Jimmy hissed in pain as his sister attacked the last line across his abdomen. "And Gin didn't write this. It was Harry and Sirius having a laugh with me."

"And that makes it better?"

"Well I wouldn't want Gin to take advantage of me while I'm unconscious." Jimmy explained. "She should do it when I'm awake. And I have a camera."

Sarah shook her head thinking both she and Jimmy inherited their perverted side from their mother. "So you'd prefer to think that two unmarried men, who live together, got you drunk and then after you passed out did something that required you to be naked." Sarah paused in her scrubbing. "Okay now I'm jealous."

Jimmy was touching his tender skin and wincing at the rawness. He looked up at the Sarah worriedly. "Have you got the hots for Harry?"

"Aww," Sarah cooed. "Is my little brother scared I'm going to steal his new boyfriend?"

"No," Jimmy snorted and sat up on the couch. "I just uh… I just…"

"Relax," Sarah assured him, dabbing a layer of healing potion over Jimmy's raw chest. "I won't let him write anything embarrassing on me in permanent magical marker."

"Oh good," Jimmy replied. "Because that's exactly what I was worried about. Are we done here?"

Sarah gave his front one last cursory evaluation. "Yeah, that should do it. If it still looks bad in a couple weeks, we can scrape again."

"Thank you," Jimmy said turning around to grab his shirt.

"Hang on," Sarah interjected. "I thought it was only on your front."

"It's not?" Jimmy asked curiously, trying to peer over his shoulder.

Sarah mentally distanced herself and focused on thinking as a healer, not a sister. She carefully tugged at the waistband of her brother's boxers and peeked down. "You say this was done by the Lord Blacks?"

"Yeah," Jimmy answered trying to catch sight of his exposed bum. "Why?"

Sarah summoned a mirror and angled it for her brother. "Because that looks like a woman's handwriting."

Jimmy paled. "Those bastards!"

Sarah lifted up her Chimaera hair brush and shook it. "Shall we take care of this one now too?"

Jimmy frowned deep in thought before reaching a conclusion. "No, I think I'll keep this one for a little while."

Sarah dropped the brush back in the solution and corked the top. "That's just creepy."

"Is that your professional opinion?" Jimmy asked holding up the mirror, checking out his signed cheek.

"Quit staring," Sarah snapped putting away her diagnostic tools. "No potion can fix your pale chicken butt."

"You think if I got a red magical marker and drew a heart around her name…?"

"Even creepier."

"Yeah," Jimmy admitted sadly. "I thought so."

"Mum's coming," Sarah warned as she felt a twinge from the perimeter charm around her private quarters. "Hi Mum."

"Have you seen your brothe-" Lily stopped when she saw her youngest hiding a mirror behind his back. "Jimmy, what are you doing?"

"Why does everyone assume I'm doing something?"

Lily was watching her son slip his shirt back on, looking for other warning signs. "Have your memories returned to you yet?"

"I wasn't obliviated," Jimmy pleaded. "I just… thought I was drinking really bad water and must have had too much. That's all."

"Really bad water, eh?" Sarah asked doubtfully.

"I worry about you," Lily explained. "And I talked to the Headmaster and he's worried too. So we're just going to check you for memory charms."

Jimmy nodded in acceptance as he tugged his shirt away from his body. Every time the cloth just gently touched his raw skin it hurt.

"Come in Headmaster," Sarah called out after the perimeter charm alerted her.

Albus pushed the door open and smiled at the three Potters. "You know when I welcome people from the other side of the door, it's much more impressive."

Jimmy answered without thinking. "That's probably more of a statement on the people at your door."

"James, Jr.!" Lily exclaimed scandalized.

"Indeed," Albus said, his beard twitching in amusement. He tilted his head down to look at the youngest Potter over the top of his glasses. "Do you know why I wish to scan you for memory charms?"

Jimmy nodded and let his irritation shine through. "Because I made a crack about playing the obliviation game. Yes, I remember the discussion and yes, I was just joking. Honestly, there aren't any gaps in my memory. Unless you count the one after the firewhisss… I mean the bad water."

"Nice catch," Sarah jeered.

"Hey Headmaster," Jimmy said while looking at his sister. "Don't you think Sarah and Harry would make a cute couple?"

Lily looked a bit upset at the idea while Albus' face reflected many conflicting emotions. Albus carefully avoided the question and replied, "Why don't we get started on checking your mind?"

Jimmy sat down on the couch as Albus drew his wand. "Go ahead. You're not going to find anything."

"Nothing at all?" Lily asked with a grin.

"You know what I meant," Jimmy grumbled as he felt Albus flittering through his mind, testing memories without actually viewing any of them.

"So Mum," Sarah began seeing Albus and Jimmy were busy. "Have you gotten any bartenders to sign your arse in permanent magical marker lately?"

Lily blinked. "What?"

Jimmy growled at his sister. "Listen, Sarah, when you're old and out of shape, and it seems like no one is willing to talk to you, other than your seventeen pet kneazles, I just want you to know that you can count on me to tell you the truth. You suck."

"Oh dear," Albus softly added as an image flew past.

"Oops," Jimmy answered. "I didn't mean for you to see that."

Lily sighed and looked over at the child who would always be her baby. "Show me your tushy. You can pull your pants down while Albus scans you."

Jimmy wished he'd had a sickle for every time he heard that one. "Now's really not the best time."

Albus paused in his rapid fire scanning to take several long measured breaths. He smiled at Jimmy. "I shall leave it to your discretion whether you wish to turn your head and cough."

"What?" Jimmy asked in confusion.

Albus waved him off. "My humor is lost on the wizard-raised. Suffice it to say muggle-borns have some rather common horror stories."

"What?" Jimmy repeated looking towards his mother for help as the Headmaster resumed his mental scan.

"If you still have a tramp stamp let's just get it off now," Lily explained unabashedly pulling at her son's pants.

"Mum," Jimmy whined, tired of being treated like a child. "I don't have a tramp stamp! That's Sarah!"

"Jimmy!" Sarah shouted in anger.

"Oh please, honey," Lily interrupted looking towards her daughter. "Your father and I have known about your tattoo for years. You still have the materials for removing permanent magical marker?"

"Yes, mum," Sarah agreed bringing over the solution and still moist stiff brush. She handed the covered bowl to her mother. "Why don't I let you have the pleasure of scrubbing this one off?"

Jimmy felt Albus still rifling through his mind as he tried to slap his mother's hands away. "I swear Mum if you don't start treating me like an adult, I'm going to…"

"You're going to what?" Lily asked dangerously with that 'I brought you into this world' tone of voice. "Find someone to write even cruder things on you?"

Albus held up his memory scan to look at the healing solution closer. "Miss Potter? What is that?"

"That's what Madame Pomfrey told me to use," Sarah admitted. "A rejuvenating elixir mixed with a dash of thickening potion. And she said you get best results with a Chimaera hair brush."

Albus glanced at Jimmy with a twinkle in his eye and pity on his face. "I believe Madame Pomfrey meant a Chimaera hairbrush, not a 'Chimaera hair' brush."

Sarah's confidence faltered. "Huh?"

"Chimaera's were created long ago and have physically evolved. They are solitary creatures with the body of a goat, the tail of a dragon, and the head of a lion, a pack animal who's grooming issues are traditionally dealt with by other members of the pack. The Chimaera had to adapt. As a result the scales at the end of a Chimaera's tail evolved magical teeth that can be used for grooming. They are extremely useful for being gentle and firm at the same time, strength without damaging."

"Huh?"

Dumbledore smiled. "A scale with working magical teeth is called a Chimaera's comb or a Chimaera's hairbrush. That," Dumbledore said pointing towards the solution and scrub brush, "appears to be a brush made of Chimaera hair. Which are usually very coarse and I would suspect uncomfortable."

"Oh," Sarah said wincing at the incredulous look her brother was giving her. "Sorry about that. I'm just an apprentice."

"Sorry?" Jimmy squeaked. "Sorry?"

Lily hoped there was no lasting harm done but felt her son deserved it for not going to the proper school nurse. "What do you use a brush of Chimaera hair for?"

"Well, obviously, you could use one to remove permanent marker from skin," Albus offered waving airily towards the indignant Head Boy. "But perhaps the most common use of one would be to sand down the calluses on Giants' feet."

"I think I'm going to be sick," Jimmy said closing his eyes.

"Yeah," Sarah said with a shrug. "That brush didn't look new either."

Albus cheerfully took the conversation in another direction. "I am pleasantly surprised to announce that you do not have any new memory charms on you at all."

"See?" Jimmy said shaking his finger at his mother and Headmaster. "I told you I didn't have any mem-… wait, new? What do you mean new?"

Sarah was never one to pass on a chance to mock her little brother and audibly sighed. "We might as well tell him."

Lily just raised a curious eyebrow.

"Thing is, Jimmy, until that potions accident when you were five… well, you used to be a girl."

"Lies," Jimmy retorted after momentarily entertaining the idea. "All lies."

"You were best the little sister I could've hoped for."

Jimmy shook his head, not rising to the bait.

Albus cleared his throat and added, "I meant 'new' in that I was only searching for signs of recent alterations, the past year or two. The older the charm, the deeper you must scan to locate it. I also couldn't help but notice there didn't appear to be any recent binding oaths or compulsion charms."

Jimmy was getting irritated. "Harry and Sirius are nice guys. They're not abusing me, obliviating me, or touching me in a way that would require a demonstration doll in court, okay?"

"So you are free to speak about anything you wish?" Albus asked giving Jimmy a significant look.

"Yeah," Jimmy said. "I am."

Albus glanced at the two female Potters before inquiring. "And is there anything you have to say?"

Jimmy caught on to what Albus was urging him to do and smiled. "Nope. Sorry, Headmaster. Nothing to say."

Albus just smiled back and nodded in understanding. His smile dropped and he let out a small sigh. "Damn."

"What was that?" Lily asked looking between the two of them curiously.

"Nothing!" Jimmy and Albus both answered immediately.

"Nothing?" Lily repeated with her hands on her hips.

Albus and Jimmy shook their heads negatively.

"Nothing to explain justifying your behavior? Nothing to add at all?"

Jimmy shook his head. "Nope. Oh!" he suddenly recalled. "Except that please, please let's not mention anything to Dad about the firewhiskey? Please?"

"You mean the 'really bad water,' don't you?" Sarah said with a grin.

"Oh yeah," Jimmy admitted. "I kinda gave up on that one, didn't I?"

Lily sat down next to her son. "Too bad, because you had me fooled."

"Really?" Jimmy asked before noticing the look his mother gave him. "Right. I'll shut up now."

"Where are we?" Sirius asked looking around in all directions.

"We're in the middle of the desert," Harry replied. "How much more do you need to know than that?"

Sirius span around in a circle. "It's just sand as far as the eye can see in every direction."

"Surprise," Harry said, mocking Sirius' wonder. He pulled out a timer and floppy hat to protect him from the sun. He put on the hat, set the timer and shoved it back in his pocket.

"How do you know which way to go?" Sirius asked. "I mean we could walk in circles and never even know it."

Harry looked up and pointed. "We need to walk for thirty minutes in that direction."

Sirius squinted towards where Harry indicated. "You're sure?"

Harry nodded and pulled out a bottle of water. He slung his large bag over his shoulder. "Positive. Now let's go."

Sirius put on his newly purchased sunglasses and fell into step with Harry. "Of course our luck would mean we have to walk towards the sun," Sirius grumbled. "How are you so sure this is the right direction? Didn't you say you'd no idea where we were apparating to?"

"Yes."

"So you don't know where we are but you know where we need to go?"

"Yes."

"Are you messing with me like that stuff about why we have to walk and can't use brooms?"

"No."

"So if you don't know where we are, how do you know that's the direction?"

"Because the tomb isn't located in any specific location."

"It moves?"

"Yup."

"So how do you get to a tomb that moves?"

"There are lots of ways. It mainly depends on the magic of the tomb."

"How about this one?"

"This one appears only if you're lost in the Sahara desert."

"Okay."

"And then you have to meet a couple of other requirements. The first of which is that you must walk. No riding in a jeep, no riding on a broom, no riding on a cheetah with a catnip muzzle."

"The magic can check that?"

"The magic can check that. And can you guess what other requirements there are?"

"You gotta walk for thirty minutes."

"That's correct. And I bet you can guess in what direction."

"Okay, now you're just fucking with me."

Harry glanced over at Sirius but kept walking straight towards the sun.

"You're telling me this cursed tomb only appears after you get lost in the desert and then walk towards the sun for thirty minutes?"

"Cruel bastard, ain't he?"

"That's horrible. That's awful. Can't we just wrestle a dragon or something?" Sirius pleaded wiping the sweat from his forehead.

Harry smirked. "If you'd like, that could be arranged too."

Sirius stayed quiet as the pair kept walking towards the sun. He grabbed Harry's bottle of water and took a drink. He tried to hand it back.

"Keep it," Harry said with his eyes focused forward. "I've got more."

Sirius took another drink of water and wondered if this was the longest half hour of his life. "You said there are traps?"

Harry nodded. "Many. You got your gillyweed?"

Sirius looked inside his cloak. "Check."

"Your antidotes and anti-venom pack?"

"Check."

"Your crucifixes and bibles?"

"Check."

"Exactly two and a quarter kilograms of petroleum jelly?"

"Check."

"How many flame-freezing charms have you stored up to trigger wandlessly?"

"You said I'd need at least five. So I layered in twenty, two at a time."

"Excellent. What do you do when you hear the singing?"

"Cover my ears."

"When you see the naked women? Or possibly poodles?"

"Cover my eyes."

"When you cross the underground river filled with candiru?"

Sirius angrily snarled. "I'm going to crispy fry every last one of those motherfuckers."

Harry shrugged. "I was looking for pucker and cover but that works."

A loud beeping began to emanate from Harry's pocket. He pulled out the timer and turned it off. "Okay now, you're going to begin to feel tension inside of you building. Your magic is going to want you to react. Do not cast any magic at all. Just keep walking."

Sirius winced as his magic began to itch.

"Eventually your magic is going to hit a point and react on its own. When that happens, everything will go black and you're gonna fall. You've got about two seconds to cast a cushioning charm, repelling charm, something, or else you're gonna get skewered on bone spikes. Move forward on the ground until you reach a fork in the road and wait. We'll meet up there."

"Harry," Sirius hissed out through clenched teeth.

"Don't cast anything, Padfoot. And don't transform either. No magic!"

"Harry, I thought you should know… I mean, I…"

Harry winced as he kept walking, fighting his own impulse to veer from this path. "Waited until the last moment?"

"Well maybe if you'd let me finish I could-"

"Don't blame this on me. If it was important enough to mention, you should have said something earlier."

"You're unbelievable. This conversation could have been over five times already but you just can't let it go."

"Just say what you wanted to, you ignorant buttnug-"

Then the sand exploded into darkness and swallowed them whole.

Chapter 24

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Author's Note: Took a little longer than I'd hoped, but this chapter is super-sized at over 10,000 words and I had to rewrite several parts. Still was less than two weeks since the last update, so I think I'll stop wasting people's time with unnecessary author's notes now that I'm back into a writing-friendly routine. Big thanks to IP, Rob, Chuck, and everyone else who helped me get this chapter in line. Reviews make the writing muse happy.

"Oh my freakin' head," Sirius muttered as he slowly regained consciousness.

"Sirius?" Harry asked from the foot of his godfather's hospital bed. "Can you hear me?"

"Oh my freakin' ears," Sirius grumbled in discomfort.

"Too loud?" Harry asked softer.

Sirius blearily looked towards Harry's voice. "Oh my freakin' eyes."

"Too bright?"

"No, I just looked at your face."

Healer Armstrong had quickly responded to the summons and entered the private room at St. Mungo's Hospital for Magical Maladies and Injuries. "I see my most deviant patient of the day is finally awake."

"We might need more Skele-gro," Harry grunted. "I think Sirius here lost his funny bone too."

"Oh my freakin' god," Sirius groaned. "That was horrible."

Healer Armstrong glanced at Harry. "I'm inclined to agree with the patient. His sense of humor seems to be functioning quite well." He didn't give Harry a chance to pout, before addressing Sirius. "How are you feeling?"

Unable to resist, Sirius happily replied, "With my fingers for the most part."

"Perhaps I spoke too soon," Healer Armstrong frowned. "We'll have to have that funny bone looked at." His expression quickly turned professional. "Aches and soreness are expected but should be mild. Are you in any pain?"

"Sore, no sharp or specific pain," Sirius said tilting his head. "But I can't move my body at all. What happened?"

"What's the last thing you remember?" Healer Armstrong asked, triggering the memories to come to the fore of Sirius' consciousness.

"Oh sweet Merlin," Sirius' eyes widened remembering their retrieval of the horcrux. "I-mmph."

Sirius' words were muffled as Harry had slapped a hand over Sirius' mouth. "He remembers," Harry assured the healer before berating his godfather. "Sirius, don't say anything stupid. Hippocratic oath protections and all." Harry turned to the healer and innocently added, "Not that I would ever modify anyone's memory without consent or going through the proper Ministry approved procedure."

"Right," Healer Armstrong replied in disbelief.

"Hello?" Sirius loudly interrupted. "Unable to move? Anyone? Anyone?"

"Your legs were severely damaged, Lord Black," the healer explained. "The injuries were serious enough that we were forced to vanish all the bones from your pelvis down and grow them back. The tissue damage varied-"

"Oh god, oh god," Sirius started to panic.

"Your penis is fine," Harry exasperatedly assured him.

Sirius let out a long breath, before a thought crossed his mind. "Wait!"

"Testiculars too."

Sirius sighed in relaxation. "Phew."

Healer Armstrong continued, "The point being that you have to be briefed on your situation before you unknowingly put too much stress on the extremely brittle bones. I will remove the paralysis as long as you don't get out of your bed or do anything that will jeopardize your healing. Sitting up, leaning over, and only the smallest pieces of magic are acceptable but nothing to disturb your legs. Nothing at all."

"I got it. Please, remove the paralysis," Sirius asked. "I need to know that he's okay."

The healer touched his wand to the hospital bed and Sirius' arms sprung free. His upper torso pitched forward as his hand wriggled underneath his hospital gown and headed straight for his crotch. "One of those, one-two… and a half of those. Okay we're good."

"Could you stop touching there?" Harry said snapping Sirius back to reality, after it appeared that the older Lord Black forgot others were in the room.

"Before I forget," Sirius said turning towards Harry. "I figured out how we're going to break into-mmph."

"He must be delirious still," Harry said, halfway smothering his godfather while smiling at the healer. "Could you give us a few minutes?"

Healer Armstrong closed up the folder he was noting his observations in. "Actually, my day ended a few minutes ago. Madame Archer will be here to assist you overnight should you need it. When I return tomorrow morning Lord Black should be ready to try standing again." He turned to Sirius and addressed him sternly. "You are not to attempt putting any weight on your legs. Understood?"

"Mmmph-mmph," Sirius said with a nod, in spite of Harry's hand.

"You have my emergency buzzer," Healer Armstrong nodded goodbye to the Lord Blacks.

Harry removed his hand and tossed up some extra privacy wards. "It's safe to talk."

Sirius huffed. "So you're really, really sure that left is the way to go?"

"It was the way to go. We got the horcrux and we got out. You were the idiot," Harry scolded while wiping the spittle off his licked hand. "And didn't you have something to say?"

"Huh?"

Harry tried repeating Sirius' own words. "Before you forget, you figured out…?"

Sirius blinked. "Huh?"

Harry sat down in the squeaky chair facing Sirius' bed. He assumed Sirius would remember what he meant to say if it was important enough. "Do you not recall when I asked at the start if you had exactly two and a quarter kilograms of petroleum jelly?"

"Yeah," Sirius admitted. "But I figured a quarter is just a rough estimate. It's not an exact amount."

"Why do you think I used the word exactly?"

"You didn't say 'exactly exactly.' You just said 'exactly.' Like it can't be two or two and a half, it's gotta be right around two and a quarter. Roughly."

"Padfoot."

"Maybe if you'd been a little clearer," Sirius gave up his argument when he saw Harry was unconvinced. "So the thing is…?"

"In the place," Harry assured him. "With the other two things."

"Three down," Sirius summarized. "Three to go."

Harry gave in to his curiosity and asked the question that had been bothering him. "So what did you use the petroleum jelly for? Because I know I gave you the right amount."

Sirius snickered in memory. "I coated the entire floor of Moony's bathroom with it while he was in the shower. He grabbed his towel and stepped out of the tub." Sirius was outright laughing by now. "Just slipping and sliding everywhere, arms flailing. He even bruised his tailbone."

Harry shook his head and reminded, "You've had to regrow your tailbone, along with dozens of others."

Sirius paused and broke out a smile. "Still worth it."

"You're an idiot," Harry retorted. "And you took some of my petroleum jelly trying to even yours out. You could've killed me!"

"Yeah," Sirius wiggled as he sat up. "How'd you get us out?"

"I snagged enough of your petroleum jelly to get me to exactly two and a quarter kilograms and then I just powered us the hell out of there. That thing was going to kill you, Sirius."

Sirius winced at the memory. "How was I supposed to know that a freakin' Giant could uproot a tree and start casting with it?"

Harry sighed. "You know we can't tell anyone where we really were."

Sirius nodded. "I know."

"I had to make up a story for the hospital records."

"Oh no."

Harry smiled.

"What did you tell them?"

Harry suppressed his delight and calmly answered, "I merely told them you were experimenting with the effects of love potions on bludgers. That's why I didn't check up on all the pounding sounds until after three hours had passed and your legs looked like a couple of dragon hairballs."

"Vivid visual," Sirius commented, glancing down at his heavily wrapped legs.

"You've been out for four days," Harry explained and pointed towards the counter by the sink. "You got some get well soon cards."

"Four days?" Sirius questioned before remembering they had an appointment. "Jimmy?"

"I met with him," Harry answered.

"And?"

Harry shrugged. "And it went exactly like he said. Dumbledore came down, checked him for memory charms, and found nothing."

"So did you…?"

Harry nodded a little reluctantly. "I obliviated him. There was plenty of residue from Dumbledore's scan to mask the charm."

"Jimmy's right," Sirius added. "Snivellus would've had no qualms about plucking it from his head at any time."

"I know. And with the brotherhood charm, I'll more than likely keep Albus from ever realizing why I don't want him discussing things with Jimmy."

"It's only a few more months until he graduates anyway."

Harry nodded. "But even then, we'll need to decide whether to remove the memory charm or leave it there."

"You think you could let it stay?" Sirius asked. "Because you're acting like some John stole your whoring money."

"I am not," Harry grumbled. "But just for that, I'm going to have sex tonight while you can't even move from your hospital bed."

"You mind doing it in here?" Sirius asked feeling bored with his confinement already.

"Those boundaries that we talked about?"

"Too far?"

Harry smiled mirthlessly. "Yeah."

"Oh that reminds me!" Sirius exclaimed. "I remember what I meant to say earlier. I figured out how we're going to break into Malfoy Manor."

Harry sat up, his attention drawn. "Really?"

"My subconscious has had four days to itself. And I'm brilliant."

"Really?" Harry asked again with more than a touch of doubt.

"It's simple," Sirius grinned. "All we have to do is get Lucius to key me into the wards. And then I can bring them down enough from the inside for you to come play too."

"That's all, huh?" Harry asked. "Just get Lucius to key you into the wards?"

Sirius looked at Harry. "You don't think I could bring them down from the inside?"

"That's not the part I'm skeptical of," Harry replied. "I'm more wondering just how you plan to get Lucius to key you in."

"I'm still ironing out some of the details," Sirius admitted. "You're going to need to be in top acting form and I need to double-check some facts on the history of house elves."

"What?" Harry asked unprepared for that.

"Bellatrix could help in a small role," Sirius mused to himself out loud. "And it'd be nice if Lucius is still clueless of all things American."

Harry couldn't keep up with the random hints Sirius was dropping. "You're not going to give me any details, are you?"

Sirius shook his head. "Not yet. You need to work on how to get into the safe. I'll get us in the door."

"You want me to have the nurse knock you out for a few days? See if your subconscious has any more bright ideas."

"Very funny," Sirius retorted. "You're just jealous of my brilliant subconscious. Which is understandable considering your subconscious is pouting like woman from having to obliviate your semi-brother. You know come to think of it, you've been a lot more willing to accept Jimmy as a little brother than you have his parents as anything."

"No kidding. And just why do you think that is?" Harry retorted staring intently at Sirius.

"Don't kill the messenger," Sirius said holding his hands up in supplication. "I'm just making an innocent observation."

"Speaking of killing the messenger," Harry chuckled weakly. "You know because of your legs healing, you can't have sex for at least three to four weeks."

A horrible, gut-wrenching sound echoed throughout the entire sixth floor of St. Mungo's.

Remus looked down at his shopping list again wondering if he was deciphering the scribbles correctly. "Three tubes of peppermint toothpaste? Milk chocolate or semi-sweet, not dark." He considered if he should read anything into the three exclamation points after 'not dark' before finally translating the last item on the list. "White bread crusts and wheat bread middles?"

Remus turned his cart down the aisle for hair care products and almost didn't believe his eyes. "James?"

James Potter, Assistant Director of the DMLE, had just set a bottle of muggle hair conditioner into his handheld shopping basket when he looked up. "Remus? What are you doing here?"

Remus sensed his friend's nervousness. "I could ask you the same thing."

"I asked first."

Remus held up his two-sided list. "I was doing some shopping."

"I thought you shopped at the market just a few blocks from your place?" James asked curiously while wondering if Remus came alone.

"I do, but they were shut down tonight to refinish the floor." Remus looked into James' basket and saw several fruity smelling conditioners, body wash, and bath salts. "I thought Nappy did most of your shopping."

"She does," James quickly replied. "But obviously she can't go to certain types of stores."

Remus pushed his cart closer to his friend and frowned, jumping to the only conclusion he could imagine. "Be honest with me. Are you cheating on Lily?"

James' eyes nearly bugged out of his head. "Heavens, no! Remus, how could you even think such a thing?"

"Oh good," Remus admitted in relief. "I thought it sounded crazy."

"Almost insultingly so," James agreed, standing up a little straighter.

"Well what am I supposed to think?" Remus defended. "You're nervous, scared, and buying all sorts of woman products."

"They're not woman products," James snapped back. "Men use," he pulled out a small pouch and read, "tangerine rain bath crystals," he looked back up at Remus, "just as much as women do."

Remus was fighting a smile. "James?"

"Alright," James admitted. "That was bad example I grabbed there but it's not all girlie."

Remus reached into James' shopping basket and read the label. "Apple blossom with extra volume."

"Not so loud," James scolded.

Remus smiled as his friend held his shopping basket protectively behind him.

"What?" James asked under the uncomfortable stare.

"Are you going to explain this to me," Remus asked handing him back the apple blossom conditioner. "Or do you just want me to guess when I tell it to everyone we've ever met, ever?"

"You've changed," James earnestly replied, before recognizing the danger of his situation. "And you can't tell anyone about this."

"I haven't changed that much," Remus argued. "And you know I won't say anything if it's that important to you."

"You uncover something I'm obviously trying to hide and immediately turn to jokes and blackmail?" James replied. "No, you've changed and we both know why."

"You do?" Remus asked uncertainly.

James nodded. "Tonks is an adult now, so if you feel the need to act like a kid again because of your immature new best friends," James trailed off and shrugged. "I can think of much worse ways to have a mid-life crisis."

"Mid-life crisis?" Remus repeated indignantly. "You gotta be… Okay, first? Sirius and Harry aren't my new best friends. They're not the ones who got me through school and spend every full moon with me. I like them and trust them, but they know who my best friend is." Remus paused before admitting, "Well okay maybe Sirius would pout and try to argue with me, but Harry would understand better than anyone."

James made a pained face as if he wanted to frown harshly but something was holding him back.

"Listen," Remus said, feeling this conversation was long overdue. "Forget everything you know about Sirius and Harry and think like an auror. Here are two people that Tonks and I know well and trust implicitly. Two people your Uncle Peter likes well enough, Dumbledore trusts enough to have a brotherhood charm with Harry, I know Lily likes them, and your son practically worships them."

"Believe me, I know."

"I'll admit they're not exactly the best role models," Remus conceded in what James considered the understatement of the year. "And while they may go about it in somewhat of an unconventional way, they are doing good things. I mean they're not Death Eaters. Hell, they've caught a few for you and they kicked the Voldemort's arse. They're even pushing muggle-friendly politics from a seat that's traditionally been one of the staunchest supporters of pureblood supremacy."

"I know all this," James tiredly agreed. "Lily gave me a rather similar lecture, though hers featured less profanity."

"Oh," Remus wisely commented. "Well okay."

"It just feels like everyone I know is changing and it's their fault."

Remus stayed quiet, recognizing some truth in James' words. "I think everyone is changing less than you realize. But I also think change can be good."

"Now you sound exactly like my wife," James grumbled. "It's her fault I'm here."

"You're going to try and convince me this stuff is for her? A second ago it was manly."

James shook his head negatively. He looked both ways down the aisle and quietly explained. "It's her fault because she got into one of her moods and ordered me to take an hour long bath to relieve some of the stress that was 'obviously addling my brain.' It's not like I wanted to take a bath but…"

"Relaxing?" Remus asked.

James carefully muffled a snort. "I'm here in the middle of the night buying this junk, aren't I?"

"Good point," Remus agreed holding up his own list.

James didn't recognize the handwriting on the list and looked closer at Remus' cart. "What do you need five jars of pickles and six jars of peanut butter for?"

"Actually five jars of each go together," Remus explained with a grimace. "The sixth is because I obviously need my own jar of peanut butter."

James blinked. "Huh?"

Remus realized this talk was also overdue but he was far more hesitant to have it. "You remember how I said I haven't changed that much?"

"Yeah."

"Well, I'm going to be a dad again soon."

"What?" James gasped. "You're going to be a dad! Remus, I didn't even know you were dating."

"Yeah," Remus winced. "We've only been on a couple of dates and we really can't go anywhere other than the occasional muggle place."

"Muggle?" James repeated. "Did you knock up a muggle? And wait, what about your-?"

"Don't worry," Remus interrupted. "It's going to be a girl. No chance of the curse getting passed on. And no, I wouldn't exactly call her a muggle."

"What would you call her?" James asked curiously.

Remus clenched his eyes shut as he heard a female voice approach him from behind.

"Honey?" Bellatrix called out recognizing Remus' back, unable to see who he was talking to. "Make sure you get creamy and chunky peanut butter. Oh and honey too."

Remus opened his eyes to see the shock on James' face. James just tilted to the side and saw Bellatrix Black come to an abrupt halt.

"Death Eater," James muttered right as Remus answered, "Yes dear."

Bellatrix heard both of them and gulped audibly. "Protect our baby!" she shouted wrapping her arms around her abdomen. She turned around and ran full speed the other way.

Neither James nor Remus made any move as Bellatrix sprinted away and around the edge of the aisle.

James looked at Remus. "Does she-?"

"She thinks you're chasing her," Remus said with a nod.

James still wasn't sure what to make of this but he remembered how Lily acted every time she was pregnant. "Do you need to-?"

"I'd rather not right now," Remus admitted.

James couldn't help but to snigger at his best friend.

"I'm glad I amuse you."

"I'm sorry, Remus," James apologized. He was still in shock that Remus was going to have a baby with Bellatrix Black. "So did you just wake up one morning and say, 'Today, I think I want eggs, toast, and to have a baby with a Death Eater. Maybe some bacon too.'"

Remus noticed James had been subtly changing as well. He grinned as he realized reverting would be a more accurate description. "I kind of got suckered into it," Remus took a moment to ponder his accidental double entendre. "And she's not a Death Eater. In fact, this is why she left them. She wanted to have a child and be free of the Dark Lord's influence."

"With you?" James added the most surprising part.

Remus shrugged. "She swore loyalty to Harry and Sirius and wants them to recognize her child as a Black. They weren't going to knock her up so they tricked me into volunteering."

James stood up straighter, assuming a firmer stance. "Did they force you? Dose you somehow?"

"James," Remus said with a frown.

"Did they?"

"Prongs," Remus meaningfully answered.

James knew Remus never used his old nickname lightly and paused. He sighed. "You've been calling me that quite a bit lately."

"You've deserved it quite a bit lately," Remus replied. He saw his friend was showing genuine concern. "No, of course they didn't dose me or force me. They just… have you seen Bellatrix lately?"

James whistled softly and nodded. "Understood. Well, not really, but if it makes sense to you."

"I don't know what I'm doing," Remus admitted with a shrug. "But I'm kind of happy doing it."

"That part I do understand," James said slapping his friend on the shoulder. "So she's pregnant? I thought her breasts looked fuller than usual."

"Tell me about it," Remus agreed with an appreciative nod. "The wolf in me adores the birthing hips."

"Okay," James replied, thinking the conversation just got weird.

"Bellatrix tells me I've started purring in my sleep."

"I'm officially uncomfortable now," James stated calmly.

"Right," Remus grinned weakly and pointed down the aisle. "I should be…"

"Yeah," James agreed and pointed the other way. "I need to…"

"Good luck with your…" Remus paused unsure how to finish other than with "bath?"

James just waved at Remus as he walked away the other direction.

"Alright," Remus said turning back to his list. "Marshmallows and… snausages? God dammit Sirius what have you been doing to that poor woman?"

"Well," Ginny drew out the word as she wiggled happily in place. "Yes, ghosts can go through the motions of eating, but it doesn't taste right."

"What do you mean?" Harry asked uncomfortably holding the ghost onto his lap.

"That sounds like another question," Ginny said angling her cheek up towards Harry.

Harry maintained his forced smile and leaned forward to kiss Ginny on the cheek.

Ginny giggled in happiness at the small smooch. "It tastes bad. Just unpleasant. But foods more closely related to death and the macabre, like maggots, have a kick. You won't get full or eat for nourishment, but the crunching and wiggling can make for a pleasurable experience."

Harry felt ill at the idea.

"Think of it as exercise for your jaw because consumption simply isn't a part of ghost life," Ginny continued.

"But how do you even chew up the maggots when you can't consciously touch solid objects?"

Ginny wiggled her bum on Harry's lap again. "That's a pretty complicated question. I figure that one's worth at least a shag."

"No," Harry said, reluctantly entering another negotiation.

"Enough over the clothes action to bring me to a-"

"No," Harry interrupted.

"Hmm," Ginny harrumphed. "Fine two kisses and a foot rub. Final offer."

Harry weighed the offer in his head. "Deal."

Ginny closed her eyes, and ever so slightly puckered her lips towards Harry.

Harry ducked left and then right placing chaste kisses on each cheek. "Two kisses," he happily announced lifting Ginny up and depositing her halfway down the couch. Her ghostly feet remained in his lap and he pulled her shoes off. "Start talking."

She held a frown for a split second before grinning brightly in happiness at the thought of her soul mate flirting so playfully. "Ooh," she murmured as Harry started to massage her feet.

Harry frowned as a lump formed in the back of his throat. "Chewing solid objects?"

"Maggots, right," Ginny recalled. "Yeah, the thing about solid objects is that most can't touch them, but there are all kinds of exceptions."

Harry nodded, keeping his head turned so he wouldn't have to watch his shameful hands.

"Some ghosts' reasons for staying behind can include specific items," Ginny explained as her ghostly body hummed in contentment. "Probably the most common are young children with a favorite toy or opening and closing doors."

"Muggleborns who didn't know magic was real and haunt their old homes," Harry offered. "And since their muggle families can't see ghosts…"

"Exactly," Ginny agreed. "Other exceptions are occasionally acquired with age. Like Myrtle can touch almost anything in her bathroom now but I don't think any of the other Hogwarts ghosts have strong affinities."

"I'd wondered why she splashed in her toilet but didn't splash me in the bath," Harry commented.

"Excuse me," Ginny warned dangerously crossing her arms. She was allowing Harry some leeway while he was still acclimating to their relationship, but she was not going to allow another ghost in her territory.

"It was a long time ago," Harry assured her tiredly. "You were a third year. She helped me with the second task of the tournament."

"Doesn't mean you have to keep talking about it," Ginny pouted.

"Sorry."

"Kiss?"

"No," Harry said. "I'm still rubbing your feet because there are more exceptions."

Ginny frowned for a second and burst into another brilliant smile. "Right. The other exceptions are dependent on objects more than the ghosts. Some times of the year or locations like graveyards can factor in. Some artifacts and specific things, like the creepy crawlies chex mix, can be touched. Sometimes it takes a large gathering of ghosts to push the collective afterlife close enough to interact with the living world. And then there are the magics that can affect ghosts. Family manors can be protected by their own legacy this way, traps that ghosts can trigger, magical sealings and defenses."

"I don't suppose you know any of those spells?"

"That's another question," Ginny happily answered sticking her cheek out.

Harry pulled her towards him and sighed as he kissed her quickly.

Ginny giggled and grabbed Harry in a hug.

He considered not allowing her to feel his physical form, but knew he had to play nice. With an awkward pat, he hugged her back.

Ginny squeezed him tighter and replied. "Nope. I don't know any of the spells."

Harry's spirits deflated and he let Ginny fall through his body.

"Sweetie," Ginny begged as her translucent body fell into the couch.

Harry stood to leave the room. "You've used me enough for today."

Ginny floated up looking hopeful and innocent. "Do you feel dirty? Do you, do you need a shower?"

Harry grimaced at the average Gryffindor amount of subtlety. He looked over at the ghost who was deftly avoiding his eyes. "Yeah, okay," Harry conceded without care. "But you're scrubbing my back."

A ghostly squeal was heard as Ginny did a loop in the air and zoomed down the hall towards Harry's bathroom.

Tonks heard the shower running and snuck into Harry's bathroom. She saw Ginny unconsciously rubbing a circle into Harry's back with her gaze firmly fixed on his freakishly pale bum. Tonks' entrance to the bathroom had gone unnoticed and she was feeling mischievous.

The sound of the sliding glass door opening alerted Harry and Ginny to the newcomer.

They stared in surprise as a completely nude, shy Ginny Weasley clasped her hands together, trying to cover her embarrassment. A blush covered her body as she met both the ghost's and young man's eyes. A soft, gentle voice dared to ask, "Mind if I join you?"

Harry wasn't quite sure how to respond but didn't have to as Ginny's gasping breaths made him look over his shoulder.

Ginny stared at the very real and solid human form of her own body. Dozens of her dreams and fantasies were within her grasp. She was hyperventilating happily, gasping as the smile on her face threatened to split her face in half.

Tonks held on tight to her metamorphmagus form but worriedly took a step towards the ghost. "Ginny?"

Ginny just nodded stupidly, breathing faster, and more frantically as her smile started to fade. She couldn't control herself as her eyes rolled up into her head, and the ghost collapsed in a dead faint.

"Huh," Tonks said looking down at the ghost lying on the floor.

"Yeah," Harry agreed.

"You don't think I killed her, did I?" Tonks said, shifting herself back to a blue-haired version of her base form.

"I'm not that lucky," Harry said, rolling the ghost over to the back of the large shower.

Tonks let the water cascade down her naked body, running her hands through her hair, slicking it back and out of her eyes. She flashed a predatory grin at Harry. "Let's see about getting you luckier then."

"Okay," Harry helplessly agreed. "But it could take a lot of work."

"Harry," Tonks said pulling him closer. "I know you've never had a real job-"

"Oi!"

"-but that's really not a lot of work."

"I suppose not," Harry grumbled to himself. "If your part is to lay there like a dead fish."

Tonks was about retort when a pair of invisible hands grabbed her ankles, flipped her upside-down, and held her in place, floating in the gentle shower stream.

Harry spun Tonks slowly in pace, admiring her body and waiting for her to proclaim his greatness.

The blood was rushing to her head, but she still maintained a straight face as she licked her lips and asked, "Got any fish food?"

Harry was still toweling his hair dry when he spotted a pouting Sirius. Knowing exactly what was bothering his godfather, Harry felt he had a duty. "Sex, sex, sex. It's like even when I'm not really in the mood, I figure why not? Let's have some more sex."

Sirius just growled and turned the volume up a notch on the telly.

"Oh I'm sorry, Sirius," Harry said without a drop of sincerity. "How inconsiderate of me. Don't worry about it though. These last two weeks have flown by, I'm sure."

"It's only been eleven days, you," Sirius resisted the urge to use the term wanker. "You orphan."

Harry suppressed his glee. "Really? Eleven? So you're not even halfway done yet?"

Sirius took out his frustration on the remote and pushed really hard changing the channel.

"Whenever they remove your ban, if you need someone to catch you up on the new rules and the rules that have changed, you just let me know."

Sirius just ignored Harry.

"So I had sex this morning," Harry began.

"That's it," Sirius snapped, digging his hand into his pocket. "I told myself I wouldn't do this, but you brought this on yourself." Sirius thrust his hand out with a marble held between his thumb and forefinger. "Bwah!"

Harry hadn't moved but looked at the marble curiously.

"Bwah!" Sirius tried again wiggling the marble. "Bwah?"

Harry sounded like a babysitter that just caught her charge with his hand in the cookie jar. "What are you doing?"

"Nothing?" Sirius said, looking at his apparently faulty marble. "I thought marbles were your greatest fear?"

Harry blinked. "What?"

"I saw that boggart nest attack you." Sirius saw the confusion on Harry's face. "In the tomb? About three rooms before we got to the cup?"

Harry chuckled. "Those weren't marbles, Sirius."

"Well they weren't dementors either," Sirius retorted. "Which is what our old Moony said your boggart turned into."

"It used to turn into a dementor," Harry explained. "But that was more a fear of fear than a fear of the creatures. After I took Voldemort down, I pretty much conquered that one. Now I can't stand the idea of not having any control in my own life."

Sirius thought back to what he'd mistakenly assumed were marbles. "Those were Imperius bubbles?"

"No," Harry replied in confusion. "Those were prophecy spheres. What the hell is an Imperius bubble? And you really thought I was afraid of marbles?"

Sirius shrugged. "Because prophecy spheres is that much better?"

Harry knew he didn't have any defense for that one. "Hey! You were trying to torture me with my worst fear. You're a mean bastard."

Sirius waved Harry off. "I knew you weren't scared of marbles."

"No, you didn't."

"Po-tay-toe, po-tah-toe," Sirius said redirecting the conversation. "So have you just been stepping up your game to rub it in my face?"

"I haven't been stepping up-"

"Nine different girls in eleven days is a significant increase in production for you," Sirius retorted. "Assuming this morning's is another new one."

Tonks was towel drying her own hair and stuck her head in the room. "Am I interrupting?"

"Okay, not a new one," Sirius corrected, addressing Harry. "Still, eight's pretty high."

"Yeah," Harry said waving Tonks over. "About that…"

Sirius let his remote control arm drop and looked at Harry and Tonks curiously.

"Just show him," Harry urged Tonks. "It'll be easier."

Tonks' form shifted into a face and body that Sirius recognized from the day before. She morphed her way through a dozen different forms, half of which Sirius had seen in just the past eleven days.

"No different girls," Harry told him. "It's always been Tonks."

Sirius frowned as Tonks pressed up next to Harry. "But why would you hide that from… oh."

"We're in love," Tonks said with a helpless shrug.

"Yup, love," Harry said especially enthusiastically.

"But… I mean…" Sirius was clearly struggling to deal with this revelation. His face looked like he was about to burst into unhappy tears. "That's great."

Harry visibly relaxed. "I'm so glad you think so. Because I asked Tonks to marry me, and she said yes!"

Sirius whimpered as if he'd been struck.

Harry swung an arm over Tonks' shoulder, pulling her closer. "So much love."

Sirius looked away and finally seemed to accept the situation. "Harry? You know I only care about your happiness, right?"

Tonks mumbled out the corner of her mouth. "There was a 'hap' in there, right?"

Harry ignored Tonks and decided to humor Sirius. "I'll say yes."

"And you know I'd never," Sirius emphatically repeated, "never interfere in your life or tell you how to live, right?"

Harry suspected the truth was not the answer to use here. "Right."

"I forbid this," Sirius said waving his hands wildly at Tonks and Harry. "It's not allowed. Meaningless sex is fine. But sex with meaning? That's, that's, that's not sex at all. It's just… dirty."

"God dammit," Tonks swore pushing away from Harry. She turned to leave the room, cursing Sirius' existence. "One day? You couldn't fake it for one day? This is Harry's happiness."

Sirius was immensely confused. "Huh?"

Harry grinned victoriously as Tonks stalked away. "She thought you'd be able to hold your tongue for at least a day. I bet we wouldn't even finish the conversation. You didn't even give me a chance to ask you to be my Best Man."

"So," Sirius strove for clarification. "So you're not…?"

"In love? Getting married?" Harry repeated with a scoff. "More gullible than the first year Gryffindor Seamus convinced was dating Hermione and that he'd been obliviated by Snape?"

"So the last few days haven't been just Tonks?"

"Eight different, Sirius," Harry assured. "And knowing it would annoy you actually made the sex a little bit better. Tonks is just a very cool girl with apparently too much faith in you."

Sirius snickered at how pissed Tonks had been when she left the room. "What did you bet?"

"Next three meals at Grimmauld Place, she's eating on the floor," Harry explained. "Food in a food bowl, drink in a water bowl, and absolutely no hands or magic at all."

Sirius looked at Harry in disappointment. "You don't bet sexual favors?"

Harry shook his head. "Embarrassment causes more lasting damage."

"True enough," Sirius agreed. "Speaking of lasting damage, Bellatrix sent the letter to Narcissa. You think you're going to be able to handle this?"

Harry nodded. "No sweat. I've got my eyes on the prize. I can hold my tongue and play a role. The only real danger would be an accidental magic killing curse."

Sirius pursed his lips in thought. "Could that happen?"

Harry shrugged. "I doubt it. But he is really annoying."

"Annoying? He's only annoying if you're lucky," Sirius commiserated.

Harry grinned. "I've been working on that actually."

"I'm sorry, I don't believe we've met," Lucius said, dripping with faux sincerity.

"I'm Benjamin Franklin, Lord Malfoy," the severely hunched over and heavily disguised Harry said extending his hand.

"Salutations, Mr. Franklin," Lucius replied shaking hands with a distasteful look on his face.

"Are you familiar with the unfortunate situation that has led me to you, Lord Malfoy?"

Lucius shook his head, watching the aged wizard in front of him for signs of treachery.

"Brighton," Harry exclaimed with a rasping cough. "The elf that has served my family since before I was born is perilously close to earning his permanent retirement, if you will."

Lucius looked at the perfectly stoic and proud standing elf behind Harry. "It looks healthy."

"That's not Brighton," Harry explained. "That's Kreacher. I asked Brighton to pick and train his successor. Kreacher here was purchased a couple weeks ago from the Lords Black. Are you familiar with them?"

Lucius' lips curled in disgust. "A pair of more worthless people would be hard to find."

Harry broke into an exaggerated and guttural laugh. "You won't hear any argument from me. They felt it was wrong owning the creatures and wanted to get rid of theirs. Even made me swear not to beat the little fucker. I should have suspected something with the price so low, but as it turns out, Kreacher here is hereditary bound to the Black line."

"I fail to see why you're wasting my time," Lucius said in mild irritation.

"I have no use for an elf born and bred for another family. His spawn will also be inclined to serve the Blacks. The Lords Black refused to take him back. Bellatrix Black was difficult to locate, but she replied negatively to my letter. She appears to only take orders from her Lords, but she did suggest her sister was married to you Lord Malfoy, a family name I knew well."

"You're trying to sell me your elf?" Lucius clarified. "I have one already and am not inclined to give to charity that dirties my front door."

"I understand, Lord Malfoy, I really do," Harry said. "And I'm not looking to sell you Kreacher. I was hoping to trade Kreacher for another able house elf as my family still needs an elf."

"Why should I do this favor for you?" Lucius inquired. "My current elf is a faithful and able servant."

Harry had a strong feeling that he doubted that but kept piling it on. "Kreacher here is most useful to those of Black descent. If you and I cannot reach an accord, then I'm requesting your permission to take this offer to your heir, Draco. I always approach the Lord first, and given who the elf's previous owners were, perhaps this elf is of… special value to you."

Lucius blinked, only then realizing the elf may very well contain the secrets of the Lord Blacks.

"I care not for its past, Lord Malfoy," Harry said with a happy snarl. "I just need an elf that can serve my family." He saw he had hooked Lucius and needed to reel him in. "I realize trading elves would be doing me a favor and can offer Kreacher and five hundred galleons for a healthy, unattached elf."

"Make it a thousand galleons and we can do business."

Harry stared at Lucius for a long time, contemplating whether to haggle over the price before remembering how much stature mattered to Lucius. "A thousand is acceptable, Lord Malfoy."

"Dobby!" Lucius beckoned.

A sharp crack announced the arrival of the elf. Dobby turned towards Harry curiously before looking back at Lucius. "Master?"

"Fetch me a piece of clothing," Lucius ordered without even looking down at the elf.

"Your elf is uncollared?" Harry questioned as Dobby disappeared momentarily. "You allow the creature to think for itself?"

"I don't need a collar to keep my elf from thinking for itself," Lucius snapped, desperate not to show his ignorance.

Harry conjured a piece of string and tied it like a leash over Kreacher. "I assumed we'd simply trade elves without releasing them from their collars, but I refuse to include a Kovnott collar with Kreacher and receive none in return."

"Keep your collar then," Lucius instructed as Dobby reappeared with a sweaty headband.

Dobby saw the collar around Kreacher's neck and gasped.

Lucius saw the motion and kicked Dobby down the few stairs at the door. "That'll be your collar soon enough, elf."

Dobby pleaded with Lucius. "Dobby is sorry! Dobby promises to serve Master well."

Lucius held up the headband Dobby had brought him and grinned at the creature's fear. "I'm not going to be your Master."

Dobby whimpered as he turned towards Harry.

Harry unsnapped the collar from Kreacher and held tightly onto the string. Kreacher exploded in a flurry of action, trying to run away, choking himself against the leash.

Harry yanked on his string and ripped Kreacher through the air falling to the ground in front of him. Harry leaned down into the elf's face and shouted loud enough to scare all the birds in the area away. "Behave!"

Kreacher was struggling in place and twitchy. A polar opposite from the cool, calm, and collected elf he had been with the collar on.

Harry pulled out a glove from his pocket and held up the string tied around Kreacher's neck. "I am ready. Any last commands you wish to give Dobby before the transfer of ownership?"

Lucius was suddenly having doubts about Kreacher's ability to serve. "Your elf is rabid. How do you expect that thing to replace my elf?"

Harry put a foot on Kreacher pushing him down while he pulled the string around his neck taut. "An elf is an elf, Lord Malfoy. I do not know how it is done around here, but all respectable families in America keep their elves collared. Your elf even recognizes the significance."

"Yes," Lucius commented, trying to reaffirm control of this deal. "Why is it that he recognizes that collar?"

"You could ask him," Harry suggested, resisting the urge to really antagonize Lucius.

"I do not want a history lesson from an elf," Lucius snapped. "I was asking you, Mister Franklin." He added the emphasis to remind the other man of his place.

"Of course, Lord Malfoy," Harry agreed. "Kovnott collars were how the creatures were first tamed and sold as objects from the goblins that created them. The collars made them into completely subservient but highly magical beings and protectors. It was only after they were sufficiently tamed that the older and less useful creatures traded in their collars and received clothes. All of today's house elves descend from the unworthy and incapable elves. The warrior elves served until they died in battle, while the house elves retired to menial labor."

Lucius sneered at Dobby, who obediently stood there with his head down.

Harry continued to do what he called 'pulling a Hermione' by piling on more information than necessary. "Millennia ago, when house elves were all that remained of the goblins' creation, Kovnott collars were worth a hundred house elves. But when Hogwarts was founded and the concept of a wizard lessened, the creatures became a status symbol of history. The value of a single elf continued to grow-"

"I asked for an answer, not a lecture," Lucius interrupted.

"My apologies, Lord Malfoy," Harry said with a bowed head.

"Why is the collar so important to you then?"

Harry fought the urge to smile and explained, "Because, Lord Malfoy, a collared elf can be spelled into the family manor's magics. Within the home, the Master of the manor has full control over the elf though usually the manor keeps the elf aware of all the manor's needs. Disobedience is handled by the collar, and in the event of a betrayal or the Master's wish, the collar will cleanly behead the elf instantaneously."

Dobby whimpered at the explanation and Harry felt like hugging him.

"In the case of hereditary bound elves," Harry said with a nod towards Kreacher, "The collar will immediately enslave and bring the next elf in line into service. For that reason alone, I would advise you to locate a Kovnott collar for Kreacher."

Lucius had reached a decision. "No. The deal is off unless you include the collar."

"Lord Malfoy," Harry snapped. "This collar is worth as much as the elf and I will not trade a collared elf for an uncollared one. Let alone give you an additional thousand galleons."

"Another negotiation, then?" Lucius smirked. "How much?"

"The collar on its own is worth almost seven thousand galleons," Harry stated as he snapped it back around Kreacher's neck. The elf stood up obediently and calmly waited by Harry's side. "By the terms of our previous agreement, I'm willing to take your elf and six thousand galleons for Kreacher and the collar."

"I'll give you one thousand," Lucius countered.

"One thousand?" Harry said shaking his head. "Five thousand is more than generous, even for a Lord."

"In that case my answer is no," Lucius added. "You may not approach my heir with your offer."

Harry sighed. "I'm sorry, Lord Malfoy, but I'm better off selling Kreacher to someone else interested in the Lord Blacks' secrets and just purchasing a new elf. My apologies for wasting your time."

Harry turned to walk away and feared he might have made a colossal mistake.

"Three thousand galleons and that's my final offer," Lucius called out as the man began to lead his elf away.

"Three thousand?" Harry repeated, turning around. "I could still probably make more, but you would spare me the effort of finding an elf for sale."

"Not a knut over three thousand," Lucius insisted. "And the offer only stands for another minute."

Harry wobbled his hunched form over and looked right into Dobby's eyes. "This elf will behave properly until I can purchase another collar?"

Lucius kicked Dobby in the back and assured. "He's behaved this long without one but if you are unable to handle a house elf…"

Dobby got back up to his feet and stared at Harry. "Dobby needs no collar to know how to be a good elf. Dobby is a good elf."

Harry grinned at Dobby before looking up at Lucius. "We have an accord."

Lucius held out the headband signifying ownership of Dobby. "Let's finish this. We have wasted enough of my time as it is."

Harry accepted the headband and handed the glove symbolizing Kreacher to Lucius. "Agreed." A flash of magic permeated through the air and Kreacher and Dobby both felt the pull of new Masters. "Now there's only the matter of the money."

Lucius reached inside his robe and withdrew a leather pocketbook. He proceeded to scribble out a bank draft for three thousand galleons.

Harry bound Dobby to him, as the elf accepted the magic from his new Master. "Thank you, Lord Malfoy," Harry said accepting the slip of paper stamped with the Malfoy seal. "Do you need any help binding Kreacher to your manor?"

"No, Mr. Franklin," Lucius snidely remarked. "If I need any help, I'll look it up. But if I need a lecture… well, I'd probably find someone more attractive than you to give it. Good day."

Harry watched Lucius order Kreacher inside and followed after the elf.

"What a dick," Harry grumbled. "Follow me, Dobby."

They walked outside the manor grounds, and once they were far enough they apparated away.

Dobby appeared in the middle of Grimmauld Place next to Harry and looked around curiously. "This is the Noble and Most Ancient House of Black," Dobby commented looking up at Harry curiously.

"It is," Harry agreed. "And I've got an offer for you." Harry held up the headband. "If you want this, it's yours."

"Master just got Dobby," Dobby noted. "Master wishes to free Dobby?"

"Not particularly," Harry said. "But I'm giving you the option for freedom. It'll come with a small memory charm, but if you wanted you could go to Hogwarts and work there. I bet you could even talk the Headmaster into paying you to work for him."

"Master knows how to memory charm house elves?" Dobby asked doubtfully.

Harry nodded. "I do."

Dobby frowned and then smiled. "Master must be a very good Master for a house elf to have taught Master that."

Harry grinned knowing that the knowledge couldn't be passed on to others. It was something only a house elf could give a person. "He was a very remarkable house elf and I'd love to tell you about him, but not if you'd rather freedom. My secrets are too important to risk."

"Master memory charmed Kreacher!" Dobby exclaimed in surprise.

Harry shrugged. "He still remembers his name and being born."

Dobby frowned warily. "But why?"

"Sorry. I can't answer that and then later give you this," Harry said shaking the headband.

"Dobby knows," Dobby said. "Dobby is a good house elf and will serve good Master. But Dobby is wondering who taught Master to memory charm house elves."

Harry pulled off the medallion Sirius had given him and his proper appearance returned. "Feel free to call me Harry or Master or whatever the hell you want. I really don't care. And since you asked, I'll tell you that it was an extremely brave elf named Dobby that taught me how to memory charm house elves."

"Dobby did?" Dobby asked in awe.

"Not you, not exactly," Harry added. "A different elf named Dobby though it was kind of you."

"That's what Dobby said," Dobby clarified. "Dobby said Dobby did."

"Right, I just… I mean…" Harry sighed. "This could get confusing real quick."

"Dobby doesn't mind if Master pretends Dobby is Dobby. Dobby doubts Dobby minds either if Dobby is a good elf. Dobby is a good elf," Dobby rattled off with a grin.

"Right," Harry uncertainly agreed. "Maybe I should explain this and Dobby should stay quiet."

"Dobby is here?" Dobby asked looking around. "Dobby is confused."

Harry was starting to remember why he offered Dobby freedom in the first place.

Harry still wasn't sure if Dobby understood it, but the elf was eager to help him gather his gear. Sirius and Harry had already spent 68 hundred galleons on the Kovnott collar they jinxed and another 15 thousand galleons to buy a special acid.

To utilize the full power of the collar, Lucius needed to key the collar into the wards as opposed to the keying in the elf. The stronger the manor wards, the stronger the connection. The success of the evening's work hinged on whether Lucius had located accurate instructions.

Sirius had been put into an enchanted sleep, set to wear off after eighteen hours. He was then transfigured into one of the jewels encrusted on the collar. When the sleep enchantment wore off around three in the morning, Sirius would transform into his dog form, reversing the transfiguration on him. Then he had to prepare for Harry's arrival, knowing he'd be apparating to him at the proper time.

Harry nodded at Dobby and covered himself in an invisibility cloak. His watch beeped once, indicating 3:30 A.M. and with a soft pop he apparated straight to Sirius' side.

Harry saw Sirius pouring magic into a keystone and whipped his cloak off. "I'm here."

"Oh thank Merlin," Sirius said letting his magic relax. "I couldn't actively change the wards without drawing attention, but I figured if I just held them open without changing anything you could power through."

Harry looked at the stunned and unmoving Kreacher on the floor. "You realize the sort of life we're condemning Kreacher…" Harry trailed off at the look Sirius was giving him and proceeded to obliviate the last half hour from the elf. "Right. Never mind. So what's the status on Malfoy?"

"We gotta stay quiet," Sirius said accepting his backpack from Harry. "Lucius and Narcissa are asleep and both wearing Malfoy rings, so no direct magic on them. I thought about silencing their bedroom door, but figured it might be a risk."

"Shit," Harry swore. "As much as I'd like to ransack the place, let's just hit drawing room floor and blood-warded safe."

"Alright," Sirius agreed. "But I'm still going to crap on their carpet."

Harry nodded and the pair stealthily made their way through Malfoy manor and towards the drawing room.

"Did you bring the stuff for a Fidelius?"

"I've always got stuff for one," Harry said. "But I'm not keyed into the wards. So the best I can do is just a chunk in the middle of the room. And more than likely he will feel that."

"You think we can do this quiet enough for three hours or however long the acid takes?"

Harry saw how energized Sirius was and how vulnerable they'd be for a long time. "Good point. Go take your crap real quick, because once the Fidelius is up, we're not crossing it."

Sirius nodded and walked down to the middle of the hall and squatted.

Harry put the finishing touches on the anchor stone placement. "I thought you were going to transform?"

"I didn't want dog shit on his floor," Sirius explained. "I wanted people shit."

"Well are you done?" Harry asked. "Because you know he's probably going to wake up."

"Let's do it," Sirius said hopping inside the small warded square.

Harry quickly flooded the stones with magic and sealed the charm, locking them in. "That'll hold," he said in exhaustion before noticing Sirius had already pulled out the first bottle of acid. "Be careful with that."

"I know," Sirius said. He'd rolled the carpet over and revealed the large floor safe and door on top. "This stupid thing better be in here."

"Whatever's in here is ours," Harry assured him. "And is important enough to the Malfoys to keep in a safe. But it'll be here."

Sirius took out one of the glimmering mesh balls and handed the other to Harry. "Start your scrubbing."

Harry dropped to his knees next to Sirius. Together the pair of them rubbed the shine off the large empty front of the door, below the Malfoy crest. They couldn't use magic, and had enlisted the help of the Weasley twins in creating what they called diamond wool. It was similar to steel wool but with a little more kick. Fred and George only knew it had to be completely non-magical, even if manipulating the materials to make it was a magical process. Any magic on the safe and they wouldn't be able to get in.

They'd only been scrubbing for a couple of minutes before they saw Lucius Malfoy running down the hall with his wand up.

They glanced at each other and went back to their scrubbing, this time a little quieter than before.

"What is it?" Narcissa called out as she pulled her night robe tighter. She saw her husband crouched down to something. "Did someone… defecate?"

Lucius looked up and around, his eyes passing right over the Fidelius protected square without pause. "Something's going on."

"Has someone broken in?" she asked.

"No," Lucius replied. "No intruders at least."

"If you don't know what, then it was probably an ally passing the Dark Lord's wards to the public areas."

"Those triggering don't even wake me," Lucius retorted. "This was something different." Lucius sniffed the air as he got a nose full of the present left in the hallway. "Something personal."

Narcissa rolled her eyes and turned away from her husband. "You probably just upset Draco again. I'm going back to bed."

Lucius was still sitting there musing over what had happened. "Kreacher!"

The elf appeared with a pop. "Master?"

"Clean this up," Lucius ordered.

Lucius stalked by the entrance to the drawing room and continued right on past.

Kreacher could be heard mumbling in the distance. "Bad Master, bad."

Sirius and Harry's arms were burning and Harry let up his furious scrubbing. "That might be enough."

Sirius carefully pulled his hand back, and looked at all the small cuts from the diamond wool. "It better be."

Harry leaned down and blew the stone dust and shavings away from a central circle, about a half meter in diameter.

Together the pair of Lord Blacks, each took a bottle of the acid and began to trace the edge of the hole they were making. It sizzled and steamed on contact but was clearly eating away at the obsidian.

"You're sure this is going to work?" Sirius asked vanishing the steam collecting inside the Fidelius charm.

"It should," Harry explained. "The magic of the safe is never tampered with. We just destroy the physical aspects of it, leaving the magic intact."

"And the gloves and sheets?"

"The magic muting gloves allow us to reach in, wrap the items in the sheets, and lift the wrapped items through the physical hole."

"It sounds like it will work," Sirius said drizzling more acid along his lines. "I just find it hard to believe you managed to crack a safe that's been considered uncrackable for centuries."

Harry was layering in the acid and vanishing steam periodically. "Says the man whose subconscious came up with a plan where he was the stud on a house elf's collar?"

"Yeah," Sirius agreed. "But I'm a genius."

"No," Harry retorted knowing they were going to be applying acid for a couple of hours. "I'm a genius." And just like that the game was afoot to see who had the stamina to out-annoy the other.

Somehow in the midst of their marathon game, they managed to discuss Dobby and Kreacher, Quidditch, Remus and Bellatrix, Tonks, the Potters, life, love and happiness.

"My genius is so thick and meaty," Sirius argued. "Female kelpies-"

"Stop!" Harry cried out. He remembered he was supposed to be quiet and whispered harshly. "Stop!"

"You recognize my genius?" Sirius clarified, lifting his nearly empty acid bottle.

"No," Harry explained and pointed down. "We're through. You're dripping acid on our goodies now."

"Shit," Sirius said placing the acid to the side. He slipped on one of the extra long special gloves. Just in time to see Harry punch hard on the remaining chunk of wall that hadn't been eaten through.

"Oww," Harry yelped pulling his hand back.

Sirius moved into place and using his gloved arm punched in the same place Harry did. "Oww."

The remaining pieces of obsidian bent inwards in a way that normal stone could never bend.

Harry grabbed a large cloth of magic muting material and stuck his arm as far in as he safely could. He grabbed onto a stack of ledgers and wrapped them up in the cloth. He slowly extracted the tightly wound objects pulled them through the active magical protections of the safe. "See? I'm a genius."

Sirius accepted the bundle and unwrapped the magic muting cloth. He quickly flipped through the stack of documents and personal books. "There's no diary here."

"Stuff that in your bag. We're taking everything from this safe," Harry said, having spotted the diary and reaching for it. He grabbed an extra magic muting cloth and wrapped it around his upper arm, so he could reach deeper into the safe. "Got it."

Harry slowly withdrew diary, wrapped in another magic muting cloth. He handed the diary to Sirius and grabbed all the rest of the cloths. "Let me clear the rest of this out. You bag it up."

Sirius nodded, carefully revealing the book, doing his best to not physically touch the horcrux.

Harry had a system going of just loosely wrapping, extracting, and dumping items on the floor. Harry saw Sirius staring at the open diary. "Don't start writing in that thing. We can play with it later."

"Harry," Sirius weakly said interrupting Harry's pattern. "Harry, I think you better take a look at this."

Harry reassessed their surroundings knowing they hadn't seen Lucius in a while. He took the diary from Sirius and realized he felt not a drop of magic from the thing. The pages were yellowed indicating its age, but a clearly newer fresh piece of parchment was stuck on top. It had been spelled so that only certain people could read it. The most damning part was that the letter had been spelled specifically for Harry and Sirius.

Dear Sirs,

Do you prefer Death Eater Bandits or the Lords Black?

I suspect I've caught your attention enough that you don't care how I refer to you but I do hope we can become allies. Or at the least avoid becoming enemies.

I know what you were expecting this to be, just like I know why you broke into Alan Weston's home. I've been wondering just what other places and treasures you have uncovered.

We need to discuss this in person. There is a hidden cellar underneath the Shrieking Shack between Hogwarts and Hogsmeade. Men of your talents should have no problem getting in there. I'll know when you arrive and will meet you there within an hour.

Harry glanced up at Sirius who was looking very pale. "Fuck."

Chapter 25

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

"Shouldn't we be hightailing it the fuck out of here, right about now?"

"Hang on," Harry said reading through the note again. "Let's think this through."

Sirius didn't have Harry's patience. "How about this? Someone knows way too much and we're sitting in the middle of the Malfoy fucking Manor. Let's think this through at home instead."

"Keep your panties on, Padfoot," Harry chided. "We're under a Fidelius. We're safe for the moment."

"We've got an hour to walk into what we both know is a trap," Sirius argued.

"No, we don't," Harry replied with certainty. "The hour referred to an hour after reaching the Shrieking Shack. No, the person who left this note didn't know when we'd be here." Harry was still thinking through the situation. He looked closer at massive ruby brooch in the pile of plunder. "And they seem to not care that we're robbing Malfoy."

"Malfoy thinks this is the real diary," Sirius added before settling in quiet contemplation as well. "You think this is That Fucker?"

Harry intermittently winced and frowned. "It doesn't matter if this mystery fucker is that particular fucker or just some other fucker."

"Fuck," Sirius added.

"It's… curious," Harry mused. "This note feels more like a courtesy than a threat."

"You think maybe it's another thief?"

Harry shook his head in consternation. "I don't know. He calls us the Lords Black, so if he wanted to blackmail us, he could've gotten a hold of us in many much easier ways. And how the hell does he know about the horcruxes?"

"Could he have wanted us here? Needed to confirm something? Maybe trap us?"

"I don't think so," Harry uncertainly responded. "But let's load up the rest of this stuff and get out of here."

Sirius frowned. "I know we usually aim for quiet unobtrusive exits, but can we please cause just a little wanton destruction this time?"

"They'll know right away if we do that," Harry argued. "Lucius barely thinks about creatures he considers below him, but even he might connect the whole new house elf and getting robbed at the same time."

"But we're in Malfoy Manor!" Sirius whined. "If someone's fucking with us, we may not have another chance like this."

Harry frowned hating the situation as much as Sirius. Harry's eyes trailed over the pile of things they'd not bagged yet when something caught his attention. A plan began to formulate in his mind. "What if we don't take credit?"

"What do you mean?"

Harry pointed towards an old case with several dials on it. "Do you know what that is?"

"No," Sirius said picking it up.

"You ever hear of a Gubraithian funeral?" Harry asked with a grin.

Sirius looked at the case in glee. "No way!"

"I'm thinking let's tone it down from burning too long," Harry said accepting the case, while inspecting the contents. "And instead we just let it go real big and burn fast."

"Not forever?" Sirius pouted.

Harry shook his head. "We do this big enough and they'll think everything got toasted. We'll make it look like an accident that started inside the safe."

"We take no credit because there was no robbery," Sirius realized.

"No robbery," Harry said. "And this mystery fucker doesn't know we're on to him."

Sirius understood how advantageous this exit would be. He was slowly nodding. "I suppose it'll have to do. It's going to blow big?"

"Real big," Harry said while readjusting the settings of the explosive magical device. He looked up at Sirius who was bagging up the rest of the contents. "And don't forget, Sirius, you're still keyed in to the wards."

Sirius smiled even brighter, getting on board with the 'no apparent robbery' plan. He finished storing away everything and pulled his backpack over his shoulder.

"Okay," Harry said, pleased he'd set it right. "Here's what's gonna happen. I'm going to pull the Fidelius down, at the same time as I trigger the funeral. I set the delay for three seconds. Lucius will feel the Fidelius come down, but hopefully he'll attribute it to the massive fiery explosion."

"Three seconds?" Sirius asked.

"You're keyed in to the wards so you're going to be apparating us both out," Harry nodded. "Questions?"

Sirius saw Harry drape a magic muting cloth over the physical hole in the blood-warded safe. He walked over and put his hand on Harry's shoulder. "Nope."

"Ready?"

Sirius nodded.

Harry nodded back and touched his wand to the front dial on the case. Four invisible magical arms reached out and grabbed the anchor stones right as the tip of Harry's wand began to glow, igniting the Gubraithian funeral. He dropped it over the hole as the anchor stones flew towards him and the room flickered in and out of view. "Go! Go! Go!"

Sirius drew on Harry's strength and apparated them out of Malfoy Manor. The last thing Harry saw was the cloth wrapping around the case as it fell into the safe, without triggering any of the safe's protections.

A couple of apparition hops were added for safety's sake before the pair of thieves dropped off their score at secure location. Rather than sorting through it now, they agreed to just head back at Grimmauld Place.

Sirius and Harry stood there silently, coming down from the adrenaline-filled night of failure and success.

"Someone knows way too much," Sirius said.

Harry nodded pensively.

Sirius realized he felt a lot less safe than he had a day ago. "What are we going to do about it?"

Harry shook his head. "I don't know."

"You got the diary and note?"

Harry pulled them from inside his robe and handed them over. "Not a drop of magic on either."

Sirius read through the note again. "It's not Dumbledore."

"No," Harry agreed.

"And it's not Voldemort."

Harry slowly shook his head. "No."

"I think it's That Fucker," Sirius concluded.

Harry sighed and turned to walk up the stairs. "I hope it is."

"You do?" Sirius wondered.

Harry stopped on the first step, with his hand on the banister. "There are enough dangerous fuckers in this world as it is. We don't need more."

Sirius frowned. "You're not thinking about leaving, are you?"

"No," Harry assured him. "But I am starting to miss not having to worry about wizards smarter and more powerful than me."

"Well what did you search me out for then?" Sirius said with a grin. His grin faltered when he saw Harry still looked tired. "Didn't you have politicians and Death Eaters after you in the old world?"

Harry shrugged. "Not as much as you might think. The remaining Death Eaters remembered my escape. Couple that with the fact that I took down Voldemort and I earned a healthy amount of fear in those trying to oppose or use me for their own gain."

"You could always take out Voldemort here," Sirius suggested.

Harry shook his head. "I can't, Sirius. And if you knew what I haven't told you, you wouldn't want me to either."

"Fair enough," Sirius said, making it clear he wasn't pushing the issue. "I'm just brainstorming." Sirius paused, noticing Harry was standing on the first step, still lost in thought. "What are you thinking?"

Harry turned to his godfather and looked at him incredulously.

Sirius exasperatedly explained, "I haven't forgotten tonight. I'm just wondering specifically what's got you making that face."

"I'm thinking about the person who left the note," Harry added as he began to walk up the stairs. "They were either good enough or close enough to Malfoy to get into the vault. That points towards Death Eater if they were trusted or Death Eater thuggery if they weren't. And it's only been in the last few weeks."

"We hit Weston's almost three months ago," Sirius inquired.

"I know," Harry said from the top of the stairs. "But this was the fucker watching us at the Gaunt House. I'm almost certain of it."

"You think?" Sirius asked.

"He knows that we knew exactly where to look for the ring," Harry clarified. "That's why he thought we might know exactly where to look for the diary. I need to think on this."

Sirius turned towards the kitchen. "And I need to drink on this."

Harry woke up around one in the afternoon and headed for the kitchen for some late breakfast.

He walked in and saw Dobby sitting cross-legged on the kitchen table, looking worriedly at a drunk Sirius.

"Great news!" Sirius cheered loudly.

Harry looked at Sirius doubtfully.

"Malfoy Manor is still burning," Sirius happily added, showing off the Daily Prophet's front page photo. A column of flame could be seen escaping a good sized hole in the roof. "Lucius is being cited for not registering a class one restricted item as a family heirloom."

Harry wasn't certain but he thought he saw Dobby smile. "I set it for fifteen minutes."

"You set it for fifteen days," Sirius happily corrected.

"Oops," Harry said thinking that as mistakes go, this one was pretty fucking awesome. "Do you think it still…?"

Sirius nodded. "The DMLE investigators early determination was that if the unregistered Gubraithian device burned hot enough to destroy a blood-warded safe, then it definitely burned hot enough to completely incinerate the contents."

"Fuck me," Harry grinned. "Karma's making a quick comeback."

"I'll say," Sirius agreed. "You got a letter from Albus."

"Aww bugger," Harry swore. "You want to get me a bowl of cereal, Dobby?"

"Thank you, Master," Dobby said, eagerly hopping off the table and over towards the cabinets.

Harry blinked. "Did you order him to stay there with you?"

Sirius drank the last of his bottle. "I didn't want to drink alone."

"You made him drink?" Harry asked in surprise. He noticed Dobby was pouring cereal and missing the bowl.

"Dobby, stop!"

Dobby was still pouring cereal onto the counter as he turned to Harry and said, "Yes, Master."

"Here," Harry said, grabbing the box of cereal from Dobby. "Do you need any potions? Or a hangover cure?"

Dobby shook his head but leaned over and hugged Harry. "Dobby loves Master."

Harry patted the slightly inebriated elf on the back. "Just take it easy, Dobby. Relax, sleep it off, whatever you need to do. And check with me the next time that idiot gives you a stupid order, okay?"

"Thank you, Master," Dobby said snapping his fingers. He turned to look at his tiny elf hand in surprise. "Dobby thought-"

The little elf with low tolerance disappeared in mid-sentence from the kitchen.

Sirius snickered. "New toys are fun."

"Dobby's not a toy," Harry scolded as he added milk to his cereal. He sat down at the table across from Sirius and looked at the letter. "What do you think the odds are that it's good news?"

"It's not a howler," Sirius said. "And Fawkes delivered it."

"Fawkes?" Harry asked looking up. "Didn't stick around?"

Sirius exaggeratedly shook his head. "Stupid bird ran away after I ordered Dobby to tackle him."

"You need to get laid," Harry chided with a smile.

Sirius growled, knowing he still had two more days before his next appointment with Healer Armstrong. "I will hurt you. I'm an angry drunk."

Harry just smiled quietly knowing it would infuriate Sirius. He opened up the letter from Albus and read it quickly. "Lovely."

"I'd ask what," Sirius began.

Harry was already answering. "He knows what a horcrux is and he knows we did something to Jimmy."

"But I'm too drunk to remember anything," Sirius finished.

Harry figured that was just as well. He looked over at Sirius and recalled an especially unpleasant memory. "You know those charmed mirrors we used to use?"

"I'm not wearing the homo-erotic arranged marriage necklaces except we're both doing recon at the same time. That was the agreement."

Harry narrowed his eyes. "You know why we have to use the necklaces."

"Yeah because you broke your mirror," Sirius pouted.

Harry shook his head. "If you were capable of using them like an adult…"

"I think the purpose for which I accidentally used the wrong mirror proves I'm an adult," Sirius argued.

"You were shaving your balls!"

"There are places you need a mirror to see," Sirius defended.

"You called me on it!"

Sirius waved Harry off. "I wasn't calling you. I was making an observation after getting the mirror angled right so I had a clear look at my-"

"I thought my mirror was cursed and showing me the face of true evil."

"Even if it was, you didn't have to break it."

"Yes, I most certainly did," Harry forcefully snapped.

Sirius tipped back an empty bottle and was trying to suck a few more drops out. "You're the one who brought it up." Sirius dropped his arm and empty bottle down in disgust. "What were we talking about again?"

"Charm-linked mirrors," Harry repeated in irritation. "Were they like a family heirloom? Or did you make them yourself?"

"Family heirloom? Are you kidding?" Sirius asked skeptically. "A pair of Lookie Talkies is about two galleons at any Wiz-mart."

"Lookie Talkies?" Harry repeated thinking that sounded smarter than most magical names but still dumb as hell.

"Yeah. They're children's toys," Sirius explained. "We used to use them all the time when we'd play blood traitors and muggle…" Sirius trailed off. "You probably wouldn't have played the same games I did growing up."

"Probably not," Harry confidently agreed.

"Well except for Tie-Harry-to-the-back-of-the-bus," Sirius grinned. "Everybody played that one."

"How the hell do you remember that when you don't even remember what we were talking about three minutes ago?"

Sirius shook another empty bottle and frowned. "What were we talking about?"

Harry sighed. "Take a hangover potion and go to sleep, Padfoot."

It showed how out of it Sirius was that he obeyed without protest.

Harry tucked a brand new pair of Lookie-Talkies into his cloak pocket and walked up the long path towards Hogwarts. He briefly wondered the odds that Jimmy would just happen to activate the Marauder's Map and notice an extra Potter on it. Harry wasn't worried this time though, because he knew how the young man would react.

Harry, not looking forward to the conversation with Albus, was slightly tempted to try and locate Jimmy first. It was late afternoon, and Harry had no clue what Jimmy's schedule was like. Albus, Harry expected to be in his office. But if Harry were to go hunting for Jimmy, he would be risking getting cornered by Lily.

Harry felt he had enough things rolling around in his head that he could safely put 'constant deception and lies of omission towards the elder Potters' onto the back burner where it'd set up camp and been living ever since Harry arrived in this world. It certainly didn't help matters that so far Lily Potter could detect bullshit from Harry better than a Master Legilimens.

Harry estimated that sacrificing his mother's soul probably meant that karmically, every other Lily Potter in existence had him by the balls until the end of time. Of course when Harry had made that deal, he wasn't planning on actually meeting any of them.

But that's what bottles and back burners were made for, Harry told himself, putting things like emotions and uncomfortable confrontations safely away and out of sight.

Harry was so pleased with his plan of inaction that he wasn't even watching where he was going and managed to walk right into the door.

Harry fell back on his ass tumbling down the front steps. "Fuck me! What the hell?"

"Are you alright?" a gentle voice inquired as the front door creaked open.

"Hang on, mum," another voice interrupted. A second redheaded woman emerged and looked down towards Harry with a grin. "Was that an offer?"

"Sarah!" Lily scolded her daughter. "That's no way to talk to… oh. Harry. Excuse me, Lord Black."

"I'm sure people talk to him that way quite often," Sarah commented, "if Witches Weekly is to be believed."

Sarah and Lily Potter had both walked down the steps to help Harry and were looking at him oddly. Sarah saw Harry wincing and asked, "Did you hit your head?"

"My nose mainly," Harry grumbled, testing the sensitivity of his schnozz. "What happened? I thought the doors opened automatically."

Lily looked at Harry curiously, wondering if he'd somehow attended Hogwarts. She was doing her best to ignore the monster in her chest sensation. "They open automatically for students and invited guests. I take it no one is expecting you today?"

"No, I…" Harry stumbled over the words. "Uh… Albus wrote me this morning."

"Oh good," Lily said as she and Sarah helped Harry to his feet. "I was hoping that was why you were here."

Harry glanced over at Sarah and then Lily, thinking he'd never feel normal around either of these two people. "Err… why is that?"

"Something's been bothering him," Lily replied thinking Albus rarely showed it, but she knew him better than most. "And a magical brother might bring him out of his funk."

Harry knew she was speaking of the brotherhood charm but couldn't stop himself from glancing at Sarah again. "I'll see what I can do about that. You know if he's in his office?"

"Should be," Lily replied. She looked towards her daughter. "Did you need to check Harry out?"

Sarah smirked at her mother. "Need's kind of a strong word but I like what I-"

"His head, his nose," Lily snapped. "The fall, you know what I meant. And don't think I won't start carrying around baby pictures."

"Baby pictures are cute," Sarah countered.

Lily tilted her head down at the unexpected challenge. "And do we remember when we kept trying to wear our little brother's diapers?"

Sarah stared at her mother aghast.

Harry hurriedly interjected, "I'm fine. It was nothing."

"Thank you," Lily said, thinking she may have gone too far based on the looks her daughter was giving her.

"But I wouldn't mind seeing those pictures sometime," Harry mischievously added.

Lily smothered a grin as her daughter glared at her.

Sarah dangerously warned, "The things I could show Dad in a pensieve."

Lily decided at that point she had definitely gone too far. She smiled pleasantly at Harry, "Would you like us to walk you to the Headmaster's office?"

"No, please," Harry said as he made a fist and knocked himself in the head. "I'm fine." Harry winced, "Okay, that kind of hurt, but seriously. I'm fine."

Sarah looked at Harry in slight surprise. "You know how to find the Headmaster's office?"

Harry nodded with certainty.

"Don't worry," Lily assured her daughter while giving a knowing look to Harry. "Lord Black knows his way around Hogwarts better than you think."

Harry watched the first two female Potters he'd ever remembered meeting walk down the rest of the steps and along the path towards Hogsmeade. He idly realized he could try and track down Jimmy without worry when he felt a tug on a different piece of active magic.

"Harry?" the wizened old voice greeted.

"Albus," Harry replied turning towards the Headmaster with a look of innocence on his face.

Albus frowned. "Why don't we talk in my office where I can yell and you can lie with impunity?"

"Sounds like fun," Harry agreed and led the way.

Albus immediately went for the seat behind his desk, establishing himself into a position of power. "What did you do to my Head Boy?"

Harry glanced around the office, noting Fawkes perch was unoccupied. "What makes you think I did anything?"

"Harry."

"What do you think I did?"

"Harry."

"I'm not kidding," Harry argued. "For all I know, you think I cursed him, so I need to hear an accusation to respond to."

Albus was unruffled. "You memory charmed him."

"I did, did I?"

"Harry James Potter."

Harry playfully winced. "Ouch. Breaking out the full name?"

"If treating you like a child is the only way to get answers," Albus said defending his actions.

Harry shrugged and helped himself to the candy dish. "It sounds like you have the answers."

"Not the why," Albus retorted, "nor the how."

Harry smirked inwardly, deducing that Albus hadn't been able to find the block. "Did you check him for memory charms?"

Albus nodded. "Twice. And I must concede your skill at obliviating is superior to my own."

Harry shrugged. "There are four charms I'm real good at. Memory charming is my fourth best."

Albus was rubbing his chin in thought, "I assume summoning and banishing are the top two."

Harry nodded.

"So what is the third?"

"You don't want to try and guess?" Harry said popping a lemon drop in his mouth. "The third one has more than a little personal significance."

Albus thought about what he knew of the young man relaxing across from him. "Snake charming?"

Harry blinked. "Is there a field of magic for that?"

"There are a few ancient spells involving serpents, but I believe snakes typically obey a parselmouth, making many of them unnecessary. Nevertheless, I can see that was an inaccurate guess." Albus shook his head. "I'm not sure I know you well enough to think of any others with personal significance."

"Tsk, tsk," Harry shook his head. "After all, the other you talked my parents into using the charm that inadvertently led to my orphanhood."

"The Fidelius," Albus said in realization. "The reason for your interest in warding?"

"Part of it," Harry agreed.

"And you're better at casting the Fidelius than memory charming?" Albus asked more than a little impressed.

"I don't know if I'd say better, but there's definitely less competition."

Albus inclined his head in understanding. "Does this mean you're not going to be telling me the how or why?"

"The how is easy," Harry answered. "I knew you'd search him for a memory charm when he got back. And unless you're very careful doing that, you tend to kick up a lot of dust."

"Being careful takes time and attentive observation of the memories," Albus reasoned aloud. "Something a cursory examination never is."

Harry nodded. "Then I come back a couple days later and make use of all that dust you kicked up. That's why even if you located it… It'll appear as though you cast it."

"It sounds like a form of layering," Albus commented.

"Exactly," Harry grinned. "Layering is where memory charms really get fun. You should've seen the job I did on these Unspeakables."

"Excuse me," Albus said after Harry suddenly went quiet.

"Nothing bad," Harry said waving away Albus' worries.

"Mmm-hmm."

Harry tiredly explained. "It was my arrival in this world. New person comes shooting out the Exit, and they'd probably grill me for days. I wanted to locate my godfather, so I had to send them in a different direction."

Albus snapped his fingers. "You're Miss Lupin's assignment! That explains a lot."

Harry nodded.

"But what about when she had to go away for days at a time, undercover?"

Harry shrugged. "We rented a lot of movies and laid on the couch."

Albus frowned in disappointment. "I shouldn't have to remind myself you're not a bad person."

"You can be a good person and a bad influence," Harry offered.

Albus murmured in resignation. "You've given me the how but still no why. Should I stop asking?"

"I'm going to tell you the why," Harry assured him. "In case he comes in again and we have to obliviate him again."

"We?" Albus doubtfully questioned.

"The why," Harry continued, "is because Jimmy convinced me to. It was his idea."

"It was?" Albus repeated, ensuring the brotherhood charm was still working.

Harry nodded. "Frankly, we don't trust Snape not to rip the knowledge from Jimmy's head."

Albus frowned. "Professor Snape has my full-"

"Blah, blah," Harry interrupted. "You're as blind to that man as Cornelius Fudge is to fashion."

Albus frowned harsher.

"Trust me," Harry argued. "Until you've been a Potter in his classroom for a few years, you won't get it. I mean it. The sheer volume of hate and petty in that man is limitless where I'm concerned and it doesn't sound like Jimmy's much better."

Albus nodded slowly. "I'll consider it a personal issue and the matter closed. But do not underestimate what I will do when it comes to protecting the wellbeing of students entrusted to my care."

Harry knew many people doubted Albus' judgment, and a few doubted his sanity, but no one doubted his dedication to Hogwarts. "Your intentions are not the same as your actions."

Albus tilted his head to watch Harry impassively. "Do tell."

"I've no doubt you act in what you believe to be the best interests of students," Harry explained when he saw Albus scrutinizing him. "But sometimes I think your attempts to redeem men like Snape do more harm to innocents than you realize."

Albus frowned at the words. "Severus Snape needs no redemption. Please," Albus said stopping Harry from interrupting. "He never became a Death Eater and you've only met him briefly."

Harry reluctantly had to admit this world's Snape could be a bit different. But he doubted it.

"My counterpart may have had a blind spot for Severus, and I may as well, but you must admit that you cannot view him objectively either."

Harry grumbled but didn't disagree. "He's a poohead."

"Moving on," Albus said steepling his hands together as he leaned forward. "Tell me everything you can about the Dark Lord's horcrux."

Harry winced at unexpected lack of subtlety from the Headmaster. "Looked that one up, eh?"

Albus' look was grave. "You were not particularly discreet in your allusions towards its importance."

"It?"

"The horcrux," Albus replied.

"Right," Harry grimaced. "It."

Albus frowned as he felt the brotherhood charm buzzing. "What aren't you telling me?"

"You ever think horcruxes get lonely?"

Albus paused at the odd question. "What do you mean?"

"Nothing," Harry said, fully aware that answer wasn't going to fly.

"Harry."

"So you know what a horcrux is, right?"

Albus nodded affirmatively.

"And you know how they're made? And how supposedly you can't make more than one because it'd leave you insane?"

"Oh no," Albus said catching on.

Harry nodded ruefully. "You ever hear Voldemort's spiel on how seven is the most magically powerful number?"

"Seven?" Albus whispered the word in horror. "Now is really not the time for your offbeat sense of humor."

"Yeah," Harry admitted with a scratch of his head. "This world is different. I mean a lot's the same, but not everything. Even still, I'm reasonably sure on the number."

"You know where they are," Albus realized.

"This world's different," Harry retorted. "They're not even all the same objects here."

Albus sat back and relaxed slightly, secure in the knowledge that Harry had been investigating them. "How so?"

Harry saw a calculating look in the old man's eye. "Alright, well, I know of one that's definitely new to me. And to be honest, I'm kind of surprised you haven't figured it out."

Albus arched an eyebrow. "Godric's Hollow?"

Harry realized he'd spoken too soon on what the Headmaster knew and nodded. "My death was used to make a horcrux out of Sirius Black's skull."

"Oh my word," Albus muttered in dawning realization that Voldemort was truly beyond redemption.

"And in this world," Harry continued. "From what I hear, the Dark Lord doesn't even have a familiar."

"Not to my knowledge," Albus replied when Harry waited for a response.

Harry nodded. "In mine, he had a snake named Nagini, which he possessed frequently and contained another piece of him."

Albus cast a quick Patronus charm, sending a ghostly phoenix from his office.

Harry looked at Albus warningly.

"Professor McGonagall was about to interrupt us," Albus said, knowing the brotherhood charm would assure Harry. "I told her this was a bad time."

"If you need to-"

"No, please," Albus said urging Harry to stay.

"Sorry," Harry offered. "I just got your note, and figured I'd drop by while Sirius sleeps off his bender."

"I do have dinner plans I'd prefer not cancel," Albus urged. "So why don't you tell me which horcruxes you've already located and which others you are still looking for."

Harry wasn't surprised at what the Headmaster had deduced. "What makes you think that… yeah. Who am I kidding?" Harry gave up acting coy. "Three of them are safe. Three of them aren't."

Albus felt pleasantly surprised. "You have recovered three of them? And I thought you said there were seven."

Harry nodded. "Six horcruxes, the seventh piece of soul stayed in him."

"Of course," Albus said in understanding. "What can you tell me about them?"

Harry frowned. "I'm not some resource for you to tap, Albus. Nor am I member of your Order." Harry clenched and sent magic into the brotherhood charm.

Albus clenched and strengthened the charm on his end. He forcefully asserted, "Nor am I the man for whom you hold so many conflicting emotions." Albus softened. "I do not see you as a resource, Harry. I'm not proud of the Albus Dumbledore you knew in your old world. And I cannot say that faced with the decisions he had to make, that I would have made them any differently. But I will not accept the blame you feel he deserves."

Harry looked away, slightly embarrassed.

"This charm," Albus said flaring the brotherhood bond, "is so that we can better understand each other and work together. It should not be a security blanket because you suspect ulterior motives in my every action."

"I know. It's not you," Harry argued. "I'm just… I'm feeling a lot more vulnerable suddenly and frankly, paranoia's probably saved my life a time or two."

Albus popped a lemon drop into his own mouth and smiled. "True. But it's probably cost you opportunities as well. Would you like to talk about it?"

Harry looked up at the Headmaster. He hesitated before answering, "Not really, but even if I did, this is stuff I have to talk to Sirius about first anyway."

"Fair enough," Dumbledore accepted. "And so now when I politely inquire about the horcruxes, can I assume you won't think I only want your knowledge and to be rid of you? Or that my only concern in things is how they pertain to the downfall of Voldemort?"

"Yes, yes, point made," Harry grumbled. "Now you're just rubbing it in."

Albus held a pleasant smile that slipped into a slight frown when Harry stayed quiet. "How can I help you locate the other horcruxes if you won't tell me anything? I suspect I know more about this world than you."

"The skull," Harry decided. "That's the one you should focus on."

Albus nodded slowly in thought. "And what of the others?"

"The three that are safe…" Harry paused, "you don't need to worry about." Harry saw Albus giving him a knowing look and explained, "It's between me and Sirius, I'm not just being petulant."

"Mmm-hmm," Albus said doubtfully.

"The other two?" Harry said, running through things in his own mind. "I think… I think someone else got to them already."

Albus sat up suddenly. "Someone else knows? The wizard in black?"

"Someone," Harry shrugged. "I'm pretty sure it's not a Dark Lord approved someone, but I don't know why they're collecting."

"What are they?"

Harry was still thinking about the note from the other horcrux hunter and answered distractedly, "The Slytherin family ring in my world was hidden at the Gaunt house. When I looked I saw signs it had once been there and there were collapsing wards surrounding the former hiding place."

Albus frowned. "You don't think Voldemort removed it for safe-keeping?"

"No," Harry assured him.

"And why not?"

Harry turned to Albus, suddenly realizing how distracted he'd been. "For reasons I'm not going to go into."

Albus sat back and raised his hands in surrender. "I'm not pushing. Just asking once."

"Right," Harry chuckled as he decided on exactly what he would reveal. "I will tell you that I think That Fucker or whoever it is that has the ring, that they also have the diary."

"The diary?" Albus perked up.

"The other horcrux," Harry confirmed. "It too appeared to have been moved by the same person."

"Where was it?" Albus inquired.

Harry snapped his mouth shut. He shook his head. "It wasn't there, so it doesn't matter." Harry glanced at his watch. "Why don't we call it a day and you can make your dinner plans?"

Albus looked at Harry hopefully. "There isn't anything else you'd like to share?"

"Actually," Harry said taking pleasure in playing with Albus' emotions. "I need to talk to Jimmy before I go. You mind telling me where he is?"

Albus frowned. "No."

"Was that a 'no' you don't mind? Or a-"

"No."

"It'll just take a moment," Harry argued.

Albus reached into one of his drawers and twisted a number of concentric circles until a point lit up with a blue light and settled. "He's coming here. If it'll just take a moment, you can talk here."

Harry wore a look of mock disappointment. "You don't even trust me to meet with Jimmy alone?"

Albus inclined his head to look over his glasses at Harry. "And what happened the last time you met with Jimmy alone?"

"I memory charmed him and made it look like you did it," Harry bashfully admitted.

"Mmm-hmm," Albus said.

"What was that thing anyway?" Harry said pointing towards the Headmaster's desk drawer.

Albus smiled mirthfully. "I'm not surprised you didn't recognize it. It's a way to contact and coordinate with the prefects and the Head Boy and Girl. The circles are each linked with a badge. I've instructed the Head Boy to come to my office and that it is not an emergency."

"Hmph," Harry chided. "I'll have you know your counterpart felt I deserved the prefect badge but didn't want to burden me with the whole prophecy and chosen one stuff already on my plate."

Albus presented an almost genuine look of embarrassment. "My apologies. And the Head Boy?"

"You were dead by then," Harry grinned victoriously. "Pity."

Albus frowned when Harry stuck his tongue out at him.

"Headmaster?" Jimmy called out as he opened the office door.

"Come in, Mr. Potter, come in," Albus urged.

Jimmy noticed the other person present. "Harry?"

"Hiya, Jimmy," Harry greeted.

"What are you doing here?" Jimmy asked glancing between the Headmaster and Harry. "You didn't do anything stupid, did you?"

Harry used a magical arm to flick his sort of brother in the ear. "Watch it."

Jimmy swatted uselessly by his ear and turned to the Headmaster curiously.

Albus motioned towards Harry. "Lord Black wished to have a brief word with you." Albus saw both Potters giving him the same look but he wasn't going anywhere. "I feel the need to chaperone."

Harry pulled out his Lookie Talkies and handed one to Jimmy. "I wanted to make sure you had a way to instantly contact me."

Jimmy accepted the small mirror in confusion. "Thanks, Harry. Not that I don't appreciate it but is there something I should know?"

"Excellent question," Albus immediately responded. "Harry?"

"No," Harry said with a glare at the Headmaster. "Nothing you should know. I'm just being cautious."

"Cautious?" Jimmy repeated.

Harry shrugged. "Yeah, cautious."

Albus looked at Harry and saw he was done. "Thank you, James. That will be all."

"Headmaster," Jimmy bid goodbye. "See you, Harry."

"Oh Jimmy," Harry suddenly recalled. "Do me a favor and please, please, don't use that mirror to shave your balls."

Jimmy looked at his half of the Lookie Talkie set again. "No worries. I doubt it's sharp enough even if I wanted to."

Harry waved goodbye as Jimmy disappeared out the door. Harry felt worry creep into his stomach. "He was just kidding, right?"

"I like to think so, but I wouldn't bet the castle on it," Albus grinned knowing the Head Boy's appreciation for taking advantage of the stereotypes of Gryffindors.

Harry decided not to give it any further thought. "I'm going to go."

"If I find anything noteworthy about the… items, shall I contact you?"

"Yeah," Harry said in surprise. "I'd appreciate that. I've got some personal stuff kinda going on right now that I need to figure out, but I'll be around."

Albus carefully worded. "Is this 'stuff' the reason you're feeling 'cautious'?"

Harry nodded. "I just got a bad feeling. By giving Jimmy a mirror, now he'll most likely never have an occasion to need to use it. But if I'd thought about it, and I'd not given him the mirror, then inevitably he would have needed it."

Albus stroked his beard. "I knew a man who utilized similar logic. On the days that clear weather was especially important, he would always carry an umbrella, in hopes to stave off the rain. It worked for him twice."

"See? Exactly," Harry agreed.

Albus thinned his lips adding, "And then it rained for two years straight."

Harry responded with the strongest logic in his arsenal. "You're a poohead too. Goodbye," Harry said as he left the office.

"Okay, what was that?" Sarah quietly asked when she felt they were out of earshot.

"What was what?" Lily replied in a whisper.

"Lord Black knows his way around Hogwarts better than you think," Sarah repeated in a deep and mocking voice.

"I don't sound like that," Lily scolded.

"That's debatable, but I meant the unspoken 'wink, wink, nudge, nudge' in your tone."

Lily sometimes forgot how observant her daughter was. "You know we all assumed the Lord Blacks never went to Hogwarts, right?"

"Yeah?"

Lily looked both ways before answering, "The way he expected the doors to open, that's a relatively common mistake. But it's common in graduates coming back to the castle for the first time. People with seven years experience of the doors opening for them."

Sarah looked over at her mum. "You think Harry went to Hogwarts?"

Lily walked into the Hog's Head as her daughter held the door open. "I don't see how we could have missed him, but yeah, I think he went to Hogwarts."

"He's younger than Tonks," Sarah replied. "Goodness knows she's been bragging about that enough. So did he change his name?"

Lily saw Gin Weasley behind the bar looking at her when the forward young woman loudly asked. "The usual?"

"Yeah, please," Lily and Sarah said as they dropped their cloaks onto the backs of their chairs.

"Like we'd ever risk anything else here," Sarah muttered quietly.

Lily smirked at her daughter. "I've heard some people rave about the Friday Fried Surprise."

"That's like calling Bertie Botts your favorite candy. You know what it is, don't you?"

Lily shook her head. "I thought it was a secret, hence the surprise."

"She just refries the leftovers from throughout the week. No two orders taste the same and she's not even sure what most of them are. That's the surprise."

"That's revolting," Lily calmly decided.

"That's bar food," Sarah assured her. "The idea is to get you drunk enough not to really look at what you're eating. And make the food salty enough that you need another drink."

"I'm beginning to think you're a little too familiar with bar room settings," Lily chided. "You know what they'll do to your skin."

"Oh please. The Hog's Head hardly counts as a bar. No one comes here looking to dance or looking to dance. And you never answered my question."

Lily took a moment to remember the question and frowned. "I don't want to spend all our time gossiping about Harry. I feel like we never get to talk anymore."

"Okay," Sarah readily agreed. "What's on your mind?"

Lily smiled back and opened her mouth, only to snap it shut a few seconds later. She opened her mouth again and began to make a hand gesture, before catching herself and closing her mouth once more. She came to a decision and was about to speak when Gin Weasley arrived with their order.

"Two beer nut salads," Gin announced settling down the large bowls. "And two house ales. Anything else?"

Sarah had already picked up her fork and answered, "Yeah. Do you know if Harry Black went to Hogwarts under a different name?"

Gin actually stumbled at the mix of the question and the oaths preventing her immediate response. "Huh?"

Lily was intrigued by the unexpected reaction. "This all looks wonderful, Gin. Thank you."

"My pleasure," Gin said with a nod.

"We were just about to gossip about the Lord Blacks. Care to join us?"

"We were, eh?" Sarah said grinning at her mum.

Lily nodded.

"Come on, Gin," Sarah urged. "I'll tell you all about how awkward Mum is around Harry."

"Okay," Gin said brimming with curiosity. She untied her apron and spun it around to her side. "Now what's this about Harry and awkward?"

Lily glared her daughter into silence and pounced on the new addition to their table. "Before we get into that, Miss Weasley, I think we need to have a talk about using permanent marker in improper ways on my son."

Gin Weasley looked at Sarah for help and gulped. "Yes, Mrs. Potter."

"Relax," Lily said with a grin. "I'm just having you on. I know it was Harry and Sirius who did that."

"Oh good," Gin said with a forced laugh. "You really had me going there, Mrs. Potter."

Sarah raised a curious eyebrow, wondering if her little brother's crush wasn't as unrequited as she first assumed.

Ginny saw both Potter women scrutinizing her and defiantly urged. "Were you saying something about Harry?"

Lily glared, every bit the mother thinking of her baby, and then nodded pleasantly. "He acts like he went to Hogwarts. But none of us recognize him or anyone similar."

"He probably would have gone around your time," Sarah said with a nod towards Gin. "Maybe a couple of years older, but he's younger than Tonks."

Gin tapped her chin, deep in thought. "You're thinking about Fred and George's year?"

"Anywhere around there," Sarah replied.

Gin was slowly shaking her head. "No, I can't think of any wizards fitting Harry's attitude and power."

"I have a wild theory," Lily offered.

"But," Gin interrupted, pointing a finger in the air and maintaining her perfectly stoic expression.

"Oh?" Lily perked up.

Gin began to slowly nod. "But there was this one witch."

"No," Sarah gaped, "way."

Lily furrowed her brow. "You think Harry's…"

"I don't know," Gin lied. "But there was that one witch who was always so quiet and really strong magically."

"I knew those eyelashes looked too good," Sarah cheered.

Lily frowned. "So are you implying he's a male who pretended to be female in school? Or a female pretending to be male now?"

"Well you know," Gin confided, "Auror Lupin is a Black by birth, so there's definitely a metamorph gift in the bloodline. Maybe Harry's…" Gin shifted her hands as if testing imaginary weights. "A little from column A and a litlle from column B."

Sarah's face was momentarily stuck in mix of disbelief and disgust. She shook her head and turned to her mother. "Didn't you have a wild theory?"

"It somehow doesn't feel as wild as it did a moment ago," Lily said in bewilderment. "But considering it appears he went to Hogwarts and no one knows him, I thought that he might simply be a time traveler."

Gin shook an accusing finger. "That would actually explain the dual Lord Black thing."

Sarah gasped and pointed at her mother. "That's why you two get retarded around each other. He's like your great, great grandson from the future."

Gin tilted her head to look at Lily. "He does have your eyes."

"I noticed that," Lily uncomfortably admitted. "But I'm not so sure he's from the future."

"What are you saying?" Sarah asked curiously.

Lily took a deep breath before quietly conceding, "That I think he might be… could be… your real grandfather."

Sarah blinked, exclaiming loudly. "You think he's your dad?"

Gin was leaning off to her side, having a small coughing fit.

Lily shrugged helplessly. "I don't know. But he's fully aware of whatever's weird between us and I'm grasping at straws."

Sarah saw Gin wasn't going to be any help and inquired, "I didn't think you could travel to the future, only the past."

"Time turners only go to the past, but supposedly there are spells that can go anywhere. And besides you don't have to actually travel to reach the future," Lily said. "All it takes is a magical accident to put you in a fifty year stasis, and in a blink of an eye, it's just like you traveled to the future."

Gin held up a hand after she'd composed herself. "Just to be clear, we're talking about the possibility that Harry is your dad, right?"

"Yes," Lily replied.

"Fantastic," Gin agreed helping herself to a sip of Sarah's ale.

Sarah was still shaking her head distressed at the possibility of dealing with a really hot grandfather. "What led you to this theory?"

Lily shrugged. "I don't know what Harry's hiding, but he takes every opportunity he can to hug me." Lily frowned as she admitted, "And he feels guilty about it."

"So like he missed out on raising you," Sarah concluded. "That's nuts."

Lily sighed. "Yeah, it is. But if you ever watch him, I mean really watch him, you'll see. He acts like he's woken up in a world that looks the same just all the people are brand new."

"Whoa," Gin was impressed. "Deep."

"This is great," Sarah sarcastically bit out while rubbing the bridge of her nose. "Either Harry is my grandfather or somewhere in the range of fifty to a hundred percent female."

Lily chuckled at the simplicity of the summation.

"I wouldn't say that," Gin disagreed.

"You got another theory?" Sarah looked up hopefully.

"No," Gin said with a bright grin. "I just meant that it's not either-or. He could be both."

"I've been thinking."

"And I've been drinking."

Harry glared at his godfather. "Sirius, stop it."

"I can drop it," Sirius agreed.

Harry growled. "Do you really want me to set back your healing?"

"No," Sirius pouted. "That prospect is not very appealing." Sirius saw he was quickly nearing the 'poke-in-the-eye' level of irritation. "Perhaps if you were more revealing? Stop concealing that feeling? Okay I'm done, don't hurt me." Sirius had his arms up to protect himself and added, "Or send me reeling through the ceiling."

Dobby snickered.

"Don't laugh," Harry warned the elf. "We don't want to encourage this sort of behavior."

Sirius grinned at the amused elf. "I've been doing a little thinking too, actually."

"Oh yeah?" Harry looked up. "What have you been thinking?"

"I think," Sirius said. "I think most people don't really appreciate how much more complicated wiping is when you're dealing with a hairy bum."

"Padfoot," Harry grumbled.

"I'm not kidding," Sirius continued. "Girls especially can't comprehend the dynamics necessary to-"

Harry cut him off with a silencing charm. "Dobby, you can stay or go, but if you stay please turn invisible. Sirius can't seem to stop playing to an audience today."

Dobby smiled and snapped his fingers disappearing from view.

Sirius had managed to break the silencing charm and pouted. "Fine, I've been thinking about the thing too."

Harry looked emboldened. "And?"

"And I think if we're going to do something, we're better off sooner than later."

Harry nodded. "Me too. Albus will connect us with the burglaries real soon, if he hasn't already. Our options are just going to get more and more limited."

"You think?" Sirius wondered. "But we're always so slick about making the robberies all quiet and clever. You know, like the opposite of the loud, blunt, and obnoxious public image we've been cultivating."

"Cultivating?" Harry repeated. "You've just been yourself."

"Myself?" Sirius said, choking back the tears. "You don't think I wish I could stop hiding? Treating it like a disease, just because I want to be a dancer?" Sirius did a pirouette and nearly lost his balance.

Harry looked away tiredly. "Padfoot, Dobby's not even listening to you."

Sirius snickered. "Sure he is. I can hear him laughing in the corner."

"Sorry," the invisible elf's voice carried from the corner.

"Invisible and silent, if you stay," Harry said loudly. A snap of elven fingers was the only response Harry received.

"What'll Albus do when he figures it out?" Sirius asked returning to more earnest conversation.

Harry frowned. "Probably not much. He won't approve, but with a supposed greater good of checking Death Eater homes for horcruxes, he'll understand. I'm more concerned with the mystery note fucker."

"Yeah?" Sirius urged Harry to continue.

"He wanted us to get the note with the fake diary," Harry summarized. "Now he may think we got the note and aren't jumping to meet him but he'll probably have to assume that we didn't get it. In which case, he either will leave notes at other horcrux locations -locations we don't know- or he'll try and contact us another way."

"You're not thinking of actually going to the Shrieking Shack?"

"Definitely not," Harry said. "We both need to stay away from there."

"You think we should just wait for him to contact us again?"

Harry bit his lip uncertainly. "Actually, I'm thinking we force him to come to us on our terms."

Sirius perked up. "You think he'll do that?"

Harry warily argued, "I think he'll have to. He can't be certain we got the letter. And if he doesn't show, then it proves his claims of cooperation and an alliance were disingenuous."

"Drawbacks?"

Harry let out a tired breath. "What I'm thinking will clearly alert the Dark Lord that his horcruxes aren't safe."

"He's probably heard about Malfoy's floor vault," Sirius pointed out. "And I doubt he missed the fires from Grindelwald's old bunker either."

"Yeah, I mean I'm almost certain he knows," Harry agreed. "But this will move us up his 'to-kill-painfully' list."

"What are you saying we should do exactly?"

Harry's face was grim as he explained. "Set our own trap with live bait."

"Live? How live?"

"I say we hold a private auction, by invitation only for Ravenclaw's cube, Slytherin's locket, and Hufflepuff's cup."

Sirius' eyes widened in shock. "And just who would we be inviting? I'm doubting an owl to That Fucker will reach him."

Harry shook his head with a smirk. "We're not inviting a single person. We just want the people who'd be crashing this party."

"Yes," Sirius agreed with a manic look in his eyes. "Yes, crashing this party… of doom!"

"What?" Harry was perturbed.

Sirius motioned exaggeratedly. "I thought we were trying to add a little flair to our conversation."

Harry sighed. "Dobby? You have to leave the room. I'm sorry. And Sirius? Stop playing to an audience."

Sirius realized Harry wasn't acting overdramatic, he simply was overdramatic. Sirius saw Harry looked pretty determined too. "So the only people who will understand what we're auctioning are Voldemort and our mystery fucker?"

"Dumbledore will too."

Sirius couldn't think of any better ideas. "You know this may well mark the end of the Death Eater Bandits."

Harry nodded. "With half the horcruxes, we have more to lose than we do to gain by continuing. The ward sets have been getting nastier because they know we're coming."

Sirius nodded having thought similar things. "But we can still make exceptions when opportunities present themselves, right?"

"Absolutely," Harry agreed. "And you know, someday in the future, there will be people, who desperately need to be robbed. And they may not have any tattoos on their arms."

Sirius smiled happily, picturing a bright future. "Very well then," Sirius said as though coming to a grand conclusion. "Let's just see who is interested in," Sirius snapped his head to face Harry, "buying some of this dark bastard's soul!"

"Oh for Merlin's sake," Harry grumbled rubbing his temples as a headache formed. "You've got no audience! Why are you doing this?"

Sirius stood up challengingly. "You're my audience."

"It's my idea," Harry pointed out.

"Yeah but," Sirius argued. "But you're not really saying it with any… panache."

Harry watched his godfather wiggle his hips and began to wonder if Sirius really did want to become a dancer. "You're an idiot."

"No, you're an idiot," Sirius petulantly retorted. "And a drama queen."

Harry looked up dangerously. "Excuse me?"

"Ah-ha," Sirius exclaimed pointing at Harry. "See?"

Harry fought the urge to huff. "You're a poohead."

"No, you're the poohead, poohead."

Harry stopped a beat unsure how to reply to that one. "Are we done now?"

"Yeah, we're done," Sirius agreed. "Poohead."

Chapter 27

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Author's Note: Big thanks to the guys that help me get these chapters right: IP, Chuck, Jim, Chris, Rob, JJ, Sean, and everyone else I'm forgetting.

Harry wasn't sure what an anxiety attack felt like, but guessed this would be as good a time as any to find out. He looked pleadingly at Dumbledore. "Uhh…"

Albus shook his head negatively at Harry.

Harry uneasily met the shell-shocked gazes of all the Potters in the room and turned back to the Headmaster, silently begging him with wide unblinking eyes.

"No," Albus insisted firmly with a stern expression.

"Uh… uh… uhh…" Harry stuttered before settling on a course of action.

"Harry, no!" Albus said wagging his finger at the younger man.

Harry was trying to come up with ways of interpreting 'no' into meaning 'yes' or at least 'alright, but just this once.'

Severus Snape finally broke the suffocating tension with a loud gasp. "You're the Potter hellspawn in the prophecy!"

Harry knew exactly how to respond to that accusation. "Obliviate!"

Severus deftly parried the memory charm and assumed a defensive position. "How dare you!" He sent back a disarming charm that Harry blocked with little effort. "Headmaster, are you just going to stand there and let him-"

"Obliviate," Albus regrettably cast, just as Severus turned his direction. The Potions Master flashed a shocked look of betrayal just before his eyes glazed over. He fell into a gentle sleep from a swish of Albus' wand. Albus frowned at Harry, showing how distasteful albeit necessary his actions were.

"Thank you, Albus," Harry said, relaxing momentarily with a supremely grateful smile. "But you missed a whole lot of the others." He finished pointing towards everyone else in the room.

"Harry," Albus scolded.

"WHAT THE BLOODY HELL IS GOING ON?" James finally exploded, holding his wand at the ready.

Lily was visibly shaken. She looked to be teetering on the brink of collapsing into tears. "Harry?"

Harry looked at the closest thing to his mum that he'd ever remembered and could find no words. "Blih…ber… bluh…"

"I need some answers," James demanded, swinging his wand arm across the room. "Right fucking now."

Sarah was frowning. "You can't be grandpa if you're a Potter."

"What?" James snapped in confusion.

"Is this about the basilisk?" Jimmy wondered aloud.

"What?" James snapped again.

"How do you know about the basilisk?" Albus jerked in surprise.

"Okay, not the basilisk," Jimmy meekly said.

"Harry?" Lily repeated unable to move.

James suddenly put two and two together. His voice was as quiet this time as it had been loud before. "Sirius?"

"Stop!" Harry shouted, attracting everyone's attention. "Stop! You've all got the wrong idea. Just give me a second here." He held his hand up and took a moment to collect himself.

One second turned into three, and three became five before Albus realized Harry was calculating. "Harry!"

"Sorry," Harry admitted, biting his bottom lip, still hoping to wake up from this emotional nightmare.

Sarah could tell Harry was hesitant to tell them everything and decided to start small. "Just how closely are we related? Because I feel dirty already and if you're just a drifter pretending to be my dead older brother…" Sarah trailed off as everyone looked at her. "What? It could happen."

"He's trying to hide the fact that he's our brother," Jimmy said looking at his sister and trying to remember if she always had that freckle by her eye.

"I'm not your brother. If anything I'm trying to hide the fact that I'm not… your… okay this is getting confusing." Harry said distractedly.

"Just tell them the truth, Harry. They need to hear this from you," Albus urged. "And you must know I will correct any and all falsities in your story."

James turned to the Headmaster hostilely. "You knew about this?"

Albus took a step back at the vehemence suddenly directed his way. "So did Tonks," Albus pointed and sold out the auror subordinate.

"Hey," Tonks whined.

Albus held up his hands in a gentle and calming manner. "And please let Harry explain before you jump to the wrong conclusions."

They all turned to look at Harry, who turned to look at his godfather. "Sirius?"

Sirius had thought it was hilarious to see how rattled his godson had become, especially since it had been Harry and not him who had messed this one up. But the sheer anger James was exhibiting coupled with how scared and fragile Lily looked made the situation a lot less amusing to him.

Sirius opened his mouth to say something and stopped at the sight of his former best friend. He opened his mouth once more, managed to produce a slightly strangled sound before finally just saying, "Good luck, Harry."

Sirius instantaneously popped into his animagus form and burrowed under Harry's hospital bed, letting out sad little warbled barking the whole way.

James' wand fell from his hand the second he saw Sirius' transformation. His entire body deflated in defeat.

"Coward," Harry grumbled at the canine hiding out of sight.

Lily staggered forward and gripped onto Harry's arm franticly. "Please."

Harry's heart never stood a chance at that look and he gave up. "You're right. I'm sorry. You all deserve an explanation. And I'm going to give you one." He took a deep breath and let it out. "Right now." He nodded resolutely. "This very minute."

"Harry!" Albus cried while fighting the urge to strangle the young man.

"Okay, okay," Harry said grabbing a hold of Lily's hand. "This may take a while, so you'll want to sit down."

Lily wasn't going anywhere just yet, and kept a sweaty hold of Harry's hand.

"Right," Harry said as he uncertainly began. "Okay, I was born Harry Potter, son of James and Lily Potter."

Lily gasped, quietly mouthing, "My baby."

James was confused. "My son is a… blood purist?"

"I'm not a blood purist!" Harry pleaded before remembering, "And I'm not your son."

"I think your headache might be contagious," Jimmy said clenching his eyes in discomfort.

"Yeah," Harry quickly agreed. "Maybe we should take a few minutes to relax our Occlumency shields and look towards my wand-"

"Harry!" Albus shouted pointing his wand at the young man.

"How can they be your parents and you not be my brother?" Sarah logically questioned.

"Hang on," Jimmy said thinking deeply. "I know I've heard this riddle."

"They're not my parents-"

"No, that's not it," Jimmy said dismissing Harry's help with the riddle.

Harry was getting irritated and shouted over everyone's questions. "My parents died Halloween, 1981. They gave their lives to save me."

Lily painfully stared at Harry while the other Potters fell back in their respective seats.

Harry continued when he realized they were paying attention. "My godfather, Sirius Black, was sent to Azkaban because people thought he was our secret keeper."

Pathetic whimpering came from under the bed.

"I am not your son," Harry said, pleading with Lily to understand. "And you are not my parents."

Lily felt struck. She was being rejected and this impostor was just trying to hurt her.

"Don't be a dick, Harry," Tonks said with a frown.

Harry saw the way Lily was reacting and exclaimed, "It's nothing to do with you! It's me. Trust me. I-"

"Trust you? Because you've been so honest with us so far?" James bitterly reminded. He picked up his wand and pulled his distraught wife closer. "Who the hell are you?"

Sirius decided he'd had enough and crawled back out from under Harry's bed. He popped right back into place and grabbed a hold of Harry's collar. "I think I've heard all I need to from you."

Harry just looked at his godfather in confusion as Sirius pulled Harry up and slammed him down on the bed behind him. The cushioning charms ensured it looked worse than it was. "Sirius? What are you-"

Sirius slapped Harry twice across the face and pointed an accusing finger at him. "You know what you-"

Harry didn't give Sirius a chance before he'd tackled him to the ground. Both of them were rolling across the hospital room floor, mere meters from the exit when Albus caught on.

A flick of his wand and the door swung shut with a loud clap. "Don't even think about it," Albus warned.

Sirius and Harry stopped their struggling and looked at the door. In unison they both exclaimed, "Bugger."

Sirius shrugged and said "Sorry, kid. I tried."

"What did you call me?" Harry raged as he picked up and slammed his godfather into the door.

"Oww," Sirius weakly protested.

Harry saw the door hadn't budged and he didn't recognize the locking charm Albus had used. "Damn."

"That is enough!" Albus roared.

"It was worth a shot," Harry mumbled, knowing he'd earned this chastisement. Harry looked at Sirius curiously. "That door wasn't open all along, was it?"

"Naw," Sirius said rubbing his sore shoulder. "I opened it while I was regrouping under the bed."

"Regrouping?" Harry repeated doubtfully.

James' patience was once more at its end. "You think this is funny? You think toying with us is amusing?"

"Well, no," Sirius replied. "That was why we were trying to make a break for it."

"I appreciate the effort," Harry said while carefully maneuvering his godfather to stand in front of him.

"You're welcome," Sirius said, moving over to stand behind Tonks. "But you're still telling them your story. Not me. For the record though? I'd recommend starting with the dimension traveling rather than repeatedly breaking your mum's heart."

Harry's face was covered by his palm as he muttered to himself. "She's not my mum."

"Dimension traveling?" Peter Potter spoke calmly for the first time.

"Yeah, dimension traveling," Harry repeated. "We come from a world where my parents died when I was one. So no brother or sister for me," Harry said nodding towards Jimmy, who'd moved over to sit next to Sarah.

Harry figured he should try and get as many relevant details out as he could before curses started flying. "A little before I turned sixteen, this was about three years after this knucklehead broke out of Azkaban, he got pushed through a dimensional portal of sorts and stuck in limbo. Last April, I started studying the portal and he got spit out into this world after ten years of basically not existing."

Sirius had to be poked three times before he took over and explained, "I woke up in a hospital bed and they asked me who to call. Last I knew, Harry'd walked into a Death Eater trap, and of course, I thought James Potter had been dead for over a decade, so I asked for Remus Lupin."

"Remus knows?" James asked, feeling like the odd man out.

Tonks started chuckling. "He's going to be so upset he missed this."

"You want me to go get him?" Harry offered.

"No!" almost every voice shouted back at Harry.

"Right," Sirius snickered at Harry's pout. "So anyway, that's when I found out it was ten years later and I was in a new world. Remus was helping me, and that meant Tonks got to hear my story. I was excited and frightened to tell it to you," Sirius said nodding towards James. "But that was before I realized you were a prick."

"Padfoot," Harry scolded.

"Maybe I wasn't the most understanding bloke," Sirius admitted with a roll of his eyes. "But come on. You insulted me, you told Jimmy how I was everything wrong, and you lost your bleeding sense of humor."

James just stood there stupidly, while Lily was wrapped around him.

"You gotta admit that Prongs, the teenager who graduated Hogwarts and the only James Potter I ever knew, would have been appalled at what you've turned into."

"Sirius," Harry interrupted. "Stop it."

Sirius shrugged remorselessly but stayed quiet.

"I get why you've never grown up," Harry said, earnestly addressing his godfather. "I really do. And contrary to just about every other adult around, I think it's great. But I also get why this James Potter did grow up. And you need to get it as well."

"I get it… now," Sirius reluctantly admitted. "I might not have at first, but I do."

"Do you?" Harry questioned.

"It's you, you goofy retard," Sirius said as his eyes began to get glossy. "We both lost our best friends. But he lost you too, so he had to change. I still had you, so I had to try and be what I thought he'd want me to be… for you."

A smile began to grow, brighter and wider as Harry stood there listening to his godfather. He was just grinning proudly at him before he realized what was going on. "Oh shit," Harry said wiping his eyes. "My allergies are always flaring up this time of the year."

"Is it the hay fever?" Tonks asked with a grin. "Or maybe the bullshit?"

Sirius was rubbing his sleeve across his face too. "Whatever it is, it brought some bugs with it."

Lily had managed to detach from James and scurried over to Harry, wrapping her arms around him as her tears were flowing freely. "Oh Harry."

"A little help, guys?" Harry pleaded as Lily's body shook with sobs. "She's crying, guys. Like big honking tears. This isn't going to help my allergies." Harry said in between loud sniffles. "Please? Anyone?"

Everyone seemed content to let Harry struggle with the emotionally exhausted Lily Potter.

"There, there," Harry said, inside praying that she would stop crying. He awkwardly patted her back. "There, there."

"Harry?" Albus encouraged. "Perhaps you could continue with your story."

Harry just held on to Lily who had moved around and was now resting her head on his shoulder. He looked at her with suspiciously bright eyes and continued. "Right, okay. Well, about two months after I started working on the portal, I got sucked in it too. So it was around the start of June, that I ended up in this world. I looked up Moony in the muggle phone book and tracked down Sirius. Since then, I've been kinda playing catch up with a new history of the world as I know it and… yeah."

"Thank you, Harry, for such a richly detailed account," Albus blandly retorted. "I suspect the Potters would like to know a little more about your life, your youth, your friends, your accomplishments."

Lily seemed to be getting a hold of herself but still wasn't letting go of Harry.

Peter saw Harry looked uncomfortable. "Anywhere you'd care to start is fine."

"I want to hear about that scar on your head," Sarah suggested.

"If we died, then who saved you?" James inquired. "Who protected you when we couldn't?"

"And if Sirius was in Azkaban," Lily said looking up brightly. "Where'd you grow up?"

Jimmy was scratching his head. "Is anyone else getting a strong feeling of déjà vu?"

"Oh boy," Harry muttered to himself. He was trying to figure out which question would lead to the least unpleasant conversation. "Can we take a break or something?"

"Still have a headache?" Sirius asked.

"What headache?" Harry said before catching himself. "I mean yes."

"You want to release me from my oath?" Tonks asked, knowing a big chunk of Harry's secrets were out in the open now among the Potters. "I can help."

Harry and Sirius nodded at each other. "You're good."

Tonks turned to Sarah, then James, and then Lily in order. "It's from a reflected killing curse. You guys saved him. I think Lily did some sacrificial protection charm thing. And he grew up with the Dursleys." Tonks paused on Jimmy and looked back at Harry. "You did, didn't you?"

Harry had winced at every blunt answer and nodded guiltily to her question.

James frowned and turned inquisitively to Albus.

Albus was having entirely too much fun and explained, "Why do you think I kept checking him for memory charms?"

"Yeah," Harry said moving over towards Jimmy and drawing his wand. "Let me go ahead and undo that."

James jumped forward pointing his wand straight at Harry. "Step away from my son."

Harry just barely glanced over his shoulder, ripped the wand from James' hand, and pinned both of his arms to his sides.

With a gentle tap, Harry broke the memory charm on Jimmy, who was staring cross-eyed at the wand between his eyes.

"Oh," Jimmy said blinking away a split second of confusion. "Okay."

Harry took a step back and his magical arms released their hold of James Potter.

James was incensed at how easily he'd been dismissed as a threat but a part of him felt awfully proud thinking of the kind of wizard his first son would have become. He felt the vice like grip on his arms dissipate and plucked his floating wand out of the air. He strode over to his youngest. "You okay?"

Jimmy nodded. "I saw the name Harry Potter on the-" Jimmy stopped suddenly. "Umm… thing."

"I know you have the map," James assured him. "I told Remus to give it to you."

"You did?" Jimmy asked in surprise. "Why didn't you just give it to me?"

"I didn't want to set a bad example," James sheepishly admitted. "And I don't always like remembering those days."

Jimmy knew his older brother and dad's best friend were difficult topics for his dad. "Harry told me about his world and then I told him to memory charm me." He was scratching his head. "Though that night is still a bit fuzzy."

"That's the alcohol," Harry explained. "Not a charm."

Sarah stuck her arm into the air, waiting to be called on.

"Sarah?" James asked.

"Can we back it up a second? Because I could have sworn Tonks said reflected killing curse."

"That's my girl!" came the muffled exclamation from Madam Pomfrey's office.

Everyone stopped and turned to the cracked open door at the end of the wing. They all remained silent and looked at the Headmaster. Albus tiredly nodded and walked towards the office.

"I said that too loud, didn't I?" the question came clearly from the office.

"Poppy," Albus greeted as he found her holding a cup up to her ear.

"Headmaster," Poppy said, still holding the cup.

"You understand what I have to do?"

Madam Pomfrey pulled the cup down and stated. "I have another option. I'll swear an oath. I just want to stay here and listen."

Albus looked at the matron silently.

"Professional curiosity," she explained.

Albus tilted his head, indicating she should try again.

Madam Pomfrey gave up the act and quietly confided, "This is better than my soaps on the Wizamundo Wireless. Please don't take this from me."

Albus looked at Harry and saw no significant objection. "Let's figure out the wording for your oath." Albus stepped in the office and pulled the door closed behind him.

James watched Harry as he asked, "Did you survive a killing curse?"

"It was my mum's shield mostly, but yeah."

"Marked as an equal," Sirius ominously said eliciting several gasps around the room.

"Oh, thank you, Sirius," Harry sarcastically chided. "I always love when the conversation inevitably gets to my preordained trip down murdering lane."

"You… beat him?" James asked, suddenly remembering the very public duel. "Of course you did."

Sarah was again hung up on the words. "Murdering is just a figure of speech, right?"

"He's being a drama queen," Sirius replied with a nod.

Harry was about to poke Sirius in the eye when he got a better idea. "Since you seem so eager to answer questions, it's your turn, Padfoot." Harry picked his godfather up with invisible arms and plopped him right in the middle of the room.

Sirius gulped at being thrust into the limelight but stood there waiting patiently.

"How did he beat Voldemort?" James asked.

Sirius shifted his weight to the other foot. "That's a complicated-"

"No," Harry interrupted with a whine. "Ask him questions about him. This guy comes from a whole different world. Aren't you curious?"

Everyone remained silent until James shrugged and answered. "I knew a Sirius Black pretty well. I have only unfulfilled dreams for Harry Potter."

Harry's jaw snapped shut with an audible click.

"Thing is," Sirius said, pondering a diplomatic answer. "Harry's not real big on talking about this kind of stuff. If it was anything that could help here, I know he'd be doing something about it. I haven't even heard all the details."

"But," James was desperate. "If you did it once, you can do it again."

"No," Harry said glancing at Lily Potter. "I can't."

"You broke his neck," James pleaded. "He was paralyzed and if he hadn't had a portkey, he was done."

"It's not that simple," Harry said. "And don't underestimate Voldemort. That was a lot of luck because we had a lot of surprise on our side."

Peter cleared his throat and sounded almost cold for the first time. "I think you'll find we all know how seriously to take Voldemort."

Harry spoke apologetically. "I'm sorry, but I'm not your savior. I did what it took to beat my Dark Lord. And the closest thing to solace I have is the knowledge that I can't ever do that again. It's not an option."

"But the prophecy…" James begged.

"Is about someone else," Harry finished for him.

Peter was able to see the larger picture more clearly than the other Potters. "It would have been nice if Voldemort was as certain as you are."

Harry flinched and stayed quiet.

"What do you mean?" James asked his uncle.

Peter was watching Harry as he explained. "Have you not wondered just why Voldemort chose to attack Potters this morning? It wasn't because of any widely known Potters."

They all turned to Harry looking for an explanation.

Peter felt a bit guilty but continued. "He obviously made the connection and targeted us for that reason. I doubt it's coincidence that tomorrow the Blacks are auctioning his ancestor's locket either."

"Shit," Harry said turning to Sirius. "We've got to prepare for the auction."

"Oh no, you don't," Lily said moving forward to grab onto Harry's arm. "We won't keep you all night, but we're not done talking yet."

Harry looked to Sirius for help. Sirius just grinned and scolded, "Be nice to your mother."

"She's not my m- You're not my mother," Harry repeated.

"Maybe not," Lily strained to agree. "But you and I need to have a private conversation before you leave."

"I need to have one with both of you as well," James said in determination to Harry and Sirius.

"Oh joy," Sirius said with a forced smile.

Albus had quietly emerged from the matron's office and made his presence known. "You are still going through with the auction? After today's events, you know it's going to be even worse tomorrow."

"Relax, Albus," Harry assured. "We are prepared for almost any eventuality. Even if the Dark Lord makes the mistake of dropping by."

"Will you at least then permit me to judge your preparations myself and assist you?" Albus inquired.

"See there's this thing called plausible deniability."

"Harry," Albus said, as was becoming habit.

Harry thought it over and suggested, "You may just want to stay away altogether."

"I'm going to be there," Albus retorted with certainty. "Whether it's to help or keep an eye on you."

Sirius grinned. "How much did you pay for your invitation?"

Albus smiled thinly.

"The goblins know there's no chance we're going to accept any of the supposed offers," Harry explained. "Their cut is all of the bribe money they can get for invitations."

"You might as well tell them," Peter advised the Headmaster. "I probably overpaid at 250 galleons for mine."

"Lord Potter?" Harry looked at the Peter curiously.

"I told you to call me PJ," Peter warmly reminded. "And I figured anything you two were neck deep in would be worth being ringside for."

"PJ," a contrite Harry said. "I thought you'd be angrier over the whole… endangering-all-Potters thing."

"I am upset," Peter stoically assured. "But as it turns out you're a Potter by birth. And you both reacted immediately and effectively once you realized your mistake."

"So we've got 250," Sirius said looking at the Headmaster. "Do I hear higher? Lower?"

Peter glanced at Albus and answered. "He's not embarrassed enough. He didn't pay anything."

Albus nodded at Lord Potter's powers of deduction. "I convinced Bloodthrust that I was working with you. And I had the magic of a brotherhood charm to prove it."

"Cheater," Sirius grumbled.

Harry noted the air had a 'calm after the storm' feel to it. After a few seconds of silence he asked, "So what now?"

"Now, let's talk," Lily said jumping up and beginning to pull Harry with her.

"Harry," Albus said attracting the young man's attention. He gave him a significant look and nodded.

Harry knew what Albus was intimating, but couldn't help himself. "You think I should?"

Albus nodded. "I think you need this."

"Alright," Harry agreed. "I'll memory charm this one while you take care of the rest."

"Harry!"

"Kidding," Harry defended. "Geez, take it easy, Albus. You're not that young anymore."

Harry let Lily pull him down to her private quarters where she quickly established privacy charms.

"Why Mrs. Potter, are you trying to seduce-" Harry stopped and agreed with the look on her face. "Yeah, creepy."

"The shield," Lily said turning to face Harry. "The shield that protected you. That's why I'm drawn to you?"

"Kind of," Harry reluctantly answered. "But not really."

"Because it sounds like an idea I had." Lily was watching Harry closely. "That involved sacrificing my magic and tricking the attacker into sealing a new blood bond tying my soul into an eternal protection from that attacker specifically."

Harry nodded woefully. "My mum didn't exactly leave me her spell notes, but that sounds about right."

"I knew it would be strong, but…" Lily shook her head in astonishment. "Reflecting a killing curse?"

Harry smiled weakly. "When he possessed a wizard my mere touch burned them. It was stronger than any protection I've ever heard of."

Lily sat up in understanding. "So when you came into this world, the bond got transferred?"

"Not exactly," Harry replied.

Lily thought she had figured out the affect Harry had on her. "Why not? How do you know?"

"I know because the bond is gone. And it has been for a while."

Lily frowned.

"And actually the protection it offered has been gone even longer."

"I don't understand."

Harry knew he couldn't keep putting this off. "When I was fourteen, he used my blood in a rebirthing ritual that gave him a body again. With my blood running through his veins, it negated the protection."

Lily was running through her theory. "It shouldn't have negated the protection. What probably happened was that it protected him from the adverse effects of the protection."

Harry nodded slowly, adding this piece of information to his understanding. "That actually makes a lot of sense and explains a few things."

"Like what?" Lily was curious.

"Like why Albus was so insistent that I keep the blood wards active at Privet Drive after Voldemort's rebirth. And like my scar," Harry said tapping his forehead. "We all assumed it was the direct result of the killing curse. But all the curse did was to forge a link between my mind and Voldemort's."

"Oh no," Lily realized. "The protection fought the link, didn't it?"

Harry winced in agreement. "Any time Voldemort was close or using the link, my scar burned. A few times it'd split open and bleed. Until now, I never even considered that it was the protection that was hurting me, fighting Voldemort."

"I'm sorry," Lily said earnestly.

"You didn't do anything," Harry assured her. "And it did save my life in the face of impossible odds."

Lily nodded, frowning at the pain she knew Harry must have endured.

"On the plus side it made it real hard for him to sneak up on me," Harry said trying to lighten the mood.

Lily bit her lip. She softly suggested, "I could do it again."

"What? No," Harry snapped angrily that this woman would even consider such a thing.

"This Voldemort would never see it coming. He'd-"

"You don't get it," Harry yelled, cutting her off. "You're not my mother. It wouldn't work."

Lily frowned. "Maybe Jimmy could-"

"Stop, just shut up," Harry shouted. "If you knew what it would do to Jimmy, you'd never even consider it. You're not that cruel. Just… forget it."

Lily quickly ascertained there was more going on than she knew. She could tell Harry wasn't going to be terribly forthcoming on the details without some careful prompting. She gave him a moment to collect himself before switching gears. "Since you didn't know it was the protection hurting you, then why did you break the bond?"

Harry closed his eyes and avoided meeting Lily's gaze.

Lily gasped. "He broke it, didn't he? Just to hurt you."

"No." Harry looked up, as his eyes glistened. "Although now that you mention it, he probably knew full well what the protection was doing to me. He practically got off on the way his mere presence debilitated me."

"So you broke the bond?" Lily questioned warily.

Harry sniffled a little as he took a deep breath and stared at his feet. "I didn't break the bond." His voice was just over a whisper. "I… I used it."

Lily blinked in surprise. "You used it? What could you have used it… oh." Lily looked at Harry frightfully. "Oh."

Harry leaned back, his eyes shining as he stared up at the ceiling, unable to even look at Lily. "I destroyed my mother's soul so that I could destroy Voldemort's." Harry let out a shuddering breath. "I would've given my own in a second. I would've given almost anyone else's. But it doesn't work that way. He used my blood. Blood my mother was bonded to."

Lily honestly wasn't sure how she felt about Harry's actions but she could tell when he needed a hug more than she needed to make up her mind. She quickly moved across the room and held him tightly. "You know she never would have blamed you, Harry."

"Yeah, well, I made sure she never could."

Lily finally realized just why Harry was so vehement in his insistence that she wasn't his mother. His mother sacrificed herself to save him and he sacrificed her to save everyone else. Pretending that Lily was his mother dishonored her memory and also made Harry vulnerable again. "I think it's safe to say I know how she would feel better than anyone else. And she would have been so proud of you, Harry."

She hugged him tighter, urging him to believe her. "She would have been proud of your strength. So proud," Lily said unable to hold back her own tears.

Harry didn't even care that his allergies were making water stream from his eyes. "I like to think so," Harry agreed, feeling like the load on his shoulders was getting just a little lighter.

"She would be," Lily said again. "She would be."

"Okay, I get it," Harry said, hugging Lily back. "And I think I've figured out which side of the family my overdramatic streak comes from."

Lily snorted in between her sniffles. "I'm not your mother, Harry. We both know that. But I just want you to know, that if you want to call me Mum, no one would blame you, least of all her."

Harry patted Lily gently on the back. "Let's not go crazy just yet."

Lily groaned and squeezed Harry one last time as she pulled away. "Why do you have to be like that? We were having a moment there. We were connecting. Kind of like long lost mother-son but not really. And you ruined it."

Harry stepped back and pointed a finger. "You were trying to guilt me into it!"

Lily had the decency to blush.

"Unbelievable," Harry said with a shake of his head. "I'm opening up to you. I'm vulnerable."

Lily arched an eyebrow as she hooked an arm around Harry's elbow and proceeded to escort him back to the hospital wing. "And just how far do you think your apple's fallen from this tree?"

Harry's mouth twitched in agreement. "True enough. I sometimes make Sirius feel guilty for not getting me Christmas presents when he was in Azkaban."

"Wow," Lily said looking at Harry appraisingly. "That's low."

"Ahem," Harry mockingly cleared his throat.

"That was entirely different," Lily said attempting to end the discussion. "So you grew up with Petunia?"

Harry nodded.

"Was that as bad as I'm afraid it was?"

"It wasn't awful." Harry shrugged. "Roof over my head, secret blood protection I didn't know about, unfair split of household chores, enough second hand clothes and food to get by. The way I see it, it would've been about the same at an orphanage, only without the secret blood protection."

Lily frowned and offered, "If you want we could go curse my sister sometime."

Harry bit back a snort. "I think I'd like that… Mum."

Lily jerked her head to look at Harry in surprise.

Harry broke into a grin. "I'm just fucking with you, Lily."

"Cruel, callous bastard," Lily calmly said. "Just remember you got that from my side of the family too."

Harry kept an eye on the devious woman walking next to him. "You know you can't tell anyone any of this, right?"

Lily kept pace with Harry and just stayed quiet.

"I'll snap," Harry warned. "I'm not kidding. I'll go dark. I'll kill everybody. I'm damn good at it."

Lily just patted Harry gently on the arm.

"Please? Lily?" Harry begged. "Mum?"

They arrived back at the hospital wing and stopped at the door. Lily leaned forward onto the tips of her toes and kissed Harry gently on his cheek. "Just because I'm not your mother, Harry, doesn't mean you can stop me from acting like it."

Harry smiled back at Lily, figuring if nothing else, he could spend time with her under the guide of apprenticing in emotional manipulation.

They opened the door and walked in, finding the hospital wing lively with conversation.

"Hey Harry," Sirius beckoned. "Who else knows about us? I know there's Gin."

"Gin Weasley?" Lily asked curiously. "She knows about you?"

Harry nodded. "She's under oath not to say anything."

Lily chuckled. "She told me she thought you were a woman in disguise."

"She what?" Harry said in a higher voice than planned.

A ghost popped into existence right next to Harry. "I told you that bitch was crazy."

"Oh boy," Harry grumbled.

Jimmy couldn't help himself. "Who is the hottie?"

"Oh dear god," Harry complained to no one in particular.

"Hello," the ghostly Ginny said with a flirtatious wave. "You must be James, junior."

Harry saw the ghost and his almost little brother were both smiling shyly. He resisted the urge to bang his head against the wall. "Everyone who's been gaping at me stupidly throughout the day and/or is still harboring doubts, this is the Ginny Weasley of our old world. She died. And she haunts me. Ginny, this is everyone."

Lily saw the tired look of resignation on Harry's face and started to laugh at the absurdity of it all. "I'm sorry," Lily said in between her giggling. "It's nice to meet you, Ginny." She just laughed louder, intermittently pointing at Harry.

"You know Ginny is Harry's soul mate," Sirius helpfully supplied, much to the amusement of Lily. "And how does Lily get Harry so easily? It usually takes people time before they realize Harry exists to entertain us."

"She's not my soul mate," Harry insisted in a manner eerily similar to his claims that Lily wasn't his mother. He turned to his traitorous godfather. "And you're about a half step away from a midget detention, buddy."

Ginny floated over next to the highly amused Lily. "Harry's still not sure how to accept my love, Mum. You don't mind if I call you Mum, do you?"

"Not at all," Lily said, her wide grin shining. "I think you and I will get along famously."

"Ginny, go," Harry pleaded as he was metaphysically pushing her away.

Ginny could tell she was about to disappear and shook her finger at Harry. "I told you that bitch was crazy," she reiterated just before disappearing with a pop.

"Wow," Jimmy said with a grin. "I mean… wow."

Harry looked over at Sirius. "We really need to get to work on the rest of the preparations."

James shook his head and stepped forward. "Not yet. We need to talk." James Potter, family man, disappeared and was replaced with James Potter, Assistant Director of the DMLE. He strode out the door, confidently expecting the Lord Blacks to follow him.

Sirius and Harry exchanged a few uneasy looks as they were led into an empty classroom.

James sealed the door shut behind them and sent out several auror-level security spells.

Harry looked over at Sirius, and they reached an unspoken agreement to wait on James.

James was standing uncomfortably, occasionally pacing and stopping. He looked up at them and began, "I'm in something of a quandary."

"Can we help?" Harry asked.

"Yes," James asserted. "You can. Let me explain my quandary. Hypothetically, let's say I'm investigating some robberies."

Harry and Sirius stood there, not responding in the slightest.

"And hypothetically, I made a huge break in the case. But the problem is I only caught the lead, because I observed a man's surprisingly competent actions as he was saving my life and rescuing me from torture."

"That's quite a quandary," Harry said while Sirius was fidgeting and swatting.

"Oww," Sirius as he buckled away from a sharp poke in the side. "Stop it, Harry."

"It is," James agreed. "And it's even more complicated by the relationship between myself and my… leads."

Harry let up on his invisible assault of Sirius and replied. "So how can we help you with your quandary?"

"Hypothetically," James carefully pondered, "my job would be easier if there weren't any new cases to investigate. No further clues to follow up on."

Harry was swatting Sirius' hands, as he tried to poke Harry back. "You know, it's entirely possible the target of your hypothetical investigation has already retired."

"Really?" James said breaking from his cautious and careful wording.

Harry and Sirius nodded.

"No more new cases at all?" James slowly inquired. "Not even a little one?"

Harry and Sirius exchanged smiles and looked at James.

"Hypothetically," Sirius jumped in. "Is there any particular place you regret not investigating?"

James knew getting captured and tortured earlier left him feeling more vindictive than usual but didn't let that stop him. "Thing is," James explained. "These cases, they've been targeting Death Eaters. And I arrested this guy named Travers."

"Peter or Michael?" Harry questioned. He saw James looked surprised. "Both are."

"I meant Peter," James answered. "Peter's twice managed to buy his freedom with an Imperius defense, a couple names, and carefully placed donations. If ever there were a Death Eater who should be separated from his money, it'd be Peter. I didn't know about Michael."

"And this will help you with your quandary?" Sirius clarified.

"No," James said, not wanting them to think he was blackmailing them. "My quandary's been resolved. This would just make me happy."

"Retirements can be flexible," Harry replied before looking at the older man curiously. "What gave it away?"

James smiled and utilized the fine art of the back-handed compliment. "The least likely trait you'd expect from Sirius Black: he was smarter than he acted in public."

Harry snickered at Sirius' conflicted feelings.

James added, "He also managed to break into Malfoy Manor with a bit too much ease. He knew to avoid magic on Lucius, he wore specially charmed boots, a chameleon cloak, and carried illusory pins in his pocket."

Harry shook his head sadly at his godfather. "I knew you'd blow this for us."

"Says you," Sirius retorted hotly. "Mr. 'look at me, I'm Harry Potter.' Oops."

"At least my way, we were able to control the situation," Harry said, clearly not remembering the last hour very well. "Your way we wouldn't have ever even known you'd blown it for us. And who knows what would've happened then. I probably saved our asses."

Sirius listened to Harry's rationalization with a smile. "A thousand galleons says you don't believe that."

Harry pouted quietly.

James took down his privacy charms and led them back towards the hospital wing.

"I was groggy," Harry argued the earlier point. "You should have warned me."

"Didn't you see? I was flashing you the 'hey, Harry, don't forget we're in an alternate universe' sign."

James watched the two banter and bicker, and felt pangs of jealousy. He wished he'd had this rapport with Harry, but felt grateful that Harry at least had Sirius.

They arrived back to find Tonks and Jimmy regaling the others with stories of Harry's adventures at Hogwarts.

"I just remembered," James said turning to Sirius. "I've got a wand you could use."

Sirius stiffened and looked at Harry.

"It was the other Sirius Black's. Driftwood, twelve inches, I think?"

"Sounds, sounds about right," Sirius stumbled through the words.

Harry carefully stated, "In the interests of full disclosure, I should mention we kind of… already… got that wand."

"You what?" the auror side of James asked dangerously.

"We're sorry," Sirius yelped. "But it's my wand. And it was just sitting there in your safe. And you were about to give it to me anyway."

James' stern face softened to a smirk. "I know." He turned and asked the others, "Where'd Albus go?"

Sirius just stared at James' back perplexed.

Harry elbowed his godfather. "Padfoot? You just got skunked by bizarro Prongs."

"I am going to break that little man," Sirius declared as Albus came up behind him.

"You know the muggles have a pill for that now," Albus commented as he brushed past. He lifted his pensieve into the air. "Found it."

"What's going on?" Harry asked as they joined the larger group.

"Seeing as you need to work on your preparations for the auction, I thought perhaps you could leave behind a number of memories, so that we all may get to know you better."

Harry glanced at Sirius worriedly before looking at all the others in the room. "That's a surprisingly good idea. How'd one of you come up with that?"

Lily, James, and Albus all began to defend themselves, but a voice from the matron's office could be heard clearly. "It was my idea."

"Got it," Harry said in understanding. He turned to Sirius. "So what highlights should we give them?"

"Stuff like your birth," Sirius answered, "could easily be the exact same here, in which case it's just a painful reminder. I'm thinking we should give them both our perspectives of that night at the end of your third year."

"You think that's a good idea?" Harry wondered. "I mean you bit Ron's leg hard enough to break it. And Moony bitch-slapped you right after he transformed into Captain Wolf-and-whine."

"It's a great night," Sirius argued thinking of its importance to him.

"And you were out of it for most of those dementors," Harry added. "There were a fuckload there. It was bad."

"Even still," Sirius insisted. "Are you going to show when they captured you?"

"Which one?" Harry said. "If you mean the second time, hell no. The first though? Where I was a main ingredient in the Voldemort rebirth soup? That one's not too bad. Cedric died and I got crucioed a few times, but it was alright."

James saw the other Potters were as horrified as he was. "What the-"

"Fuck," Sarah finished for her father.

Sirius smiled brightly as they all got a glimpse of Harry's crap-ass life. "Are you going to show them the basilisk?"

Harry frowned at the looks on the Potters' faces. "That one seems to make people really nervous. I thought instead I'd show the end of first year, when I killed my first defense professor. That one's always a crowd-pleaser."

Peter wanted them to stop adding to his anxiety. "Why don't you just surprise us?"

"Surprise you," Sirius nodded eagerly. "I think we can do that."

Harry and Sirius took the pensieve over to a corner and proceeded to fill it with several memories, many of them triggered to play in a set order. It took them twenty minutes, but they had deposited several hours' worth of memories to peruse.

"You asked for a surprise, so the first few memories are queued up in order," Harry explained handing Peter the pensieve. "After that it's pick and choose."

Right away, Jimmy, Sarah, Tonks, Peter, James, and Lily lined up around each other and plunged into the memories.

Albus held back as he watched Harry and Sirius. "You're going to be gone before they even come out, aren't you?"

Harry nodded, slightly elated to have dodged the goodbye bullet. "We gotta do this thing."

"Oh god. Oh god. Oh God." Tonks frightened shouts startled Harry.

He saw she was still in the pensieve. "Can people talk from inside a memory?"

"In cases of extreme emotion, yes, but it is rare," Albus explained with a nod. He paused in reflection. "Just what memory did you show them?"

Sirius smiled innocently. "Well, it starts with Tonks pregnant…"

"Really?" Albus said intrigued. "Who's the lucky man?"

Harry shook his finger negatively. "We don't want to ruin the surprise."

Five loud shouts of outrage and shock came from the group at the pensieve.

Albus stumbled momentarily and began to look at the pensieve and memories contained warily. "I'm not going to like this, am I?"

"There may be a few special highlight reels," Harry meekly admitted.

"We looped your 'I trust Severus Snape with my life' with Snape's 'Avada Kedavra' like twenty, thirty times in a row," Sirius explained. "And there's even a 'Sirius, we both know it's more important that he be alive than happy.' That one really got my goat."

"Oh dear," Albus mumbled, wondering how he'd not seen this coming.

"Come on," Harry said motioning with his head. "We've got a lot of work to do tonight. Albus, perhaps we'll see you tomorrow."

"I will be there," Albus assured.

Harry and Sirius walked out of Hogwarts and down to the edge of the wards.

"You sure you're up for this?" Sirius asked. "We can postpone. It's been a long day."

Harry shook his head. "Naw, I'm ready. I'm juiced. These wards are going to take some work, but I've built up a lot of nervous energy just waiting for an outlet."

Sirius nodded in agreement.

"And I want to find out who this fucker is."

Harry patiently sat cross-legged on the floor of the small converted chapel within a clear cylindrical tube. The top was smoothly curved and it stretched all the way into the floor below, giving the tube an appearance that made Sirius giggle. He claimed it was the irony of the similarity to the After Dark Mark, but Harry wasn't convinced.

Floating behind Harry, at about eye level from his seated position, was a large shiny mirror laying parallel to the ground. A transparent film was being pulled and stretched from the surface of the mirror encompassing a crystalline display case. In the display case behind Harry's head were the three lots they were required by goblin law to present.

Enlisting the assistance and authority of the goblins to manage this auction meant a few extra risks but it was well worth the effort of earning the goblin stamp of approval, so all parties involved would know there was legitimate bait in the trap.

There were four rows of seats, four seats on each side of the aisle splitting the room in half, and every one of the seats was filled. Thirty-two middle-aged and older uninvited wizards and witches were all exchanging wary looks and inspecting the seemingly innocent meeting room.

"Welcome, welcome," Sirius cheered emerging from a side door. "I see we have quite the packed house here."

Bloodthrust was the only goblin in the room. The pleasantly vicious creature nodded to Harry and Sirius and stood off to the side near the door Sirius had used. He was eagerly anticipating the results of this auction.

"It looks like everyone coming is already here, so let's seal the doors and see if we can't avoid interruptions." Sirius looked over the podium and touched his wand on a button that in actuality did nothing other than give the appearance of a control console. Heavy duty solid metal doors appeared with the sound of creaking and stressing. Suddenly, all the sets of doors slammed shut, blocking all the windows, both side doors and the door in the back blanketing the room in darkness.

The interior lights gradually brightened, while everyone in the seats was getting a little restless.

"Oh don't fret," Sirius chided the nervous people. "Make sure you hang on to your invitations. You'll need them if we alter the customized Fidelius on the fly. Treat them like your safety blanket as it appears we may have a few uninvited guests."

"First things first," Sirius continued. "We certainly want to ensure the safety of all of our properly invited guests, and there were many protestations that it would be rude and way too easy on us to make you surrender your wands. So we found a middle ground. Harry?"

Harry turned his hands flat onto the stone floor and pushed down hard, feeding extra power into the wards.

With only a whoosh sound for warning, every guest's seat was surrounded with a clear cylindrical tube very similar to Harry's. Shouts of outrage and worry began to spread and a few attempts to portkey away failed.

Some of the people were testing the strength and knocking on the inside walls and top of their tubes, surprised to find it made no sound, but they could hear just fine.

"We've got crashers," Harry warned Sirius.

"Excellent," Sirius explained to his literally captive audience. "It appears some people are intent on getting in the way of this auction. Let's hear their grievances and see if we can't resolve this peacefully." Another faked motion of touching his wand to the podium and the front door slid open, revealing two dozen masked Death Eaters. "Is there a problem, gentlemen?"

The Death Eaters stormed into the room shouting war cries and thinking they'd overcome the wards. Many had stopped to look around the room curiously. Other than one goblin and Sirius, all the others were sitting down looking like a giant upside down rack of test tubes.

The man in the lead hesitated for only a moment before shouting "Die!" and launching a devastating blasting curse straight at Harry in his tube.

Harry didn't even blink as the bluish-purple spell zipped towards him. The magic slowed to a crawl as it neared the reflective glass and could only slide across the curved surface of the giant tube. The spell completed its circuit of the tube, picking up speed at the end, and rocketed off right back at the surprised caster.

The force of the spell had been magnified and the Death Eater's body was like a leaf in front of a cannon. The man was blown clear out of the building leaving only a pair of smoking boots behind. The thick metal doors slammed closed, crushing many thoughts of escape.

"This is so freaking cool," Harry commented from inside his tube. "It's like I could feel the magic in here. It tickles."

The more knowledgeable uninvited guests swore upon realization of the protective measures the Lord Blacks had taken.

The other Death Eaters had heard more than a few rumors about what happened yesterday, and it was no secret that a lot of their mates did not return from their missions. They had a fair idea of their Lord's expectations for success.

They watched the mission commander get roasted by a calmly seated Lord Black who was clearly more enamored to feel a tickling than he was bothered by the violent death. They spotted their inside men all looked nervous as hell and were making no motions to assist them.

The next Death Eater in line glanced over his shoulder before asking uncertainly, "Die?"

Harry's tube flickered and flashed with magic as he narrowed his eyes at the masked men. He sensed their hesitancy and calmly asserted, "I will break you."

"Oops!" the lead Death Eater said tossing his wand to the ground. "You got me."

"Coward!" a voice in the back of the group shouted.

Several more wands clattered to the ground and voices emerged. "Oops."

"Aww shucks."

"Clumsy me."

"Curses, foiled again!"

They all turned to the area from which the 'coward' exclamation had come. The lone Death Eater still holding his wand tossed it backwards over his shoulder. "Damn peer pressure."

"Smart move," Sirius commented as he walked over to a glistening anchor stone on the ground. His swished his wand over an edge of the stone and it rotated slightly. A purple beam of magic bled out the stone and connected with another glistening shaped rock. The line of magic streamed between the stones as they rose from the floor and stopped at the ceiling. Left in purple magic's wake was a solid black nothingness. "Why don't you guys walk on through there so that we can get on with our auction?"

The freshly wandless Death Eaters all looked at the mysterious darkness and then back towards the Lord Blacks. "We'll just stand, if that's okay."

Harry stared down the lead man until he swallowed the lump in his throat. He turned towards the other Death Eaters and nodded, "Excuse me, gentlemen." He calmly walked straight into the black wall and disappeared.

"You can go," Sirius nodded towards the wall, while keeping his wand ready. "Or we can make you."

"Works for me," was the response as the lemmings began to follow each other into the black wall. A couple of them hesitated, caught Harry's eye, and then changed their minds, jumping to the front of the line leading towards the unknown.

"I'm off."

"Goodbye."

"Good luck, Uncle Andre."

The last was directed to Andre Romanov, who was suddenly fidgeting inside his giant test tube, unconsciously rubbing the tattoo he was really beginning to regret.

"What have you done to them?" Albus inquired from within his own transparent penis-shaped prison.

"Nothing yet," Harry explained. He still hadn't stood up or made any ambulatory movement. "Why don't we give the Ministry workers here on undercover missions something to do?"

Sirius watched the last of the Death Eaters disappear, and saw on the quickie map he'd charmed that all twenty-three of them were accounted for and not moving. "That sounds excellent. Now I can see some of you have recognized our little protections around here and for those of you that haven't feel free to interpret your neighbor's look of fear and uncertainty as I explain this. We are on a Black property and here, for the next few hours, we've enacted some living wards. Only those genuinely invited are exempt from the negative effects of the wards, and most of those effects are currently being restrained by our unconventional use of a sentient anchor."

"I see the looks of doubt from those of you with only a passing familiarity with the law, but living wards are only illegal if they're anchored to a property. Anchoring them to a person is a perfectly acceptable alternative, since then the wards do not develop their own personality or become uncontrollably dangerous. Now that we're clear on that point, let's just see who the Ministry chose to invite without our consent."

Again Harry placed his palms flat on the ground and pushed.

Slowly, most of the seats, clear arched tube, stone floor, and all, lowered about a meter into the ground. Ten of the tubes remained firmly in place. The guests now seated with just their heads above the floor, all looked up at the people separated from them.

Without warning one of the tubes still even with the ground, shattered and the wizard within sent three quick spells towards the magical display case.

Harry and Sirius both watched impassively as the case and all its contents disappeared with a pop.

"I do believe we have an Unspeakable in the house," Sirius announced calmly as he saw the portkey on the case had worked exactly as planned. He mimicked pushing a button, and a solid wave of light magic erupted from the east wall. It slowly passed through everyone in the tubes without incident, but forcibly pushed the loose Unspeakable into the inky black wall on the other side.

Sirius smiled at how effective the living wards were. "That was rude of him."

"You attacked him!" another of the heavily cloaked individuals exclaimed.

"He was uninvited and in an ancient Lord's home. I think it's safe to say the law is on our side in this one. Not to mention we now have a legitimate threat to our property from which we must protect." Sirius explained as he walked to the floating mirror and cast a spell at it. The surface of the mirror rippled like liquid and the crystalline display case floated up and out of the mirror. The same slight veil of magic covered it as before. "Now how many of the rest of you are aurors on the clock?"

One hand went up, subtly glancing towards all the others.

Sirius shook his head. "The least you could have remembered is that you always work in pairs. Now, I should point out, aurors on the clock get to walk out the door and not pushed into the wall."

Six hands went up among the remaining nine tubes at normal height. Twenty-two tubes were still submerged, guests stuck to their seats, with barely their head above ground.

"Excellent," Sirius cheered. "Because everyone going through that wall is getting splashed with a draught of living death and encased in solid rock."

The six tubes all shattered at once and the aurors immediately took the opportunity to rise from their seats.

"You all still have your so-called invitations?" Sirius reminded, once he was sure they weren't going to attack him. "Read them."

The aurors discovered another Fidelius secret that said simply, The shed door is around back.

As soon as they were done reading, the invitations burnt themselves until even the ash was gone.

"Help yourself to anyone out there," Sirius said as the front doors spun sideways one turn and the metal doors slid up and down rather than side to side. "The Death Eaters, the highly irritated Unspeakable, and any of the rest of these dangerous trespassers we send through the wall. Bit of advice? If I were you, I'd check their arms for tattoos before administering the antidote."

There was a tinkling sound of glass-breaking and suddenly a wave of force swept through the room. Harry and Sirius were unaffected, but everyone else in the room felt like they were being squeezed and compressed, tighter and tighter.

"Oh, you are good," Harry said looking towards the would-be-thief fading into view frozen in place. The room darkened and one of the three remaining tubes at normal height lost an illusory field and revealed a jagged hole and empty tube.

Sirius walked over to the completely immobile wizard whose face was reddening and peered in the display case. "He got through the first wave but missed the muted collapsing." Sirius walked back over and tapped his wand to the podium.

"I'm impressed," Harry said nodding with respect to the man he expected was another Unspeakable. A ripple of white magic crossed the room, pushing the frozen wizard into the black wall.

As the white curtain of magic passed through the people, they felt the pressure of their tubes lessen and their bodies relax.

Harry stared at the other two Ministry workers, measuring their worth. The two tubes shattered allowing them to stand from their seats.

"You can go out that door," Harry nodded towards the aurors who were leaving. "Or that one," he said with a motion towards the black wall.

The man and the woman hurried out the front door and it sealed shut behind them.

Sirius began again. "Now I know some of you may wonder why you work for the Ministry but are still here. The answer to that I'm afraid lies in the tattoo on your arm." He made a show of tapping his wand three times on the podium.

Thirteen more tubes began to grow up from the ground leaving nine people neck deep staring at the Death Eaters carted up to their fate. Three of the men began banging and punching the walls of their tubes. Spells reflected right back on them. One older woman was begging for sympathy.

"Yeah, we don't care," Sirius said, as another white wave of magic swept from the east wall. "Tell it to the aurors."

This time, tubes and all were pushed across the room, breaking against the black wall and sending all the people in them away.

"And then there were nine," Sirius pushed a button and then all the rest of the people still seated partly underground were raised back up to the proper height.

Two tubes shattered as Harry greeted, "Albus, PJ. I don't recall your names on the guest list but I believe you may be able to help us out here."

The two older men moved over to stand next to Harry.

A portly gentlemen looked at the other six people sitting by him before asking, "Out of curiosity, just who was on the guest list?"

"Just one name," Harry happily informed them nodding his head towards the goblin. "Bloodthrust."

The goblin standing off to the side smiled grotesquely looking much like his picture.

"Now I want to know," Harry asked, still seated on the floor facing towards them, "just who would turn themselves into uninvited trespassers of an Ancient and Noble Lord's home."

There was some noticeable shifting from the people realizing what they'd managed to walk into.

"Albus? PJ?" Harry asked. "Do either of you recognize these people?"

"David Monroe," Albus said nodding to one of the two gentlemen in the back left row.

David inclined his head. "It's been a while, Albus."

"Master Monroe," Albus explained, "is a world renowned mental healer and he's been in charge of Frank Longbottom's care. I do not know why he'd be interested in this auction."

"That's Lord Charles Marbury," Peter Potter said pointing to a graying man with a shiny nose. "He's an alcoholic."

Harry looked at Peter curiously.

Peter shrugged. "I don't know what kind of details will help you."

"Harry," Sirius called out in warning. He was looking through a charmed pair of omnioculars. "Harry, you might want to take a look at this."

Sirius walked over towards Harry and reached right through Harry's tube, handing him the omnioculars.

Harry canceled the charm on his eyes and looked through the omnioculars. His first thought was to wonder why the hell Sirius had turned on the clothes-less feature in a room of old men. His next thoughts were all about the man sitting next to David Monroe with a very familiar tattoo on his arm.

"Huh," Harry said, handing the omnioculars back to Sirius. He cast another magical sight spell on his eyes and recognized a line of magic around the Death Eater's neck. Both the man and David Monroe next to him were wearing necklaces that fooled magical sight. It was only because Harry had used the same thing when he traded for Dobby that he recognized the slight but unique effect.

Harry glanced over making sure Sirius was still alert and ready. He cocked his head staring at the two men. "How the hell did you manage to sneak a Dark Mark through there?"

David Monroe stood up calmly from his seat and walked straight through the tube surrounding him. "I'm afraid that was my doing."

The man with the Dark Mark also left his tube and moved to stand protectively at David Monroe's back.

Albus stiffened and drew his wand while Peter took a step away from everyone.

All the remaining tubes shattered and the front doors opened. Harry just stared at David Monroe waiting for him to move. "I must humbly ask that everyone not invited to please leave now while I'm giving you a choice."

Albus watched the others hurry out the front door and leaned over, "You don't mean me, do you, Harry?"

Harry saw David Monroe give a slight shake of his head and answered, "I'll catch up with you later, Albus."

Albus frowned. "I'm afraid I'm going to-" He stopped suddenly as a wave of white magic crested out from the right wall.

Proving just how spry he still was, Albus galloped three brisk steps and dove headfirst out the front door, rather than allow the wave to push him through the black wall. The doors sealed shut behind him and Albus was stuck outside looking in. "Bugger."

Peter just laughed at him.

Inside the building remained only the two Lord Blacks, two necklace-charmed protected identities, and one bored looking goblin.

Harry turned to the goblin. "I don't mean to be rude, Bloodthrust, but would you-?"

"Bah," Bloodthrust grumbled as he turned to stalk out the front door. "I expected more from you, wizard. One measly death? Bah."

As soon as Bloodthrust was gone, two more tubes appeared boxing in the two unknown men.

"Who are you?" Harry said to the one with the Dark Mark while keeping an eye on the other. "I recognize the magic of your necklaces. I know those aren't your true faces. So I'm asking you, who are you?"

The man with the Dark Mark was about to remove his necklace when the glass tube around David Monroe shattered.

"Alan, wait," the supposed healer said.

Harry immediately realized he was right in that it wasn't coincidence that Alan Weston had been in possession of a horcrux.

"It'll be easier if I tell you my story," David Monroe explained, drawing Harry and Sirius' attention his way.

"You can start by removing that necklace," Harry said wanting to see this guy's face.

David Monroe frowned. "I think it may be easier-"

"Humor me," Harry urged strongly.

"Very well," David Monroe agreed. He tilted his head down and pulled the charmed-necklace over the top of his head.

Dark, messy hair was the first thing Harry could see. As the man lifted the necklace down his face, brilliant green eyes were staring back at Harry. The man's complexion got lighter and clearer. He was younger than David Monroe looked but it wasn't until the effect reached the superior smirk on his face that Harry recognized him.

Harry's brain processed it but his gearshift was stuck in neutral. He just stood there staring in shock. There were a million different things running through his mind. Each sudden insight led to another moment of clarity as another mystery unraveled.

"Fuck," Harry swore in realization. "Neville's really gone, isn't he?"

The man's pupils dilating were the only sign of surprise he showed. He had been startled at how quickly Harry reached that conclusion. "That's one way to put it."

"How else would you put it?" Harry snapped angrily.

The man nearly looked humble. "Sometimes I prefer to think he lives on through me."

"Harry?" Sirius said jumped in, staring at the man in confusion. "Did Voldemort have a kid and never tell anyone?"

"No," Harry replied, watching the man's every move. "But he did have a diary."

Chapter 28

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Author's Note: I'm not a fan of using notes to tell the story, but a number of people were confused by the eye color in the last chapter. Some thought Tom's eyes were blue, others brown, etc... I've always assumed they were green. Canon doesn't ever say anything other than red at evil times and 'dark.' But even the diary Tom in the second book mentioned he and Harry "even look something alike." Might be why I assumed green. That and the Slytherin connection. Big thanks to the folks who help me straighten out these chapters. Thanks for all the reviews. I've been a bit lazier on the replies lately, but I read and appreciate every one. Direct questions that won't be answered by the next chapter I will do my best to reply to. You should definitely start to see light at the end of this tunnel now. Just a couple more chapters (I think).

Sirius looked at the man and summarized his feelings on the subject. "What?"

Harry sighed in sadness. "It was the prophecy getting out, wasn't it?"

The man occasionally known as David Monroe nodded.

"What?" Sirius said, not following that at all. "Please, for all the slow people in the room like me and the Death Eater. What?"

"Speak for yourself, Lord Black," the Death Eater known as Alan Weston mumbled.

Sirius just stared at the Death Eater, daring him to give Sirius a reason to curse him.

"When Frank Longbottom let the prophecy get out, he opened the door for people to send Neville presents. Bloody hell," Harry said thinking back to his talk with Albus. "Why didn't anyone question it when a seven year old managed to cast an expansion charm in his backpack? It only made it that much harder to notice an old diary mixed in with all the other books."

The healthy, pleasant version of Tom Riddle shrugged. "He was the chosen one."

"Oh that's rich," Harry darkly chuckled. "Coming from you."

"So this guy ate Neville?" Sirius asked as he pointed at Tom and looked at Harry.

Tom waited for Harry to clarify, uncertain just how much Harry knew.

"Metaphysically, yes," Harry said with a nod. "The horcrux in the diary leeches the soul and life force from a naïve and innocent child and presto, new physical body in the real world for the horcrux to inhabit while little Neville's body gets cold and dies."

Sirius was still keeping his distance and pointing at the man. "I thought you said the diary had a teenage Tommy Junior."

Harry was watching Tom display some real emotions. "He sprung into the world a teenager, but that was back in, what, 88? So you're about 36 now?"

Tom made no effort to deny Harry's claim, instead he explored another avenue of conversation. "You really are from another world, aren't you?"

"Fuck," Sirius swore, still pointing at Tom. "Does everyone know about us? First Albus figures it out. Just the other day we discover Voldemort knows and now Tom Riddlebottom and his pet Death Eater are giving us shit? What the hell, Harry?"

"Tom Riddlebottom?" Harry repeated, glancing at the look of horror on Tom's face. "Oh that name's going to stick."

Tom softly mumbled, "As long as it's not on a t-shirt."

"Stop that," Harry ordered. "I'm having enough trouble reconciling the idea of a child murdering dark artifact with the mysterious fucker fighting the Dark Lord. You don't need to add in humility and a substandard sense of humor."

"If I may?" Tom politely interrupted. "I believe the Dark Lord discovered something while dueling you or shortly thereafter. It was then that he began to investigate parallel worlds. His investigation tipped off myself and most likely Albus. But I must say, until today, I didn't believe it was true."

Sirius was still pointing at Tom and looking at Harry helplessly. "Well shit."

"Relax Sirius," Harry said shifting his weight while watching Tom. "While I'd like it if you didn't get into the habit of just blurting that out, Tom here was already convinced after we knew so much about him."

Tom nodded silently.

"What I don't get though is how he's so… human. Or why he's doing this."

"Why?" Sirius repeated. "I'm just going to take a wild stab in the dark and say Dark Lords don't play nice with other Dark Lords."

Tom stood there calmly, willing to let them reason things out in front of him.

"Not just why he's opposing Voldemort," Harry said, noticing how tense but obedient the other Death Eater was. "But why he's here and making himself so vulnerable to us."

Tom saw they were waiting on him and admitted, "I'm here because I need your help and you won't give it with anything short of full disclosure. Can we speak freely here and without interruption? I'm willing to tell you nearly anything, but I'm not prepared to extend the same courtesy to Headmaster Dumbledore."

"Problems with Albus?" Harry questioned.

Tom shook his head. "He never gave me the benefit of the doubt when I was a student. I am reluctant to find out if he would understand my situation now."

"What makes you think we're any different," Harry asked.

"You're not giving me a choice in the matter," Tom explained. "But I know you won't trust me easily, so I have a suggestion."

Harry and Sirius exchanged a glance. "We're listening."

Tom squared his shoulders to address Harry. "Are you familiar with the charms of brotherhood?"

"You gotta be fucking kiddin' me," Harry grumbled in disbelief. "You want a charm of brotherhood?"

Sirius remembered when Harry explained his plan to get one from Albus and wasn't sure how much to read into That Fucker attempting to extract the same from Harry.

"I'm not willing to condone veritaserum," Tom argued. "And I doubt you would trust the results if I did agree to it."

"Perhaps you should remember you're in no position to negotiate," Harry said as the living wards sprung to life encasing both uninvited men in giant solid blocks of crystal up to the neck.

"I'm far from helpless," Tom said coldly, letting his dark side show for the first time. "And will not continue extending this kindness indefinitely."

The crystal prisons around the two men began to liquefy and melt with no visible motion from Tom as he stared down Harry.

Harry was reminded of just who this adversary was and remained alert and vigilant. "True. But as I'm sure you've noticed all of your attempts to wrest control of the living wards have failed miserably. Though I find it interesting that you and Albus go through very similar processes of trial and error."

Tom's harsh look faded into one of humble embarrassment. "I must admit I'm perplexed at that. You've protected yourself in way that eludes me." He slowly and obviously withdrew his wand and began to trace magic across his fingers. "I swear on my existence that I will not intentionally reveal either of you are from another world nor that you are the Death Eater Bandits, for as long as you permit me the courtesy of a charm of brotherhood." He finished by extending his magically glowing hand towards Harry.

"Your existence?" Harry questioned, already beginning to cast the same magic over his fingers.

"My life and magic are debatable topics as to whether they are mine," Tom explained. "Existence felt the most fitting."

Harry clasped hands and sealed a charm of brotherhood with Tom Riddle. It was a concept Harry never would have believed just a few hours earlier. "Agreed."

Both men felt the magic of the charm reacting and watched each other for any signs of deception.

Tom amicably broke the tense silence. "You are certain Albus isn't listening in?"

"Not certain," Harry shook his head. "Though I highly doubt he is. I can tell you what he's trying right now is going to fail, but he is a brilliant wizard."

"How do you know it's going to fail?" Tom inquired, knowing the likelihood of crossing wands was much lower now with the charm of brotherhood between them.

"He's basing everything off an inaccurate assumption," Harry said feeling slightly proud of his plan. "An assumption you also made."

"Care to enlighten us?" Tom asked. He noticed Alan looked uncomfortable and knew he needed to move this conversation along. When he saw the hesitancy from Harry, he added, "I've no intentions of attacking you or your wards. I'm just curious."

Harry sensed truth from the charm of brotherhood but common sense still told him not to trust this man. "I think we're getting away from the story you need to tell," Harry said, producing the usual pair of recliners for himself and Sirius.

"Understood," Tom genially replied. A slight twist of his wand produced a pair of finely crafted chairs for himself and Alan, copying the Lord Blacks. "As Harry indicated, one of the most important events leading to my existence was the prophecy getting out.

"After the Dark Lord… killed the both of you, he became intensely focused on destroying Neville Longbottom. For years he was thwarted by the protections surrounding the Longbottoms. Stories of his persistence led into rumors of a prophesized savior. When Frank Longbottom confirmed those rumors and leaked the details of the actual prophecy, Voldemort ordered all of his followers to get Longbottom using any means necessary."

Tom was speaking calmly, like a history professor patiently lecturing his class. "Fortunately for me, Lucius Malfoy had been entrusted with a diary that would ensnare any who used it. He did not know of the significance of the object, only that it was a tool for which he could earn the Dark Lord's favor."

"I," Tom paused and hesitantly admitted, "I did what I was created to do. I tricked a child into trusting me and ensnared him with promises of the greatness he could achieve. It didn't take long before Neville had made me whole again. I took his body with me and went to find the Dark Lord."

Harry felt genuine emotion from the brotherhood charm and was constantly comparing this version with his memories of the diary from his old world. "This is so fucking surreal."

"Hah!" Sirius exclaimed. "Not so much fun on this side, is it? A little dose of your own medicine."

"Excuse me?" Harry inquired. "Just what is that supposed to mean?"

"You know," Sirius said uneasily noticing how similar his godson and the strangely dignified version of the Dark Lord looked and acted. "That tone of voice where you're saying a bunch of stupid shit that's way beyond belief but still makes a twisted kind of sense."

Harry just stared at Sirius for a moment.

Sirius crossed his arms and stuck his fingers out to the side wiggling them wildly. "Invisible freaky arms?" He put a finger on his forehead and motioned it flipping up. "Avada Ke-doink!"

"Sirius!" Harry snapped. "Perhaps you'd care to share a few of your own secrets instead of mine?"

Sirius gulped. "Never mind."

Harry turned back towards the two others who were failing to keep the confusion off their faces. "Continue, Mr. Riddlebottom."

Tom frowned slightly at the name but resumed his tale. "When I located the Dark Lord, he was furious. I'm not sure why, but I stayed back and observed him. I wanted to see what I'd become, what kind of wizard and leader I was. Suffice it to say, I was disappointed.

"Electing not to approach him, instead I just watched for a few days. I saw Death Eaters cowering in fear, many of them regretting their decision to join me. I saw myself taking pleasure in punishing them. Dispensing all the blame for failures on them and never admitting my own faults. After a while, I came to a sad conclusion about the horcrux process."

Harry saw Tom had paused and was waiting. Harry glanced at Sirius before stating, "Feel free to pretend we're enraptured and are encouraging you to continue."

Tom looked disappointed but explained, "When I was made, when Voldemort made his first horcrux, I believed that I'd figured out how to make multiple horcruxes and avoid the most damaging side effect, insanity."

He took a breath and asserted, "I've come to discover that I was wrong. And thus by definition, I'm the only sane piece of Tom Riddle left in this world."

"You hear that Sirius?" Harry mocked while thinking Tom was way too calm about this. "There's a sane piece."

"Yeah," Sirius caught on to what Harry was doing. "The piece that ate Neville. You know, the good piece."

Alan Weston was bristling, clearly unhappy with the Lord Blacks, but he continued to be a civil guest.

Tom smiled sadly. "Nevertheless, I felt uncomfortable revealing my existence to the Dark Lord I'd become. I discovered Lucius was the one who sent me to Neville. He was waiting to hear if his use of the Dark Lord's 'cursed diary' was successful before sharing his plan with Voldemort. So I relieved him of those memories and planted a fake diary into his vault."

Harry saw Tom had paused again and doubtfully asked, "So that's it? You saw him being a Mr. Meany-pants and decided you'd rather frolic under a rainbow through fields of daisies with the bunnies?"

"It's not that simple and you know it. I'd appreciate it if you stopped trying to bait me, but I understand if you feel you must." Tom was rewarded by a couple of narrowed pairs of eyes and calmly explained, "I didn't oppose him at first. I wasn't helping him, but occasionally I'd toss in a new element into his plans to see how he'd respond. Simple obstacles a rational mind would overcome. Encourage a little token resistance when he wasn't expecting any. It was months before I accepted a disturbing truth: I'm much smarter than Voldemort."

Sirius didn't sound nearly as sarcastic when he commented, "Says the man fighting a stalemate from the shadows for twenty years."

"Yeah," Harry agreed, showing more curiosity than anything else. "He's held you off it seems. What makes you so sure you're that much smarter?"

Tom crossed his legs and pondered the answer. "I know if I were him, I would've figured out my identity by now. And like I said, I didn't oppose him at first. It wasn't until I discovered a Death Eater who'd gone so far as to fake his own death in an effort to get out from Voldemort's control that I began to actively oppose him." He glanced over at Alan, as the other man began to fidget in his seat.

Harry shook his head in spite of what the charm of brotherhood was telling him. "I'm having a lot of trouble buying this change-of-heart load. You were already a cruel bastard at 17. Hell, you made a horcrux."

Tom nodded. "It is a foul and dark magic, I agree. And while the costs of doing such an act may seem too high to you, the allure of a magic so powerful is undeniable. For what little it is worth, the part of the process I recall bothered me sufficiently to swear off the necessity of making more. I still have not uncovered what changed Voldemort's mind but I do know it was more than a decade before he made the second."

"And you? You've not been having any second thoughts?" Harry said, unable to resist the pun.

Tom shook his head. "Even if I sought to uncover a way around the known limitations, it would most likely cost me my rationality. I take solace from the knowledge that I cannot make one. I do not have to worry about the temptation because it is not an option for me."

Harry bit his tongue, thinking of the eerily similar words he'd used with others in regards to his defeat of his Voldemort.

Sirius saw something about that had rattled Harry and drew attention his way. "So we're just supposed to accept this change of heart stuff you're shoveling?"

"It wasn't a change of heart or pity for the Death Eater I'd just met," Tom earnestly answered, "as much as it was further disappointment in Voldemort.

"Here was a man who had faked his death but was unaware of the soul magic in the Dark Mark. Voldemort knew he was not dead and was torturing him, most likely in the same way he tortured your Bellatrix. I reached the same conclusions you did in that the Mark was permanent, but ownership could be transferred.

"As I unraveled the layers of the Dark Mark, I discovered a number of other weak spells blended into the soul magic. Compulsion and obedience charms, secondary and tertiary leeches on their magic. It was everything I despised in my youth. A follower, an ally, or an emissary should be able to think for his or herself, and at full strength, without undue influence. Obedient weak drones may be easier to control but are a significant waste of resources.

"And in spite of all those subtle corruptive magics, people were still willing to fake their deaths to get away."

Tom finished shaking his head in sadness. "I admit I felt a little lost then. Fortunately the Death Eater I'd saved and whose Mark I controlled was like a stray puppy that I'd made the mistake of feeding once."

Alan cleared his throat loudly before patting his chest innocently.

"We got acquainted with each other while he healed and he opened my eyes to an opportunity before us," Tom continued. "I had a chance to fix all the mistakes Voldemort had made and be the sort of wizard I knew I could. Inspire the people and remind them of why they followed me in the first place."

"Oh lovely," Sirius summarized. "A glass-half-full Dark Lord."

"Not a Dark Lord," Tom said shaking his head. "I've seen where that path leads. No, I intend to follow the path last taken by Albus Dumbledore."

Harry and Sirius exchanged wary looks.

"I will rise from the glory of saving the wizarding world and defeating the Dark Lord," Tom said matter-of-factly. "And I need your help to do it."

Sirius could barely believe the audacity of this man. "How's that charm working, Harry?"

"He's telling the truth," Harry assured him. "Or at least what he believes it to be."

Tom glanced regrettably towards Alan Weston before turning back towards both Lord Blacks. "Considering your noble and ancient status in this world, I feel I should mention the Death Eater, whom I saved and has helped me to forge my own path, is Regulus Black."

Sirius and Harry both froze in surprise. Sirius just kept staring at Tom, waiting for him to say something more about his bizarro little brother. Harry's gaze moved from Tom over to the suddenly nervous and fidgeting Alan Weston.

Harry lifted his arm and pointed at Alan. "You're…"

"Regulus is alive?" Sirius blurted out finally.

Tom nodded with an amused smile.

Harry saw Alan was still avoiding eye contact. "You're-"

"Harry!" Sirius interrupted, pulling his godson's arm down. "He's talking about Reggie. I think this is more important."

Tom opened his mouth but was interrupted by Sirius' yelp of pain as he slapped a hand over his eye.

"Dammit Harry!"

"Maybe if you'd let me speak," Harry snapped. "You might learn something."

"I'm talking to Riddlebottom," Sirius argued, pulling his hand down when his eye stopped stinging.

"Sirius," Harry said tiredly, noticing even Alan was looking at Sirius incredulously. "What kind of retarded Death Eater is going to have a muggle dryer?"

Sirius looked over at Harry curiously, before he gasped in comprehension. He slowly turned his head to see the Death Eater had removed his charmed necklace.

"Why you gotta call me Reggie?" he said in irritation. "You know how much I hate that."

"Reggie!" Sirius exclaimed, his face splitting into a bright grin. He pulled the reluctant and oddly older man but sort of younger brother into a hug. "Why didn't you say something sooner?"

Regulus looked at Sirius. "I had no clue who you were until after you'd broken into my place, snatched the Slytherin locket, and stolen my dryer!"

"Oh," Sirius recalled his many gently warmed bathrobes. "Right."

Regulus shrugged indifferently. "And even since then, you've pretty much been a prick."

"Shit," Sirius swore.

Harry's face split into a victorious grin at Regulus' blunt assessment. "Did you hear-"

"Shut up, Harry," Sirius snapped, knowing full well that he was on the receiving end of what he'd said to James.

Harry started to laugh. "Oh, oh, oh-"

The words were more insistent as Sirius again said, "Shut up, Harry."

Harry grinned at his godfather when he was startled to feel genuine happiness through the charm of brotherhood. He turned to Tom, who was smiling back at him.

Sirius and Regulus easily fell into their own private conversation, both excited to speak to something close to the brother they thought they'd never see again.

"So Alan Weston," Harry said turning towards Tom.

"He couldn't continue being Regulus Black," Tom replied as he levitated his chair over next to Harry. "Why don't we let those two catch up? It will allow us to take advantage of a little privacy and the protection of our charm of brotherhood."

Harry uncertainly watched the privacy dome surround him and Tom Riddle. "Uh-huh."

"You doubt my intentions," Tom said, prompting an earnest discussion.

Harry was on guard but found himself beginning to believe and trust the words of Tom. "It was more the unsubtle way you revealed Regulus' identity. Divide and conquer is the next stage of your master sales pitch?"

"I'm going to be honest with you, Harry," Tom urged while adding strength and resolve to the charm of brotherhood.

Harry sent a burst of magic to match into the charm and smirked. "Is that your way of saying you've been lying thus far?"

Tom shook his head. "There will always be differences in the truth you hear, the truth you can accept, and the truth as I see it. I've been honest so far, but that was primarily to ensure your cooperation to get to this point."

Harry nodded and listened attentively.

"I'm not a light wizard," Tom said, smiling at Harry's snort. "Nor are you a dark wizard. But if we work together… there's nothing beyond our reach."

Harry was amazed to realize this supremely confident wizard respected him for some odd reason. It was most definitely a change from any facet of Voldemort he'd seen before.

"I'm not talking about taking the world by force," Tom continued. He paused and considered the possibility. "We'd probably manage that one a lot better than Voldemort has, but I know your conscience wouldn't ever allow it. I'm talking about shaping the world we live in. A revolution known only to us."

Harry looked at Tom dubiously. "That sounds like an awful lot of work."

Tom laughed. "I've heard the vitriol you spout towards blood superiority and just about everything hereditary in our world. We share views on greatness and the beauty and power of true magic.

"When Voldemort falls, just about everything standing in our way can be painted with his brush and tainted by his association. The ills of our world can be healed and our lives can be whatever we make of them. If we work against each other, neither of us will accomplish a fraction of what we could by working together. Albus Dumbledore's time has passed. It's our turn, Harry."

Harry was beginning to see a side of Tom Riddle that would attract others. He was a man with a vision and the power to back up his words. "You seem to be presuming an awful lot."

Tom looked off into the distance. "If a junkie could foresee what his life would be, if he could see what he would look like at his worst moment, do you think he would ever take that first hit? Knowing where it would lead him, would he ever start?"

"Voldemort's not a junkie," Harry argued.

"No," Tom agreed. "But he's not who I want to be. Voldemort is the madness, I am the man. That's not someone I'll ever allow myself to be. And I hope it's not someone you'll ever let me become."

The brotherhood charm was as strong as ever. Harry clarified, "You want me to be your dark magic nanny?"

"You really infuriate Albus, don't you?" Tom said with a shake of his head. "You know what I am, right?"

Harry could think of several answers to that question but nodded silently.

"If Voldemort ever figured out who I am, or rather what I am, then he could have a control over me that I'd be powerless to resist."

Harry hadn't even considered those implications. "That's why protecting your identity is so important."

Tom nodded. "There's a way that I could be freed in case Voldemort ever got me, but it requires a horcrux. That was why Alan had the locket. Neither of us appreciated losing that as I had to move Sirius Black's skull into a place where Alan could access it."

"So you do have the skull," Harry said. "That's… that's all of them, right?"

"I'm going to try and lure the Dark Lord into a trap in about a week," Tom assured him.

"Really?"

"Your public announcement of Voldemort's horcruxes has backed me into a perilous position and one I must address sooner rather later."

"Oh," Harry realized. "Sorry about that."

Tom chuckled darkly. "Your sincerity is just oozing from the charm of brotherhood."

Harry shrugged, knowing he couldn't exactly convince him otherwise. "Why'd you show Reggie Sirius' skull instead of the ring? Just to fuck with him?"

"Contrary to your experiences with Voldemorts and Tom Riddles," Tom chided. "I do have feelings and am not a cruel, heartless man."

Harry felt slightly ashamed and saw Tom was surprised to sense the emotion through the bond.

Tom twisted the invisible ring on his left hand. "No, I'm sorry to say the ring is no longer a horcrux, thus the skull was the only active one I possessed. Had I known you were going to announce the other three horcruxes up for auction I would have spared Alan the uncomfortable experience."

Harry looked at the Slytherin family ring featuring a shining emerald resting in the middle of a silver Ouroboros. Golden claws decorated the sides holding the very lifelike snake in place. "You managed to remove the fragment without destroying the ring?"

Tom slid the ring up and down his finger a couple times. "That was not my intention, but yes."

Harry felt the nudge from the charm and inquired. "And just what was your intention?"

With a sad look, Tom explained, "I thought perhaps I could absorb the other soul fragments and become closer to a whole person. It was a mistake I was lucky to survive. I'm not going to go into it now, but the other fragments are vile and the horcruxes must be destroyed."

Harry could tell whatever happened was a big reason for his current attitude. He glanced over towards the protected display with the lots for the auction. "You sure you can't extract the soul pieces? Those are some pretty valuable old toys."

Tom shook his head. "I'm sorry, but there's no controlling where the soul fragment goes if you destroy its bindings. The one in the ring came after me and I foolishly tried to accept it.

"I've come to believe that it was Neville, and his soul that saved me and called for help."

"Neville's soul called for help?"

"That is no ordinary affliction Frank Longbottom suffers from," Tom stated darkly. "He is a good man and a good father."

"Hang on," Harry interjected. "You're telling me the soul fragment is in Frank?"

"No," Tom insisted. "It's gone. I made certain of that. But it didn't go quietly."

"You fuckers are sons of bitches, ain't ya?" Harry said recalling the horcruxes he'd destroyed.

"It attracted too much of the wrong kind of attention too. It's also the reason Alan volunteered to rejoin the Death Eaters." Tom was fiddling with the ring and constant reminder. "Even the ring hated it. It's my understanding that the ring rejected Voldemort when he put it on. And for that reason, to spite it, he turned the ring into a horcrux."

"It doesn't seem to mind you," Harry commented.

Tom shrugged. "I suspect it trusts me about as much as you do. It refused me the lordship of the Slytherin line but recognizes me as the Head of the family."

"Speaking of Slytherin," Harry questioned. "How do you plan to reconcile our differences on pureblood supremacy?"

"Differences?" Tom said. "I assumed we shared somewhat similar ideas on the value of blood." He saw Harry's frown and added, "Voldemort's only using the pureblood agenda as a means to an end. I believe preserving the ancient bloodlines are important, particularly the genetic gifts and familial magics, but I could care less whether your parents, grand-parents, and great grand-parents were all purebloods or not."

"You don't care?"

"Harry, my magical relatives were all inbred weak idiots. My mother was two steps from being a squib, but as soon as some fresh blood was introduced to such a noble and ancient bloodline, even muggle blood…" Tom trailed off and shrugged. "I may not be very humble, but I am quite intelligent and I'm easily the most powerful wizard of my generation.

"The truth is that the most powerful politically, financially, and sometimes magically tend to flock to the pureblood banner. A necessary evil Voldemort is all too eager to exploit. In the world after his fall, we can oppose issues of purity by associating them with him."

"So you oppose it?" Harry clarified.

Tom shook his head. "I believe in the importance of history. Families like the Potters or the Blacks. You're the result of a muggleborn added to the Potter line, a half-blood like myself. Blood purity doesn't matter, but the bloodlines do."

"That doesn't sound very much like your most famous ancestor."

Tom looked up sadly. "He lived in a very different time. And I suspect history has not been kind to the Slytherin legacy. I know you've mocked the unchecked hereditary seats in the Wizengamot. Maybe it's time to catch up to fourteenth century muggles and institute a House of Commons for elected Wizengamot seats?"

Harry looked at Tom warily. "This is your private little revolution?"

"I like to think of it as our revolution. Intelligent, rational wizards like us should be able to agree on mutually beneficial changes."

"Yeah," Harry said. "It still sounds like a lot of work."

Tom wore a predatory smile. "Don't worry. I've got ambition enough for both of us."

Harry let out a small sigh. "So what kind of help are you looking for?"

Tom looked up hopefully.

"I'm not saying you're getting it," Harry diplomatically offered. "Just wondering what you want from us."

"Nothing life threatening," Tom assured him. "But I need all of the horcruxes destroyed before I can kill the Dark Lord."

"Correct me if I'm wrong, but that sounds suicidal."

A ghost of a smile crossed his face. "Forgive me. I need all of the other horcruxes destroyed. Then when I kill Voldemort, I can capture what remains and lock it away."

"Lock it away?" Harry repeated skeptically.

Tom nodded sadly. "As long as I exist, he can't move on. He'll be powerless, bodiless, and locked in a prison of my own design, but he will exist."

Harry frowned. "I'm not a fan of imprisoning Voldemort. He's a bloody, tricky bugger, even if he is insane."

"The only other option is, as you said, suicide." Tom turned to face Harry and showed his dedication to survival. "And I am not willing to accept that."

Harry got the message loud and clear but didn't have to like it. "So that's it? You just want us to give you our priceless little toys so you can break them? You're not asking us to back you up when you fight him?"

"No, I don't need physical assistance, but I do need your help with legitimacy."

Harry smiled distastefully. "Makes sense."

Tom nodded. "David Monroe, renowned for his skills at healing the mind, suddenly overpowering and destroying the Dark Lord would be hard for many to believe. But when I mention that my good friend Lord Harry Black has been known to keep me on my toes, then it's far less surprising that I defeated Voldemort."

"Bugger," Harry said. "I knew beating the crap out of him in public was going to come around to bite me in the ass."

Tom smiled. "If you want, I'm willing for you to 'have played a large role in the defeat of Voldemort,' but I get the feeling you do not wish for the fame or the glory. It's going to earn Alan some recognition and amnesty. Perhaps Sirius would like an Order of Merlin third class?"

Harry looked over and saw Sirius smiling brightly while Regulus was rolling his eyes. "Maybe, maybe not."

Tom saw Harry's eyes wandering and canceled the privacy dome surrounding them. "So do we have an agreement? You provide the horcruxes and validation while I handle all the other pesky details?"

Harry pretended to slowly nod before stopping. "No."

"No?" Tom asked in surprise.

Sirius and Regulus walked over. "Reggie gave me most of the highlights. Destroy the horcruxes, kill the Dark Lord. He claims the whole thing will be over in a matter of days."

Regulus looked like he didn't mind the unwelcome childhood nickname as much as he had before. "Did I hear you right, no?"

Harry nodded and stood over by his godfather. "If we were being nice I can see us returning the locket to you guys. But we busted our ass for those other two. Padfoot, you were almost killed. And do I have to remind you of all the pussy that damn cup cost you?"

Sirius nodded in support of Harry, even if he didn't agree with him on this.

Harry could tell Sirius didn't care but insisted, "We've invested too much to just give up the horcruxes for free."

"This is to end the reign of the Dark Lord," Regulus snapped. "This isn't about profit."

Harry smirked at Tom. "Really? Because all I've been hearing is how this is going to catapult David Monroe to being the apple of the wizarding world's eye. The next Albus Dumbledore. The way I see it, Tom is planning to reap the windfall and in the process give me a few more headaches dropping my name as he sees fit."

Regulus looked upset but Tom just laughed out loud. "Damn Harry. I had you pegged as a Gryffindor but now I'm not so sure. What was your house at Hogwarts?"

Harry's mind recalled a distant memory of when he was just eleven and a hat spoke to him for the first time. He grabbed onto Sirius' arm and walked backwards, keeping his eyes and body facing Tom.

Regulus glanced at Tom uncertainly. "You'd think they wouldn't need a conference to answer that one."

Tom watched Harry and Sirius yapping away behind a silencing charm and saw both of them grinning dangerously. "I think they've come up with a price for the horcruxes."

Harry and Sirius walked back over to the other pair. Harry explained, "If you must know I was a Gryffindor but that was more my choice seeing as Albus made sure I came to Hogwarts believing all Slytherins to be evil."

"Hmm," Tom said, feeling the charm of brotherhood tingling in the back of his head. "Something tells me you should have been a Slytherin."

Sirius was smiling. "Funny you should say that…"

"We've decided on a fair trade," Harry explained calmly, thinking this would be a real test of this Tom Riddle. "You get to destroy the horcruxes and in exchange you name me the heir to the Slytherin line and pass the family ring on down."

Regulus blinked at the unexpected offer. He frowned. "And what do you plan to do if the ring rejects you?"

Tom had a calculating look on his face as he stared at Harry. "It won't reject him. I've no doubt the ring will jump at the chance."

"What?" Regulus asked.

"The only direct ancestors left are fractured souls unable to produce heirs," Tom explained, keeping his eyes on Harry. "The line is dying. Harry has already been accepted as a noble and ancient Lord once. He's young, powerful, he's defeated a Dark Lord, and he may be the only other parselmouth in the UK."

Tom was fiddling with the ring on his finger. He was disappointed in himself for not having thought of this before. It would make a lot of his future plans easier but it would give Harry further power over him. "And just what do you plan to do if you are Lord Slytherin?"

Harry sensed none of the outrage he half-expected and saw Tom wasn't dismissing the idea out of hand. "I suppose considering Voldemort, you could say I'll be restoring the name to one synonymous with greatness. But if we're being really honest with ourselves, I'll probably just use it to piss as many people off as I can. Albus will be miserable, I'm sure."

Tom's lips thinned into a tight smile as he slipped the ring off his finger and held it up. A glimmer of white magic flashed through his fingertips. "I must ask that you keep this a secret until after Voldemort is defeated."

Harry and Sirius exchanged a looks of surprise that Tom was willing to agree to their offer.

Tom was reassured by their surprise. He held the ring out. "Are you prepared to accept your new title, my heir?"

"Shit, you're not kidding," Harry mumbled. He thought over his spontaneous plan just a moment longer before pulling off his Black family ring. He accepted the Slytherin ring, glanced over at Sirius' fearful look, and slipped it on his finger.

The glistening emerald flickered black and white as a tiny golden snake appeared inside the jewel. It slithered around and froze in the shape of the letter S, centered in the emerald.

"Lord Slytherin," Sirius greeted with a bright smile.

"Lord Black," Harry greeted back.

"Lord Slytherin," Sirius repeated, liking the sound of it.

"Lord Black," Harry agreed, looking over at Tom and Regulus. He turned to Sirius and showed him the Black family ring.

Sirius caught on to the unasked question and nodded.

Harry tossed the ring to Regulus and told him, "I'm not expecting much but it's worth a shot."

Regulus glanced at Tom who shrugged in response. Regulus slipped the Black family ring onto his finger and it quickly resized to a smaller ring, indicative of a family member, not a Lord.

Sirius grinned at Harry. "My little brother is older than I am."

"I'm not calling you my Lord," Regulus warned Sirius. "And you owe me some restitution for my washer-dryer combo."

Harry smirked at Tom. "You can call me your Lord if you want to."

"This," Tom said motioning between them. "This right here is the reason I hesitated so long."

"Come on, Padfoot," Harry said jerking his head towards Regulus and Tom. "Let's be nice to our loyal subjects and allow them to kiss their Lords' rings."

"Now that we've finished our business, will you answer a few questions?" Tom gently asked.

Harry nodded.

"How did you defeat your Voldemort?"

"Oh no," Harry said shaking his head. "I may never answer that one and certainly not the day we meet."

Tom knew he wasn't going to get the answer to that one but hoped asking it would make Harry more willing to answer others. "What made you ask for the Slytherin title?"

"My sorting," Harry fondly recalled. "The Sorting Hat told me Slytherin would help me on the way to greatness. I said no back then but… second chances, right?"

Tom smiled at unsubtle reminder. "Any advice you can give me based on your original world?"

Harry and Sirius looked at each other.

Sirius answered first. "If you gotta kill a baby, always use the killing curse."

Harry grinned. "If you're unsure, it's safe to assume it's a one-time one-way portkey."

"The worst thing you can do," Sirius insisted, "is to overestimate your opponent. Trust me. They're always untalented and lucky. And alone."

"Matching tattoos to easily identify your followers are a must."

"It never hurts to reveal all your plans and leave your opponents in a complicated death trap. It's safe to assume it worked. No need to stay and watch."

"If you ever meet a snake named Nagini, just run the other way."

Tom looked at Regulus. "They're mocking me, aren't they?"

"Picked up on that, did you?" Regulus grinned back.

Tom accepted the good natured ribbing as a very positive sign. "I don't suppose you'd care to expand on your survival of the killing curse?"

"Care to?" Harry repeated. "Nope, sorry."

Tom nodded. "Perhaps then you'll share just how you've managed to keep the living wards uninterrupted?"

"Still haven't figured it out?"

Tom shook his head. "You said I've made an inaccurate assumption?"

Harry glanced around the room. He turned to Sirius. "It might be better to just let them take the display case."

"That's what I figured," Sirius nodded thinking of all the tracking and spying charms built in. He walked over towards the mirror and floating display case, casting a spell. The case sunk down into the surface of the mirror. Sirius turned to Tom and Regulus. "I'm going to want this back."

Harry had also moved over, breaking down the black portal covering the west wall. He looked over his shoulder at Tom. "Now have you figured it out?"

Tom tilted his head. "This is the first you've shown your back to me, but I do not see the significance."

Harry pocketed the ward stones that had powered both walls and looked smug. "You've been acting under the assumption that I am the sentient anchor to the living wards."

"I've seen the magic flowing into you," Tom mused aloud. "Unless… you've cloaked someone on your back?"

"A sentient anchor only has to be capable of making decisions," Harry said. "No strain from casting or maintaining the wards."

"Are you not willing to reveal who you trust so much?"

Harry felt the nudge in his back and explained. "No one will see a house elf that doesn't want to be seen. And it's hard to find a willingness to protect or loyalty stronger than from a house elf with a Master who treats them well."

Dobby's head faded into view, peering over Harry's shoulder. He smiled and nodded. "Hi, Mr. Fucker," before a snap of his fingers faded him back into invisibility.

"The magic appears to come from you," Tom commented. "And from the house elf bond you can convey all your intentions without a word. I'll admit I may not have ever considered that."

Regulus saw no one else seemed fazed but had to ask. "Did that elf just call him Mr. Fucker?" When no one answered him, he turned to Tom. "Can I call you Mr. Fucker?"

Tom paused. "Yes, provided you never call me Riddlebottom."

Regulus started and stopped a couple times. "I'm going to need to think on this."

Sirius had finished deactivating many of the security measures on the mirror and display. He carried the large mirror over towards them. "If anything happens the entire case gets portkeyed into a subspace. Every layer of the wards contains the same spell with it." He lifted up a small rock. "Here's the stone needed to access the subspace and alter the wards. Mind you there is no off switch. You have to be working the stone, while you remove the case."

Regulus looked at Tom assuring him he didn't follow that explanation in the slightest.

"Thank you," Tom said pocketing the stone and accepting the mirror. He looked at protections on the mirror. "This is an impressive piece of magic. It's nice to see someone applying their mind and talent."

"Really?" Regulus asked at the unsubtle jab. "You want to go there now?"

"I know how competitive you tried to be with your brother in your youth," Tom chided. "And now, here's something a lot like him… and he knows wards as well as anyone."

"And he has warm sheets," Sirius added.

Tom sighed as he saw Regulus was nearing another temper tantrum.

Harry looked up and warned, "You might want to put your necklaces back on because I'm about to-" He was interrupted as the entire building began shaking and the strength of gravity doubled momentarily.

"Living wards are down," Harry said, standing up from the rune inscribed corner of the floor.

The faces of David Monroe and the unknown other man were back in place just as the front doors whipped open and Albus came running in, wand up.

He swung his arm around the room, surprised to find all four people perfectly healthy and calm.

"Just a second," Harry said, closing his eyes in concentration. "Okay, portkey and apparition are down."

"Harry?" Albus asked letting his wand arm relax. "What's going on?"

"Good day, Albus," David Monroe said, gripping onto the mirror. "Harry, we'll be in touch."

Two consecutive pops indicated Tom and Regulus had apparated away, taking the horcruxes with them.

Albus recognized the significance of the frame they left with and turned around in horror. "What have you done?"

"I just took the portkey and apparition wards down. You think it's a bad idea? You're right. It is a bad idea. I'll just put them back up."

Albus' thoughts of chasing after the two others vanished and he looked at Harry in disappointment. "I thought this was all for show."

Harry stuck his head out the front door and saw no signs of aurors waiting to pounce. "Everyone gone?"

Albus nodded. "What happened to your assurances the items were safe?"

"They are safe," Harry simply stated. "PJ left too?"

Albus frowned. "He was the last to leave more than half an hour ago. Did you deceive Monroe and convince him that he has them?"

"No. Listen, we caught thirty something Death Eaters," Harry reminded with a jerk of his thumb. "For what it's worth, this is not how I expected my day to go at all. But it wasn't the kind of offer you refuse."

Albus shook his head in confusion. "Why would you put yourself in a position to allow anyone to blackmail you over something as important as this?"

Harry was smiling confidently. "Do I look like I've been blackmailed?"

"You look pretty happy to me," Sirius said while flashing Harry the all clear sign after checking the Fidelius protected shed.

"Do you even know what David Monroe plans to do with them?" Albus tiredly asked.

Harry nodded. "Yeah, I do."

"And what's that?"

Harry glanced at Sirius and shrugged. "Defeat the Dark Lord."

Albus frowned under the realization that researching David Monroe was getting more and more important. "Who is he?"

"You really want to know?" Harry asked with a grin.

Albus recognized that tone of voice. "You're not going to tell me, are you?"

Harry's voice was laced with sarcasm. "He very well may be the next Albus Dumbledore."

Albus was watching Harry. "That's not a compliment, is it?"

Harry just smiled innocently.

"Don't look at me like that, Harry. I can make your life very difficult, you know."

Harry just kept smiling.

Albus was getting worried as Sirius was smiling now too. "I'm… sorry?"

Harry was enjoying Albus' insecurity entirely too much.

"He's not going to eat me or assume my life is he? Harry! Why did your eyes widen and our brotherhood charm twitch? Harry, get back here. Harry!"

Chapter 29

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

Author's Note: Only one more short chapter (more like an epilogue but probably named CHAPTER THIRTY) to go. Big thanks to the usual folks and thanks for all the reviews. Keep them coming.

"A '78 Montrachet?" James accepted the two bottles of wine. "And a '61 Petrus? Are you trying to impress me?"

Harry and Sirius shook their heads. "You invited us to dinner. We figured we should bring the wine. Are these bad ones?"

James looked at the exorbitantly valuable bottles. "You have no idea about wine, do you?"

"Not a clue," Harry admitted. "We've got a whole bunch more if you want to come pick something better."

"Something better?" James repeated doubtfully. "Harry, these bottles are worth a small fortune. I can't accept these."

"Forget accepting them," Sirius said. "Let's drink them."

"I'm not surprised they're valuable." Harry leaned closer and whispered, "There's a good chance they came from a magically warded display case in Peter Travers wine cellar."

James blinked as he looked back down at the two bottles in his hands. He squelched his first instinct to take them in as evidence. He glanced over his shoulder before whispering back, "Already?"

Harry nodded.

"Why haven't I heard anything about this?" James wondered.

Sirius asked, "How many robberies have you attributed to the Death Eater Bandits?"

"Eight," James replied.

Sirius smugly added, "And what happened to anyone who reported a robbery?"

Harry happily explained, "Public perception says anyone targeted by the Death Eater Bandits must be a Death Eater. That's probably why less than half of them were even reported."

James couldn't stop the vindictive smile from spreading across his face. He looked back down at the wine in his hands. "I'm going to enjoy drinking these. Come on in, guys."

Harry and Sirius hung their cloaks on the stand by the door, walking into Potter's home as guests for the first time.

"They're here," James shouted loudly.

It sounded like a stampede coming around the corner with Sarah and Lily in the lead. Lily arrived a split second before Sarah, as the two slammed into Harry's body with a double thud. They both were desperately hugging the life out of them.

Harry hadn't even caught his breath before Tonks was embracing him too. He saw Jimmy smiling at his discomfort before he also joined in the smothering group hug.

"See!" Sirius exclaimed. "I told you that cologne was every bit as good as the brand name. Trust the power of the Pad-nose."

Harry sent out an invisible arm and flicked the aforementioned Pad-nose. Harry then used his invisible arms snaking all around the mass surrounding him and patted everyone on the back. "There, there."

"Shut up, Harry," Lily ordered in between sniffles.

"Okay," Harry weakly said, not taking much comfort from the sudden group hug. "But a little reminder: I grew up in a cupboard. Not a big fan of tight enclosed spaces."

The Potter family and Tonks all disentangled themselves and gave Harry room to breathe.

Harry relaxed and smiled at the expressive show of emotion. "I don't mean to sound ungrateful but what can I do to avoid that happening again?"

"Oh Harry," Lily said, fighting back tears as she thought of her time in the pensieve. "The things you… and when you had to… and when she… it was the most heart-breaking thing I've ever-" her words finally crossed into truly unintelligible gibbering. She lunged forward and hugged Harry again.

Harry resigned himself to holding on to Lily Potter for a little while and shifted her to the side, so he could talk with the others. "Let me guess, the Mirror of Erised?"

Lily let out a small wail and Tonks and Sarah latched onto Harry again.

"Oof-kay," Harry said, slightly more prepared than the first time. He was patting them all on the back with invisible arms. "I feel it's only fair to remind you that I was eleven when my parents and family were what my heart most desired. So we're talking years before I ever learned about the Feast of Satiation and how once every four years an entire colony of Veela goes into a frenzied lust for one very magical weekend."

"That's just a rumor," Sirius insisted, giving Harry a significant look.

Harry smiled at his godfather. "Sure it is," Harry said as he tapped his nose with his forefinger.

Smiling back, Sirius mirrored the gesture, tapping his nose with a silent nod.

Lily was still hugging Harry as she wryly commented, "If only you'd had a mother, you might not have been such a pervert."

"Somehow, I doubt his godfather would have let that happen," James said with a grin. He quickly clarified, "I meant he'd still be a pervert. Not that he'd kill Harry's mother."

Harry scrutinized his godfather. "Let's not be hasty and rule anything out just yet."

"Prison changes a man," Remus added from the side in a faux raspy voice.

Sirius faked a look of emotional pain. "Moony! Making fun of my most painful and private moments?"

Remus growled. "I owe you both for the crap they've been giving me. You promised never to tell anyone about my evil pedo twin."

"But we didn't tell anyone," Sirius argued. "I intend to keep honoring that promise. Besides Moony, I'm sure you can imagine some of the things we could have put in there."

Harry was finally released from Lily's grip as he turned to Sirius. "Have you been holding out on me?"

Sirius shook his head. "I was thinking of this world and how I've accidentally walked in on-"

"Nine times is not accidental!" Remus snapped.

Lily sighed and pleaded, "Can we please at least pretend to be responsible adults and not discuss our perversions or homicidal tendencies for one night? Just one."

James laid a comforting hand on his wife's shoulder. "I think we can manage one-"

A loud extremely high-pitched shriek interrupted James.

Sirius winced. "Someone step on your house elf's tail?"

"House elves have tails?" Jimmy asked in confusion.

Sirius frowned. "How else are they supposed to eat?"

"Nappy!" James called out interrupting the surreal byplay.

"Yes'm, Massa," Nappy replied as she appeared. "I din't mean fo' choo t'hear dat. Iza sorry, Massa."

"Are you okay?"

Nappy nodded her head.

"But you screamed."

"Yes'm, Massa. Iza sorry fo' dat."

Lily tried to sound gentle. "Why did you scream?"

Nappy looked embarrassed. "Choo know how Iza like pickin' cotton."

Lily translated for the others. "She's referring to the lint trap in our Magi-wash-n-fluff. Nappy uses it as stuffing in the wonderful pillows and quilts she makes."

"Yes'm, Miss Lily," Nappy agreed. "I makin' a quilt and was pickin' my cotton. Iza just startled and screamed. I din't mean to int'rupt cho' evenin'. Iza jus' gonna put the finger back and not be askin' no questions."

"What?" Lily snapped in surprise.

"What?" Peter Potter said as he and the Headmaster approached the welcoming party.

James was remembering a bit of paperwork he'd put off and forgotten about. "Oh… crap."

"James?"

Sirius just started laughing. "It's Malfoy's, isn't it?"

"What?" Albus snapped in surprise.

"What?" Jimmy asked in confusion.

James looked slightly embarrassed but not all that upset. "With everything going on that day, I guess I just… forgot."

Harry looked way too happy, holding in his giggling. "You forgot you had Malfoy's finger in your pocket?"

James saw the looks his wife was giving him as he shrugged helplessly.

"Hang on!" Sarah shouted. She turned to her little brother. "So when my whites came out pink that really wasn't a prank?"

"I told you I had nothing to do with that," Jimmy insisted.

"I think I'm going to be sick," Sarah said running off to change and burn some of her clothes.

"Sorry honey," James called out to his pale little girl. He saw the looks of horror and amusement on others' faces as he turned to the squat, frowning elf. "And sorry to you to, Nappy."

Nappy waved her hands in the air in distress. "Choo da Massa. I da Nappy. Choo don't hafta apologize to me."

James saw his wife still looked pretty upset. "I know, I know. Always empty the pockets before putting it in the dirty laundry. But it was a big day."

Sirius noticed Lily was still speechless and asked, "If you're not using the finger, do you think-"

"Eww," Harry said swatting his godfather on the arm.

"What?" Sirius argued. "It's a collector's item. There can't be more than nine others like it in the world."

Harry sighed. "Think about where that's been."

"It's probably clean and snuggly soft by now," Jimmy argued.

"It's da size of a baby's arm," Nappy supplied.

Lily was beginning to lose hope that this was going to be the perfect family dinner she'd envisioned for this evening.

"I'm sorry but that finger is going into evidence," James assured Sirius.

Albus cleared his throat. "Would you mind perhaps explaining why you have Malfoy's finger?"

Everyone turned to look at Albus, displeasure on their faces.

Albus sighed. "How many times must I also apologize for my evil pedo twin?"

"That's it!" Lily yelled. "No more evil pedos, no more severed fingers, no more homicidal tendencies or… what was the other one?"

"Perversions," Remus helpfully supplied.

"No more talk of perversions either! I want a pleasant, family dinner. Anybody got a problem with that?" Lily slowly swiveled her head from side to side, daring the others to speak up.

They had all pasted smiles on their face as they nodded at Lily.

Harry leaned closer to her and softly joked, "It's okay to cry, you know."

Lily let out something in between laughter and crying and took the opportunity to hug Harry once again.

"Okay," Harry said accepting the unexpected hug. "I was just trying to be funny. You really shouldn't cry. It makes people uncomfortable."

"Shut up, Harry," Lily said, intentionally hugging him harder. She let go and walked over to her husband. "I think we need wine."

"I'll get the…" James trailed off at the look on Lily's face. "I mean I'll give you the wine and go take care of the… thing."

"Smart man," Lily said grabbing the bottles and leading the rest back towards the dining room.

Albus waited for the others to pass and pounced on Harry. "I was hoping you might shed some light on a few of the mysteries surrounding David Monroe."

Harry waved his godfather on and looked at Albus. "Jumping right into it, eh?"

"The longer I keep you, the more I risk your mother's wrath," Albus explained.

Harry darkly laughed. "Why are you the last one to keep calling her my mother?"

Albus frowned. "What would you prefer I call her?"

"Lily, Mrs. Potter, master, whatever you want," Harry said with a shrug of his shoulders. He saw Albus wanted a better explanation. "Yes, I mean Lily is family, as are all the Potters. And there isn't a good word for our relationship, but you're insulting my real mother every time you call Lily that."

"My apologies," Albus said slightly shamed. "Now please stop stalling with your attempts to get me into trouble with your evil pedo twin mother."

"That'll work," Harry cheered thinking 'evil pedo twin' was a sufficient qualifier for calling this Lily Potter his mother.

Albus was beginning to think he wouldn't be getting any decent answers tonight. "Harry."

"Yeah?"

"David Monroe?"

"Interesting fellow." Harry grinned. "Very interesting."

Albus sighed and whispered conspiratorially, "Will you at least confirm if he is the mysterious wizard in black?"

Harry's voice dropped to a mocking whisper. "Will you at least call him by his proper name?"

"That Fucker," Albus quickly added. "Is David Monroe that fucker?"

"No," Harry said.

Albus blinked. "He's not?"

"No," Harry corrected. "I was answering the first question. No, I won't confirm it."

"Harry," Albus frowned, knowing without a doubt that David Monroe had to be.

"You told me you were blissful in your ignorance," Harry reminded. "Why would you want to lose all that safe protection of the sand surrounding your head in the ground?"

"Harry," Albus said, wondering just how many meanings and emotions he'd managed to use with that single name.

"Okay, let me put it this way: you know more than a fair share of my secrets and you know why it's important that they stay secret."

Albus nodded.

"David Monroe, as I'm sure you've guessed, also has a number of secrets that should stay secret."

"He's from a-"

"Don't even try to guess," Harry interjected. "Just don't."

Albus sighed in frustration, thinking of his distinct lack of options.

"Listen," Harry said. "You remember how Tonks and Remus trusting me was enough for you at first?"

Albus nodded.

"Same thing," Harry said sending magic into the brotherhood charm he shared with Albus. "Have a little faith in my judgment."

"So you trust him?"

Harry chuckled. "About as far as I could throw him."

Albus sighed.

"Okay, maybe not even that far."

Albus took a breath and tried to salvage something positive from this discussion. "I understand you don't trust easily, but you at least believe him to be a good man?"

"No," Harry blurted out way too quick for Albus' liking. "A good man? Hell, I don't even think I'm a 'good' man."

Albus just glared.

"It's a switch I can flip on occasionally," Harry admitted. "But David?" Harry saw Albus was desperate. "For what it's worth, while I might not buy his motivations, I do believe that David is trying to be something of a good man."

Albus latched onto that as solace and nodded.

"Or rather he's trying to do good things," Harry clarified. "We are who we choose to be, right?"

Lily Potter cleared her throat loudly. She was standing in hallway, holding two glasses of wine.

"Sorry about that," Harry said to Lily as he accepted the offered glass of wine. "It was his fault."

"I know," Lily said holding out the other glass for Albus. "Drink your wine, Headmaster."

Albus double-checked the hidden bezoar he kept in his false tooth and warily took the glass.

Lily glanced over her shoulder as Harry hurried towards the dining room. "Harry sure likes getting you in trouble."

"He most certainly does," Albus agreed subtly casting detection spells on the wine. "And you know it only works because you allow his-"

"Don't," Lily warned.

Albus wisely stayed quiet and took a sip of the wine.

"I know you're not the one I'm angry with. But if nothing else perhaps you'll learn to never place an orphan with people like my sister."

Albus was quietly mumbling into his glass. "You were the one who gave him the blood protection."

"What?" she snapped dangerously.

"Nothing," Albus quickly exclaimed. "Lesson learned. No role in child placement without many, many layers of accountability."

Lily nodded in agreement.

Albus began to walk with Lily towards the dining room. "Perhaps, Harry's former Headmaster relied too much on your brilliant advice and counsel in those sorts of matters."

Lily looked at him curiously. "You know, if you want to distance yourself from Harry's former Headmaster, I'd advise against rationalizing his actions for him. But the sucking up to me is a nice touch."

Albus smiled in amusement. "I can see where Harry gets his bluntness from."

"Don't push it," Lily warned, making it clear he wasn't out of the doghouse yet.

"Check it out," Jimmy said pointing towards Nappy's glazed over eyes. "Harry can obliviate house elves."

"Obliviate," Harry cast yet again on the poor elf. "Stop saying that."

Lily looked up in surprise. "I didn't think it was possible to memory charm a house elf."

Nappy looked up. "Choo can-"

"Obliviate," Harry cast once more. "Stop! Or I'll start casting them on everyone."

"It's cool!" Jimmy defended.

James came in from the back way. "What'd I miss?"

"Harry can-mmph-mmph," Jimmy was cut off as a buttery roll floated up and was crammed into his mouth.

"Nothing," Harry said. "Just… nothing." He saw Jimmy was now calmly eating the roll. "Jimmy's got the right idea. How about we eat?"

The large group settled into the lengthened dinner table and several of the dishes started to get passed around. Sirius leaned over towards James asked, "So you took care of the thing?"

James chanced a brief glance at his wife and told Sirius. "It's gone. Give it up."

"But I wanted to-mmph-mmph," Sirius's whining was cut off by a roll as Harry saw Lily was getting irritated again.

James grabbed a roll of his own and commented. "You like to use those arms, don't you?"

"They have their uses." Harry couldn't help but want to show off. Food from all around the table floated into perfect place onto his plate. "I can be a terror in a food fight."

Lily shook her head with a smile. "I shudder to think of the-"

She was interrupted by the sudden splat of mashed potatoes smacking Harry in the back of the ear. She saw the guilty party at the other end of the table. "Peter!"

"What?" Peter defended. "He was practically asking for it. Thinking he could take on all of us at once."

"I never said that," Harry insisted as some hot gravy was poured down an unprepared Peter's back.

"No," Lily shouted. "I will not have this evening descend into-" She stopped suddenly as an olive tweaked her nose.

"Oh… crap," Jimmy muttered under his breath.

"James Edward Potter, Junior," Lily said breaking out the full name.

"Dad hit me first!" Jimmy pleaded pointing across the table.

"You're grounded," James retorted in lieu of an empty denial.

"I'm still in school."

Lily had reached her breaking point and drew her wand. She clenched a fist around the tip and slammed it down on the table. The magic reacted instantly and every plate in front of a guest jumped up and flew into their respective faces and laps.

Lily smiled at all the indignant shouts. "I feel much better now."

Harry looked up from the food covering his front and smirked at Lily. "A worthy opponent I see."

"I did not do this to-ohhh…" Lily trailed off into a shocked gasp as the bottle of wine floating over her head proceeded to pour its entire contents into her hair and down her favorite dress. "It's on now."

With a whip of her wand, two still warm pies came arcing in, circling around the group and zeroing in on Harry from two sides.

Two invisibles punches sent steaming peach and blackberry filling splattering into all directions.

Sirius just grabbed the two glasses in front of him and simultaneously threw their contents into the faces of Harry on his right and James on his left.

Albus, not one to miss an opportunity, sent out an animated army of chicken wings marching down the table. The chicken wings were pouring salad dressing into a miniature trebuchet they'd fashioned out of a ladle and a napkin holder.

Sarah and Jimmy were focused on tossing anything they could get their hands on at Harry. Jimmy saw how pointless their efforts were as everything bounced back towards them. He noticed his sister wasn't paying him any attention and transfigured an ear of corn to look like a swollen rotting finger.

Timing it as a hail storm of peas bounced back at them, Jimmy subtly levitated the finger right in front of his sister's dress and jammed it into her awaiting cleavage.

Sarah looked down and saw the discolored finger pointing up at her accusingly from between her breasts. She started to shriek. She toppled wildly out of her chair and scrambled back trying to get away. She was pulling on the offending digit but her grip slipped and she cleanly knocked herself out leaving a small dent in the wall where her skull hit.

Everyone paused for a moment to observe the first casualty.

"For wanting to be a healer, that was pretty pathetic," Jimmy commented.

Tonks admitted from the other side, "In fairness I saw what you were doing, and I might have hit the finger with charms to lock it in place and wiggle constantly."

The pause in fighting lasted only until another ladle full of dressing splattered onto Harry's shield.

Albus snapped his wand and the chicken wings all fell lifelessly where they were. "I see cooler heads have-" His declaration was cut off as a giant amorphous jelly monster had appeared behind Albus and fallen forward. The headmaster's entire upper torso and head were submerged inside the dark green gelatinous blob.

Albus barely opened his eyes and saw the world was tinted green. He closed them in concentration and appeared to vibrate in place. The resulting green jelly explosion coated the walls, ceiling, and everyone else, shields and all in a sticky soppy mess.

"Get him!" Lily shouted with a renewed fervor as a pie knocked the back of Albus' head forward.

What had started as a chaotic battle quickly turned into a bloodbath, a gravy bath, and an au jus bath. Albus made no offensive maneuvers and hunched down letting everything hit him. He hid his face behind his arms resting on the table.

The good natured food fight offered the Potters an opportunity to vent some of their anger for Dumbledore's counterpart on the old man himself.

Harry spotted the crafty magic at play and moved over towards the wall where the real Dumbledore was invisibly observing. "Not going to sneak away, are you?"

Dumbledore knew he'd been spotted as he watched the others laying into his hastily transfigured body double. "This is you and your manipulative memories' fault."

"They're just memories," Harry argued with a grin. "A little unvarnished truth from my life experiences."

"Yes and arranged to play in a devastatingly precise order," Albus commented. "The Mirror of Erised at the end was a masterstroke."

"Sirius talked me into that one," Harry agreed. "I thought it felt a little too Dumbledore-ish for me."

Albus sighed at having become an unflattering adjective. He canceled his invisibility spell and attracted the others' attention as he loudly asked, "Are you about done?"

One last conjured pineapple clunked off the illusion's head.

"Sorry," Remus said meekly having been the last one to stop. "Mob mentality and all."

Albus frowned knowing he definitely would have bruised from that pineapple. "And do you feel any better?"

"Yes, much," Lily happily concurred.

"I do," Tonks nodded in slight surprise.

"That was fun," Jimmy agreed. "Especially since Sarah missed most of it."

James was already casting a simple bruise-relieving charm on the back of his daughter's head. He helped to her feet while Albus reversed his double's transfiguration.

Lily was looking at the carnage everywhere, including the green jelly dripping from the ceiling. She grabbed a handful of her own hair and squeezed. A small stream of wine dripped out and into her empty glass. She lifted her glass in salute to Harry and drank it.

"Eurgh, that's horrible," Lily announced, wincing from the taste.

"Pretty disgusting from this side too," James added.

Sarah extricated the ear of corn from her chest and dropped it down her little brother's back. Jimmy's hair and front were covered with mashed potatoes. He just shrugged indifferently at the corn pressing into his back.

Sarah picked a couple of kernels from her cleavage and warned her brother, "I'm going to make you rue."

Jimmy begged. "It wasn't that big a-"

"Rue!" Sarah shouted.

Remus saw Harry and Sirius looked lost. "Jimmy's first detention with Snape was to write lines. Three rolls of parchment of I shall rue the day I ever met Severus Snape. Since then it's kind of…"

Sirius couldn't help himself. "He's a rued bastard."

"Oh Merlin," Harry groaned. "Pardon me, Lily, but…" He paused and used a pair of invisible arms to yank the chair right out from under Sirius.

Sirius's tailbone hit hard and he yelped in pain.

Lily had finished dabbing her face clean and admitted the obvious. "It appears we didn't prepare enough food."

"You know I don't think it's the amount as much as it is us," Harry suggested.

"Is this how most of your dinner parties go?" Lily asked while brushing a deviled egg off her shoulder.

"The good ones," Harry agreed. "And besides it's hard to call this a dinner party when we're all family." He paused a beat and added, "And Albus."

Albus cleared his throat and retorted, "I believe you'll find we're brothers in magic."

Lily stood up from her seat. "How does sandwiches and beer sound?" She received nods of approval and continued, "You can take turns cleaning up and meet me back in the kitchen."

"Sounds perfect," Peter heartily agreed, knowing his entire left side was still coated in green jelly.

James explained, "There are two showers upstairs and one downstairs. Sirius, there's a hose out back."

Harry chuckled and moved to follow Jimmy towards one of the bathrooms.

"Nappy!" Lily called out.

The elf popped into the room and had her mouth open before she took in the current state of cleanliness. Nappy just looked from Lily to James to the walls to everyone else. She was making a little keening sound and appeared to be nearing a breakdown.

"Relax Nappy," Lily tried to comfort the elf. "We're going to leave this room, and you can clean it at your leisure. No rush, no pressure. We're going to help ourselves and stay in the kitchen."

Nappy was taking quick and frantic breaths, unsuccessfully trying to calm herself. "Can Iza sing, Miss Lily?"

Lily smiled at the kind-hearted creature. "Of course you can, Nappy."

Nappy looked at Lily pleadingly.

Lily nodded and could tell Nappy was eager to get to work. "Alright, everybody out. Let's stop bothering poor Nappy."

Wet squishing sounds accompanied every step as they all filed out of the dining room, away from the tiny creature waving them on.

The doors closed behind them and a deep voice was heard from the edible battlefield. "Swing low, sweet chariot…"

Harry took a bite from his roast beef sandwich and elbowed his smiling host. "I know this probably hasn't lived up to your expectations, but I like this more than a formal dinner."

Lily smiled at Harry. "Why is that?"

"The food may not be as fancy, but it's more intimate." Harry took a sip of his beer. "The formality of entertaining guests versus the familiarity of friends and family."

"You know you're welcome here anytime," Lily offered.

Harry nodded in gratitude. "If you don't mind, I'd like to put up a ward or two. Secure it a bit more and let me know if anyone tries to attack here."

"You're pretty good with wards, aren't you?"

Harry shrugged. "I know a bit. One of those side effects of my life."

"Harry," Sirius shouted out in between giggles. "Have you seen today's Quibbler?"

"Oh dear," Lily muttered as she saw all the others were crowded around a copy of the eccentric periodical.

"What is it?" Harry asked warily.

"Another supposed conquest of yours that I dearly hope is polyjuice," Lily said distastefully.

Harry accepted the paper and saw the magically moving photo on page eight. "That's my bedroom," he said as he saw his half naked body sleeping. The covers over his legs shifted and Delores Umbridge's surprised face came up from between his legs and looked right into the camera, before burrowing back under the covers.

The scene repeated over and over, with Umbridge looking surprised each time.

Harry growled at the unsubtle laughing. "Oh Tonks?"

Tonks was cowering behind her adoptive father as far from Harry as she could. She softly asked, "Yeah?"

Harry grunted at the extra effort in the distance but yanked her to float right in front of him.

"It wasn't me!" She insisted.

Harry looked back down at the small print by the photo. "Photo courtesy of Tonks Poopin?"

"Okay it might have been me."

Harry growled.

"Parley! Truce! Uncle!"

"You're not a pirate and your only uncle is Lucius Malfoy." Harry belatedly added, "Or perhaps your dad."

Jimmy and Sirius both found that addition and Remus' reaction particularly amusing.

"Truce, Harry, truce," Tonks begged. "Can't we all just get along?"

Harry narrowed his eyes. "You have more pictures, don't you?"

"Tons," Tonks happily agreed. "There's this one where Snape's hair is tickling your nose and it looks like you're petting him."

"Tonks!"

"Truce!" she insisted back.

Harry saw the eager looks on the others' faces and set her back down. "I'll agree to a temporary cessation of hostilities while I figure out suitable terms for a truce."

"Done," Tonks agreed. "But I'm not doing a midget detention."

"No, no midget detention," Harry agreed. "You need something special."

Lily saw Harry's devious smile. "There's a lot I don't know about you."

Harry chuckled and looked up in surprise to see his owl at the window. "Kid Killer McGee? You got something for me?"

The owl hooted as the window opened and flew over to land on the counter in front of Harry. He stuck out his leg and waited until Harry untied the letter before pouncing on the roast beef sandwich in Harry's hand.

"Were you expecting a letter?" Albus asked as he watched Harry casting diagnostic charms on the sealed parchment.

Harry looked at Albus and shrugged. "I don't know that many people beyond those in the room."

Harry detected some unknown magic in the parchment but it wasn't on the whole paper just a small spot. He unrolled the letter and discovered a string sprouted near the bottom left corner sticking out a couple of inches from a small magical seal.

"There's a string coming out of the parchment," Harry said seeing if anyone else recognized the spell.

Sirius could tell Harry wanted a response. "If it's anything like a passed out drunken hag, trust me, you don't want to pull on that string."

"Oh god, I'd forgotten about that," James cringed remembering a trip down Knockturn Alley the summer after his first year.

Harry did his best not to think about that and read the letter silently to himself.

Harry,
I suspect you'll have more use for this than I will. It never liked me much but as you know well, it makes a powerful tool to use against its brother. Nevertheless, I am now in possession of an excellent yew wand that likes me far more than this one ever did. I suppose it's also worth noting that my yew wand's previous owner is secure in his cage. Brothers in magic and brothers in wands, eh?

We'll be in touch.

-David

Harry blinked as he took in the meaning of the letter. He looked up and saw no one else could see the contents before inspecting the string excitedly. He grabbed onto it and carefully tugged. The small circle around where the string connected lit up in a white hot fire and a holly wand was erupting out from the surface as he pulled the string up.

"I have got to learn this spell," Harry commented highly impressed at the magic involved. Just as the full eleven inches were out the seal on the parchment and the string disappeared. The wand began to fall.

Seeker reflexes kicking in, Harry snatched it out of the air. "Ohhh," Harry groaned in release as the comfort of his first wand reacted to his magic. His eyes were shut in contented bliss. A geyser of red, white, and gold sparks streamed from the tip. It lasted several seconds before slowing to a trickle. "Oh-oh," Harry grunted again as another couple of spurts shot out the tip.

"That was disgusting," Sarah summarized for all those watching.

"Ahh," Harry said one last time a two more dribbles of magic oozed out the tip of his wand. "That's the stuff."

Albus suddenly put two and two together. "He obliviated Ollivander."

Harry didn't feel like implicating the man just yet and flashed a smirk at his godfather. Harry turned to Albus with a determined expression. "I think it's time I joined the Order."

"Really?" Albus said in surprise. "You were waiting on the wand?"

"Sure," Harry shrugged indicating that had nothing to do with it. "But only until Voldemort is defeated."

Albus blinked. "Of course. The Order will be disbanded after the Dark Lord is gone."

"So…" Harry trailed off. "Don't I get a merit badge or something?"

Albus frowned. "I'll introduce you at the next meeting but it's nothing so formal. The only identifiable characteristic is one of these." Albus floated his personal chocolate frog card into Harry's hand.

Harry thought the holographic picture of Albus had jammed his beard in his ear, but it moved too fast for him to be sure.

"Potter! Are you there?" A shout came from the fireplace in the other room.

"Kingsley?" James asked hurrying into the next room and spotting the bald auror's head in his floo.

"The Dark Lord is dead! Get to the Ministry. I've got to track down Albus next." Kingsley's head disappeared before James could say another word.

"The what is what?" James repeated in disbelief.

"The what?" Albus shouted from the kitchen.

"I believe he said the Dark Lord is dead," Harry said with a grin while still inspecting the chocolate frog card. "And may I say, it's been a pleasure being a part of the Order, but I'm glad that chapter of my life is over now."

Albus was too flustered at first to properly respond.

James hurriedly kissed his wife on the cheek and promised to be in touch. He apparated straight to the Ministry.

Albus looked at Harry standing there calmly. "Harry? Is this…"

Harry nodded with certainty as the chocolate frog card in his hand flared to life.

"Headmaster, err, Lord Black?" Kingsley Shacklebolt corrected himself in obvious confusion.

"Relax, Kingsley, I'm part of the Order," Harry assured him with a smile.

"Right," Kingsley warily agreed. "Where's Albus?"

"I shall summon him immediately," Harry pompously replied as the chocolate frog card was wrenched from his hand.

"Give me that!" Albus loudly pouted. "I'm here."

"The Dark Lord is dead! Voldemort was going after the Minister's daughter but David Monroe protected her and killed him with a lucky shot! Mad-eye's testing what's left of the body now." Kingsley's head turned to the side. "I've gotta go. There's a secure floo to the site connected from DMLE headquarters."

Albus just nodded at the chocolate frog card as it deactivated. He looked over to Harry expectantly.

Harry was content to act nonchalant. "So do Order members get like a pension or something?"

Albus sighed and apparated away.

Harry glanced around the room before turning to Sirius with a glint in his eyes. "You know, Padfoot…"

"I like that look in your eye," Sirius exclaimed, grinning excitedly.

Harry was smiling while the others were still struggling with the shock of the Dark Lord's sudden defeat. "I was just thinking this calls for a celebration."

"Yeah?" Sirius asked hopefully.

Harry nodded. "We should throw the party to end all parties."

"Who were you thinking on inviting?"

"Well," Harry admitted and scratched his head. "I was thinking we should invite… everyone."

"Everyone?"

"Everyone."

"Grimmauld Place?"

"Say about two to three hours to set everything up and let the good news spread?"

"I bet we could get Gin to close her doors and sell us her current inventory."

"The twins could probably help put together a light show or two."

Sirius was smiling so brightly his face looked like it would split. "I remember how things were the first time when I was hunting Wormtail. Ministry Obliviators are going to hate us."

"That's why they're invited too," Harry grinned.

Sirius was running through ideas in his head. He jumped up and jerked his head. "Well come on. We've got work to do."

Harry turned towards the still stupefied Lily Potter. He leaned over and kissed her on the cheek. "Thank you for a lovely dinner. But it looks to be a long night."

Harry and Sirius happily marched out of the room, off to hastily arrange the party of the century.

Lily, Remus, Tonks, Peter, Jimmy, and Sarah were all still standing around slowly comprehending the magnitude of the news.

"Voldemort is… dead." Lily tried out the words.

Jimmy nodded and voiced the only question on his mind. "What do you wear to a 'dark lord defeated' party?"

Harry and Sirius didn't have enough time for all of their grand plans, but they did create a giant circular dungeon room with no visible doors or windows that served as the primary dance floor, hire a DJ, enchant several trampolines illegally, steal all of Hogwarts school brooms, hide the second and third floors of the manor, ward the entire property from muggle notice, magic a massive hole through to the roof, and conjure a few hundred masks for anyone who wanted them.

The masks were of Voldemort's face locked in a look of surprise with "I'm so dead!" branded across his forehead.

The immense circular room was Sirius' project. It was big enough to fit the Burrow stacked twice within the room. All the walls were charmed to show memories controlled by the throne like stage where the DJ worked. Also at the DJ's control was a button that would mimic an earthquake on the dance floor. If the button was held down, eventually the whole room would start to spin in place.

One trampoline was charmed to catch people jumping down into the room, while another bounced them the seventy feet up to the enlarged foyer where the only door in and out of Grimmauld Place was. Half a dozen more trampolines were around the floor and pre-charmed with several easily modifiable settings. Brooms were scattered all around the place for those uncomfortable with the trampolines.

On the other side of the stage was the pudding pit for wrestling.

Howlers were sent off to all the major magical alleys, Hogsmeade, Hogwarts, St. Mungo's, and even the Ministry. They all said the same thing. "Voldemort is dead! If you feel this nugget of knowledge is worth celebrating then come party with the Lords Black at Number Twelve Grimmauld Place. Leave your conscience at the door. Clothing optional."

Tonks urged her platinum blonde hair to grow longer and cover her ridiculously sized bare breasts. She took a few more tentative steps adjusting to the feel of hooves. "Are you sure five minutes isn't enough?"

"Ten," Harry said nodding in approval of the partial transfiguration. Tonks had to take a Norton's Brew to get it to stick, but her bottom half had been replaced with the body of a horse. When you added in her nude upper half, she made for a hot centaur. "Ten minutes from the moment we appear, and you can't just stand there. You have to engage in conversations with people."

Tonks was pulling her hair flatter, trying to keep her nipples from poking out. She looked at the bright smile on Harry's face. "I'm beginning to think a midget detention doesn't sound so bad."

"Just ten minutes," Harry reminded her. "And then we've got a truce. I shall pursue no further vengeance for this morning's Quibbler. But if any new pictures surface, all bets are off."

Tonks gave up playing with her hair and tried to swish her tail. She only managed to wiggle her bottom. "You're not forcing me to return all the other pictures and destroy the negatives?"

Harry gave her an experimental squeeze and looked up at her indignant frown. "Where would be the fun in that?"

Tonks slapped Harry's hand away when he went for another squeeze. "Let's get this over with."

Harry tapped a disillusionment charm over his head and grabbed Tonks' arm. "I'll help you to the dance floor."

Harry rested a hand on Tonks' back where it met the horse transfiguration and guided her from the backyard to the foyer.

Dozens of people were standing around the railing circling the twenty foot in diameter hole in the foyer. They were chattering wildly, breaking into excited hugs and exclamations of joy, and passing bottles of unknown alcohol around merrily. But not a single person missed the fact that a large and healthy female centaur just walked out from the kitchen.

Males and females alike were struggling to meet Tonks' eyes. She just nodded silently at them while Harry was sniggering into his disillusioned hand.

"I got you," Harry assured Tonks as she gracelessly hopped over the railing and down the hole to the dance floor.

The receiving trampoline caught them smoothly and their fall slowed to a gentle stop. Tonks took a few shaky steps and walked off the trampoline with the help of a disillusioned Harry.

"Nine more minutes," Harry muttered out the corner of his mouth as he gave Tonks a gentle smack on her hindquarters and walked away.

"Wow," one man exclaimed shortly before getting cuffed in the head by his wife.

"Greetings," Tonks said walking up to the unknown man. "I am Sugarbane. Tell me, do you know where I could find Lord Harry Black?"

Several scantily clad women had all surrounded her and asked, "What're you looking for him for?"

Tonks had to smother a smile at the slutty Lord-diggers' jealousy. She arched her back proudly and thrust her chest out. "Stories of his legend have spread far across the lands. And I tire of the pathetically small horse cocks among the males in my clan."

A disillusioned man fell to the floor in an effort not to laugh out loud.

Tonks nodded at the incredulous faces. "Fridwulfa the Giantess tells of the prowess-"

"Tonks?" Jimmy exclaimed having recognized her mannerisms, even if he'd never seen this face before.

Tonks took four slow and wobbly steps towards Jimmy, and when she was finally close enough, she slapped him across the face. "Hold your tongue, youngling."

Jimmy put his hand against his sore cheek but couldn't tear his eyes away from the sight.

"Eyes up," Tonks snapped.

"Sorry," Jimmy said looking Tonks in the eye. He stole a quick glance to make sure the breasts were still there but held eye contact for the most part.

Tonks sighed and asked, "Do you know where I could find Lord Harry Black?"

"Huh?" Jimmy asked with a wandering eye.

"Eyes up!"

Jimmy jerked his head up. "Lord Harry Black?"

"Yes," Tonks eagerly asserted.

Jimmy looked over to the right and then the left. "There he is. That's him."

Tonks had her arms out to the side to steady herself as she half-galloped towards the extremely amused Harry and Sirius.

The effect of her brisk movement was not lost on any of the men there.

"Lord Harry Black," Tonks said with a slight bow. "The stars speak of a glorious joining."

Harry was holding his chin in thought. "Can you gallop again?"

Tonks restrained herself from trying out a donkey kick. Instead she hopped in place a couple times, making sure her swollen mammary continued gyrating in small aftershocks. She stoically deadpanned, "The heavens have foretold my coming."

Harry knew he was going to crack up if he let Tonks keep talking. He smiled at Sirius. "Why not?"

Harry took two steps and used his magical arms to hop into place on Tonks' back like she was a normal steed. He twirled his wand towards the wall and a curtained doorway appeared. "Giddyup!"

Harry used his magical arms to steady and urge Tonks forward leaving a stunned packed dance floor behind.

As soon as they were past the curtain, Harry fell off Tonks back and let out the laughter he'd been holding in.

Tonks stopped and steadied herself in place. "That wasn't ten minutes."

"I don't care," Harry assured her through his mirth. "That was perfect. Full credit. Oh Tonks… did you see the looks on their faces?"

"You mind giving me my legs back?" Tonks said waving her hands towards her equestrian half. "Jimmy needs a little payback too."

"He's a teen," Harry argued. "And those were bouncing. Why did you have to bring Hagrid's mum into this?"

Tonks shrugged as she kneeled down and rolled onto her side. "You know any others giants that've boinked humans?"

"True, but she died a long time ago… I think." Harry carefully reversed the transfiguration, leaving a completely naked Tonks lying on the floor.

"I doubt anyone fooled by that is going to be up to date on giant current events." Tonks stretched and morphed her body into a more comfortable form as she readjusted to being bipedal. She ignored the pile of clothes Harry set out and stalked over towards him. "Now it's your fault I'm feeling all randy, so you have to fix this one."

Harry didn't fight back as Tonks pushed him down and stood imposingly over him. "Really?"

A predatory smile and a swish of Tonks' wand were the only warning Harry received.

Ten ridiculously frenzied minutes later, the top half of Harry's naked sweaty body stuck out from the curtains and found a crowd of people waiting. "Anyone got a cigarette?"

A loud whinnying sound of relief could be heard in the background.

"Thanks," Harry said accepting a silent offer of a cigarette from a man. He smiled extra brightly at the resigned but amused look on Lily Potter's face as he disappeared back behind the curtain.

Eight minutes and one shared cigarette later, Harry emerged from the curtain providing the cover for a hidden and disillusioned Tonks to sneak out right behind him. Harry waved his wand and the curtained doorway disappeared from view.

"Where's Sugarbane?" the primarily young and male waiting crowd asked.

Harry spotted a brightly smiling and clearly drunk Ron Weasley nodding eagerly to the question. "She, uh," Harry quickly lied, "she said she's going to need to sleep for a few days so… yeah."

Lily approached Harry trying to look disapproving as she handed him a clear glass. "Some whiskey. To wash the sin from your mouth."

Harry smiled at Lily, inspecting the glass. "We're going to need more whiskey."

"Yes," Lily agreed. "We're probably going to need to soak your-"

"Mum!" Jimmy shouted.

"Sorry," Lily apologized, thinking she might need to lay off the whiskey.

Up on stage by the DJ, Sirius cast a Sonorus charm, and shouted, "Welcome!"

Conversations stopped and turned to the host.

"The Dark Lord is dead, the Dark Lord is dead," Sirius sang with a little dance.

Everyone cheered and thrust their hands into the air.

"For those that don't know, I am Sirius Black, one of the Lords of this Noble and Most Ancient House or some such rubbish," Sirius preened under the cheers and praise for him. "First off, let's give a big hand to Gin Weasley and the Hog's Head for the drinks."

Gin waved as a spotlight flashed her way.

"And of course her illustrious brothers and the fine folks at Weasleys Wizarding Wheezes have provided a number of fireworks." Sirius shouted pointing a spotlight towards Fred and George.

The twins responded by triggering a pair of magical rockets. The first one reached the main level and exploded, sending a large shower of harmless white sparks all over the foyer and cascading down to the dance floor. The second one spiraled up through the hole out the roof and blew a deafening bang as massive WWW logo hovered in the sky for ten seconds.

Several Ministry workers palmed their faces and went off to make up a story for the muggles.

"And providing the music," Sirius said pointing towards the man with a fashion sense only Albus Dumbledore would appreciate, "DJ Drastic Squibtastic!"

The quiet music exploded into a frenetic beat and the man pressed the button a couple times to get the room shaking.

"Now I can understand no one breaking in the pudding pit yet," Sirius continued working the crowd as the music quieted. "We still need to get Tonks a little drunker, but we're getting there."

"Oi!" The pink-haired auror shouted down from the railing in the foyer.

Sirius just waved at her as people laughed. "But I'm disappointed no one's using the trampolines. Maybe you need a demonstration. Harry, show them how it's done."

Sirius continued to narrate while Harry grudgingly walked over to one of the six blue trimmed trampolines. "For those of you sober enough to understand, that big hole up there is charmed so that anyone falling through it lands safely on the receiving trampoline. It won't catch you if you're on a broom, and it won't catch you if you're bonded to a different trampoline."

Harry bounced softly in place until a flash of light appeared.

"Now Harry's tied to that trampoline," Sirius explained. "Just sit there until it syncs with you, and then it responds to your wishes."

Harry had started bouncing ten and fifteen off the ground.

"Don't be a pansy," Sirius chided Harry.

On his next bounce down into the trampoline he sank just a little further and longer in before he was launched like a missile, straight up through the foyer, the warded second and third floors, and out the hole in the roof up into the night sky.

Harry's less than manly scream of glee came zooming back down into the hole and landed right back on the trampoline again. He shouted, "Overdid it a little," and shot back up into the sky.

The crowds were all looking up waiting for Harry to come back down, but he never did.

"What my camera shy fellow Lord Black has done is to sever his connection with the trampoline," Sirius explained. "He's probably setting up the barbecue on the roof right now."

Sirius turned his head watching the hole in the ceiling while a couple people on brooms flew up to check only to zip out of the way of Harry as he fell. He landed smoothly on the receiving trampoline and nodded at Sirius.

"Fire pits are lit and the night sky up there is beautiful," Sirius urged them all and nodded at the DJ to start up the music again.

Harry apparated with a soft pop and launched the slippery projectile at his godfather.

Sirius felt the splash on his back and sighed. "Oh yeah. And in addition to all the fireworks on the roof, a few of the five hundred water balloons up there are filled with clothes-dissolving potion."

Sirius ran through the crowd as his upper body and lower legs were already bare. He immediately synced with a trampoline and jumped out of view just as the last of his underwear disappeared.

His still amplified voice called down, "Fair warning to anyone thinking of crashing here. If the sun is up and you're still passed out or lying around, we're going to toss you into the floo with no destination. Now turn that music back up!"

The music started pumping loudly and the cheering even drowned that out as the party resumed. Lots were dancing, some using the brooms to get to the roof. Several people used the trampolines to just bounce and make poses for those surrounding the railing in the foyer. There was no argument with giving the ladies first dibs on the trampolines.

Much alcohol was consumed and merriment had.

Inevitably, twenty brooms, some with individuals, some with couples, were all positioned for the first annual naked broom race to Big Ben and back.

All the competitors were wearing "I'm so dead!" Voldemort masks to hide their faces. The masks looked especially amusing on the dozen or so mighty fine looking naked female bodies.

Harry had magically attached the mask to his face after his clothes dissolved for the third time. He looked to his left and saw a pale nubile woman's body that was clearly affected by the breeze. He looked to his right and saw a pair of identical naked female bodies on a single broom and came to a conclusion.

"This isn't going to work," Harry muttered pulling the broom out from under him and spinning to face the other way. He remounted his broom with the bristles in front of him.

"Three, two, one, GO!" The mask wearing referee shouted.

Harry zoomed off the roof, getting way ahead of the pack, despite flying backwards and facing the wrong way. He was watching all the naked women gripping their broom handles tighter. "Sweet."

Harry had to reach behind him and jerk the handle of the broom as he was flying a little too close to a large Victorian house. "Whoa."

"Ha-ha!" a particularly competitive woman shouted as the pack flew over the stumbling backwards facing wizard. "Not so cocky now, are you?"

"Well you can't beat the view," Harry grinned looking straight up at them. "And it's not like these brooms protect from shrinkage."

Harry kept flying underneath them with his eyes aimed skyward while maintaining the pack's pace. "Sweet."

A scream erupted as a few of the racers got too close and one of the two identical naked bodies fell off her broom.

"Shit," Harry said as he jumped off his broom, spun it around to face the right way and dove after her. He caught her arm just before she crashed into the street below. "Hang on," Harry said as a bus was headed straight for them. He zipped back up into the air and swung the scared woman up over his head and landed her right in place onto the back of his broom behind him.

She was still out of breath as she clutched her arms around Harry holding him tight.

"You okay?" Harry asked as her race partner came flying over.

"Oh my god! I'm so sorry!" the likely twin sister shouted.

"I'm okay," she assured, scooting closer to Harry. "I'm okay."

"You saved her," she said looking at Harry gratefully.

"It happens," Harry ruefully admitted. "You two want to catch up and win this race?"

"No," the soft voice over his shoulder said, resting her cheek on Harry's back. "Take me back, please."

Harry realized his passenger wasn't going to get back on the other broom and agreed. "Alright but we're going to have to have some fun on the flight back then. Hold on." Harry felt the woman's breasts press up against his back as she gripped him tighter and he dove down to street level, pulling up just before hitting the pavement.

The fearful shriek of glee was like music to his ears, despite being shouted at point blank range. He saw the other woman was hunched over and keeping up with them as he happily swerved in between cars, stop lights, and trees the whole way.

"Oh," Harry eeped. "That's… not the broomstick."

"Are you sure," came the breathy answer in his ear. "It feels like it."

"Umm," Harry considered the question.

"Besides," she whispered, licking his ear. "My sister and I must thank you for saving my life."

Harry gulped and decided to take a slightly longer way home, streaming up into the sky hoping the thinner, colder air would settle him down.

"Slow down," the cry came from the other broom rider.

Harry had leveled off as the other girl caught right up to them and hovered just a little higher.

She suddenly leapt from her broom and landed right in front of Harry who had to pull his arms back.

"I can't let you have all the fun," the new girl in front said while holding the other broom in one hand grinding her backside towards Harry.

He was struggling but managed to steady the broom wrapped safely in a naked twin Voldemort mask wearing sandwich.

"I don't think this broom was meant for three," Harry said suddenly finding the night air far less cold.

The one in front was holding Harry's arm against her side as she leaned back and whispered in his unoccupied right ear. "Then you should probably take us somewhere, Lord Black."

Harry found himself agreeing heartily. "Recognized me, huh?"

"You have a habit of getting your picture taken shirtless," the answer came from the girl in back nibbling his left ear.

Harry spotted the fire from the pit barbecue in the distance and flew back towards the party. "It's nice to know you've been studying my pictures, Padma."

Both Patil sisters seemed to stiffen and Harry was reassured that he still had some control over the situation.

The awaiting crowds cheered them loudly as the broom carrying three naked people and an extra broom arrived back at the roof.

"There's no way you made it there and back already," the masked referee argued.

"You're right," Harry said as both women hugged him tighter. "I lost the broom race, but well… I win."

"To winning," a clearly inebriated man toasted and everyone around clinked glasses and cheered another reason to take a drink.

Harry flew down the hole, making sure everything was going okay and circled over the heads of the people still dancing.

The naked twins sandwiching him were blushing and holding on while he lazily flew around.

"What are you doing?" Parvati asked from in front, feeling all the eyes on her.

"I could say I'm just making sure the party's going okay," Harry earnestly answered, spotting several aurors and sober responsible adults manning the door, the bathroom lines, and generally keeping an eye on things. "But honestly? Victory lap."

Both Patil sisters ducked their heads to hide their smiles.

Harry spotted Sirius wearing a Voldemort mask and an engorged copy of the troll leg umbrella stand. He poked him in the shoulder inquisitively. "You doing okay?"

Sirius knew only person who'd poke him with an invisible arm while sandwiched between hot naked twins. "Not as good as you are, but yeah."

Harry suddenly felt the identification wards trigger and one of the presences he wasn't expecting arrived. "Did you catch it?"

Sirius nodded. "Bring him on down here."

Harry was squeezed tightly as he flew back up and around the people bouncing on the trampolines. He whispered to both of his passengers. "Don't think I can't tell how much you like people looking at you while hidden under your masks."

Both Patils were giggling softly and holding on.

Harry flew right to the front door and stopped before a non-descript man. "Are you going to wear that glamour all night?"

"I suppose not," the man known as David Monroe agreed, dropping the simple charm and revealing the face his enchanted necklace displayed.

Most people didn't react any, but there were a couple of shocked gasps. Harry could tell neither Padma nor Parvati had recognized him and he whispered to Parvati. "Give him the broom."

Tom took the broom and followed Harry down the dance floor. Tom whistled softly in appreciation for the magic of the room. "Sirius' work, I'm guessing?"

"You can identify our styles now?" Harry chuckled as a few others were whispering and pointing to the fully clothed unmasked man landing on the stage.

Sirius had gotten back up on the stage wearing the troll leg like a barrel. He pulled his mask up showing his face and cast Sonorus on his throat. "Excuse me! Excuse me!" he shouted as the music quieted.

"We have a very special guest tonight," Sirius yelled as his voice carried throughout the foyer and up to the roof. "Ladies, gentlemen, perverts, deviants, miscreants, and scoundrels," Sirius said walking over and thrusting his arm around Tom's amused shoulders. "For those of you who don't know, I'd like you all to meet David Monroe, the Vanquisher of Voldemort."

Cheers and shouts erupted from everywhere and thunderous applause shook the foundation of every house on the street. People from the roof were flying down as others jumped the railing and landed on the receiving trampoline to get a better look at their surprising savior.

Tom just smiled modestly and waved his thanks while they all kept clapping and shouting his name.

"Did you need anything tonight?" Harry asked Tom who was beginning to blush under all the praise.

Tom shook his head. "Everyone's calling this the party of the century so I thought I'd see what sort of shindig you two were throwing. You know the DMLE is scared of what would happen if they tried to shut this down." He leaned over towards Harry and Sirius. "Alan's still being interrogated, but he may stop by later."

"Well then," Harry said, amazed that the people were still cheering and applauding. "If you gentlemen will excuse me, I have better things to do and many positions to do them in." He waggled his eyebrows and flew back up towards the protected floors, disappearing still happily held in a naked twin sandwich.

Sirius thrust a twenty galleon bottle of brandy into Tom's hand. "You know, I'm guessing here, but I bet defeating the Dark Lord could get you laid. Just maybe."

Tom opened the bottle and took a sniff. He glanced over at Sirius. "Have you been drinking?"

"A little," Sirius admitted while snapping the straps holding his troll leg suit up. "Ooh! A Potter."

Tom just watched in amusement as Sirius ran over towards Jimmy, who had passed out headfirst on the makeshift bar Gin was working at.

"Jimmy?" Sirius asked pulling the young man's head up by the hair.

"Uhh," the exhausted Head Boy groaned.

Sirius let his head drop back into his folded arms on the bar and smiled at Gin. "Hey Gin? You wanna do me a favor?"

"What's that?" she asked, sipping on her own beer.

"Jimmy's got a guest room on the third floor," Sirius explained as he slapped a sticker onto her arm. "Don't take that off, or it'll vanish. But now you should be able to see the second and third floors. You mind helping him up to his room?"

Gin looked at the stream of drool connecting Jimmy's open mouth and a small puddle on the bar and found it pathetically cute. "Sure." She agreed moving over and slinging one of his limp arms across her back.

"Oh and when you get him to bed, make sure that he drinks this potion before he falls asleep for the night."

"Got it." Gin accepted the clear vial and helped Jimmy over towards the trampoline that took people up.

"Padfoot?" Remus said as he walked up behind him. "You're not trying to play matchmaker again, are you?"

"Who? Me?" Sirius replied a little too innocently.

"What was in that potion?" Remus warily asked.

"Same thing Fred and George tricked me into drinking earlier," Sirius admitted while looking down his troll leg suit. He looked back at Remus. "New one they're working on called Pecker-Up. It's basically a Pepper-Up but it also makes the drinker's-"

"I got it," Remus interrupted with a frown. "So when Jimmy… oh."

"Yup."

"And you think she'll…"

"Enh… maybe."

Remus sighed. "You're like the tallest and sickest cupid ever."

"Worked with you," Sirius argued. "Speaking of, where is your worse half? Did she even make it?"

Remus shook his head. "Didn't you notice the winner of the naked broom race was slightly pregnant?"

"Really?"

Remus nodded. "She painted over the Black Family crest on her arm. And since the food is on the roof…"

"Ahh," Sirius said in understanding. "Say no more."

The two idly chatted watching all the people dancing and cheering, flying all around them. Occasionally people would come over for drinks and Sirius would happily help the naked ones first. After twenty minutes and no sign of Gin, Sirius decided he'd waited long enough. "Well, I guess this cupid hit another money shot."

"So it appears," Remus agreed, sipping on his beer.

"You wanna do me a favor?"

"Not when you ask like that," Remus said shaking his head.

"No, no," Sirius argued. "Nothing like that. I just don't think Gin's coming back any time soon and wanted you to watch the bar, maybe help mix a few drinks."

Remus nodded. "That I can handle."

"Excellent," Sirius exclaimed. "Because this erection is really starting to itch."

"That was more than I ever wanted to know," Remus said waving Sirius away.

Sirius turned towards the still full crowd and just yelled this time, without any help from a charm. "Excuse me? Sorry, but I seem to have been cursed with a magical erection. Would anyone care to help me with that?"

Several hands went up in the air. Remus felt pity on the world where that pick-up line works.

"Excellent," Sirius agreed at more than two dozen arms in the air. "Okay fellas? Sorry I'm not that drunk and you shouldn't believe what you read in the papers. Now why don't I start with you," Sirius said grabbing the arm of a masked naked woman. "The rest of you can wait in line or draw straws."

"Or they can watch," the unknown woman suggested.

Sirius turned to look at the woman whom he still hadn't seen the face of or even knew the name of. "I love you."

Sirius waved to all the other women with their arms in the air. "The rest of you follow me if you want."

Not all of them did, but Sirius figured eight was enough.

Harry woke up to the feeling of two warm bodies pressed up against him. Padma was nestled snugly under his arm, while Parvati's head was resting on his chest.

"Sweet," Harry mumbled happily.

A loud knock was heard on his bedroom door disturbing the twins' sleep.

"What?" Harry shouted in irritation.

"Hey Harry?" Sirius' voice came from the other side of the door. "Can I come in? I've got…" There was a brief muffled conversation before Sirius continued, "Kelly with me."

Harry pulled the covers up so that only their heads were showing. "It's open."

Sirius walked into the room, having already showered and cleaned. He looked at the twin women under Harry's arms curiously. He waved between Kelly and the twins, "Okay, so how do you three know each other?"

The three women were all shaking their heads.

"I don't think I've ever met them," Kelly explained. "I told you, I'm from the states, and I'm just here visiting my cousin."

"Who's your cousin?" Sirius asked.

"Scott Martin," she answered. "He's a squib from California based in the London headquarters of UPPS."

Parvati was sitting up and holding the sheet to cover herself. "Never heard of him."

Harry sighed. "Sirius, it's not going to happen every time."

"Hah!" Sirius scoffed. "So far this morning I've ended three feuds that have all been going on for centuries and reunited an orphan with the aunt that wasn't allowed custody. Now Kelly is all that's left. So come on, no one's got a missing relative? Or mystery that's befuddled them for years?"

Padma and Parvati were looking to Harry for help but he just shook his head.

"Sorry," Kelly shrugged. "I'm just a girl on vacation who can appreciate a good party when she sees it."

Sirius was getting desperate. "No ancient family feuds or rare artifact you have to find? No Gatekeepers or Keymasters?"

Kelly shook her head. "Muggleborn."

Padma shrugged. "Not unless you know someone with Bombay blood."

Kelly gasped. "I have Bombay blood!"

Parvati jerked up suddenly. "And you're magical."

Kelly nodded. "Graduated from Salem. What did you need?"

Padma was beginning to feel hope again. "Our mother has been slowly dying for years. She needs a kidney transplant-"

"I was born with three kidneys!" Kelly exclaimed in surprise. "This is unbelievable."

Sirius was smiling brightly at Harry as the naked twins jumped over to talk more with Kelly. "Say it."

Harry shook his head.

"Come on. I earned it."

Harry sighed as he watched Padma and Parvati getting dressed paying no attention to him or Sirius at all. "You were right. I shouldn't have doubted you."

Sirius closed his eyes and basked in the admission. "Oh it feels good. It feels very good."

Harry yawned as he slipped on a pair of pajama bottoms and a robe. He saw the three women leave the room without even saying goodbye and felt blessed. He noticed Sirius was really furiously rubbing the front of his pants.

"The morning itches, eh?"

Sirius was still scratching. "The what?"

"You know," Harry assured him while scratching himself too. "The usual morning itches. The ones you're supposed to get."

"Harry," Sirius said looking down the front of his pants. "It's not supposed to be itchy."

Harry slowed down his scratching. "It isn't?"

Sirius sighed thinking they'd both be needing a visit with a healer. "No."

Harry closed his eyes in frustration at his naivety. "There's no such thing as sexual goose bumps, is there?"

"Oh Harry!" Sirius had to laugh.

"I thought it was a Veela thing."

Sirius was still snickering. "I hate to break it to you, but I doubt she was a Veela."

"I'm beginning to think the same thing," Harry admitted. He paused for a moment before going right back to his scratching. "Bugger."

"With every great gift comes a curse," Sirius ominously explained.

Harry knew he should stop scratching and managed to convince himself rubbing didn't count as scratching. "So is there a counter-curse?"

"Not to my knowledge," Sirius replied, deep in thought. "But there are some good ointments."

Chapter 30

Disclaimer: I own nothing; it all belongs to J.K.Rowling. I'm just borrowing the characters to play with for a while. This is for pleasure only, no profit is being made, and no copyright infringement is intended.

"Shiny?" Tom repeated. "I show you one of the most complicated prisons ever created and your first impression is shiny?"

"Well, it is," Harry argued. "I just hope the bindings holding him in place are as good as the polishing charms."

"He's not going anywhere," Tom said with confidence.

"So was it a conscious choice to pass on concrete, steel bars, and the usual jailhouse classics in favor of the aquarium meets lava lamp art nouveau style?"

Tom looked at his creation with a frown. "It's a prison for the unbound spirit not a physical manifestation."

"I'm not contending the purpose," Harry agreed. "I'm just saying it looks like someone engorged an ugly vase your mother-in-law gave you. The kind of thing you have no choice but to keep on the mantle in case she drops by unexpectedly."

Tom walked around the grandfather clock sized contraption. The top foot was a cylindrical copper seal trimmed in brass. It capped a two foot stretch of transparent material and sat on a copper base so that the aquarium aspects were at eye level. On two opposites sides ran a series of brass latches and locks. "I didn't consider aesthetics much when designing it, but you know if you really wanted we could-"

"No," Harry chided. "We're not putting Voldemort on display anywhere. As amusing as it might be, I try not to tempt fate if I can help it."

Harry cast a charm over his eyes and was examining the spell work he recognized in the prison. A fingernail sized black knob inside a small brown bubble from within the opaque green tube was swirling with a sickly grey magic. "So what happened to the trap you told me about?"

Tom could tell Harry was trying to figure out the prison and answered, "Voldemort was feeling vulnerable after the loss of more than half his Death Eaters in only two days, nice job on that by the way. He needed some leverage and planned to kidnap among others, the Minister's daughter, a young woman who just happens to be a patient of mine."

"A patient of yours?" Harry repeated. "How'd you manage to get the Minister's daughter as a patient?"

Tom smirked in a manner eerily reminiscent of the teenage diary Harry knew. "I am one of the foremost experts on healing the mind. My services are highly sought after."

"That's worrisome."

"Harry, I should remind you that while I am not Voldemort, nor am I a Dark Lord, I am still Tom Riddle. And I've been exploring the boundaries of magic in relative secrecy for the last two decades."

Harry suppressed a shiver.

"It started with Frank but I saw a genuine opportunity to gain allies and favors. Ones I intend to make full use of when the proper time comes. The Minister's daughter is not my patient by coincidence. It's worth noting that I've spent significant time inside the minds of eight different presidents, twelve prime ministers, and four kings."

"I don't want to know," Harry shook his head.

"When I heard the Minister's daughter was a target, I moved her appointment up, passed the details on, and altered the plan to fit. Voldemort brought only four other Death Eaters with him, and three of them I'd already compromised."

"Compromised?" Harry asked warily.

Tom was willing to explain this because he knew the charm of brotherhood would prevent Harry from telling anyone. "You know he's got compulsion charms, loyalty charms, and in some cases outright control charms running through the Dark Mark's connection to their soul?"

Harry nodded.

"Well, he only ever checked that the charms were still in place and were his magic. More than half the Death Eaters, though mostly the weaker ones, see me as number one, and him number two. They still listen and follow him, unless the moment comes for me to belay an impulse and give them a different compulsion."

Harry blinked and showed Tom he wasn't too happy about this minor revelation. "You have your own Death Eater army."

Tom frowned. "It sounds worse when you put it like that."

"Remember when you said you weren't following Voldemort's path?"

"It's not like they know about me," Tom argued. "And you know it's because I have 'my own Death Eater army' that it'll be so easy to capture them and all the others."

"You're not going to keep them out of prison or allow them to buy their way into your favor?"

"Harry," Tom explained. "These people believe they are loyal to Voldemort. They don't remember me modifying their soul connections."

Harry didn't particularly care, but was still getting a feel for Tom's sincerity. "And you're going to let them hang for the things you and he made them do?"

"No, I'm not," Tom corrected. "They will be tried as both the criminals they are, and the victims of the Dark Lord. Even if by some miracle they managed to dismiss all their actions as unwilling puppets of the Dark Lord, they still have to confess to whatever crime they committed to earn their Dark Mark. I don't know if any will ever get released from Azkaban. Frankly, I'm more concerned with the Death Eater bandits having a shortage of targets and too much free time."

"Rumor is they hung up their ski masks and have gone legit," Harry admitted with a grin. He pointed towards the impressive contraption he'd given up trying to unravel. "So how does this thing work?"

Tom's face lit up proudly as he explained, "There are three separate chambers surrounding the anchor."

Harry got up next to the clear aquarium section of the spiritual prison. There was a small knob surrounded by what looked like to a dark brown murky liquid. That brown bubble was inside a tall green tube that was held in place in the center. The rest of the round aquarium was filled with clear blue water.

"The inner chamber that looks brown?" Tom explained. "That's actually a bright red liquid crystal of my own design. It prevents every possible sensory input, including magic. The next chamber of green liquid surrounding that is more crystal. The green is actually the arithmantic opposite of the red. And they are both poisonous to body and soul. So if anyone managed to get through green would be completely vulnerable to the red, and vice versa."

Harry was looking closer at the anchor in the middle of the magical prison. "And the blue liquid?"

"Salt water," Tom answered happily.

"Salt water?"

"I'm opposed to conjugal visits but there are times we may wish to…" Tom's voice trailed off as he drew his wand. "Allow me to demonstrate." He cast a spell into the smooth block of obsidian at the base of the front where the aquarium met the copper base.

The clear tube protecting the green liquid crystal split vertically and unfolded open. The green fluid spilled out into the water slowly dissolving into a greenish tinted cloud.

"What are you doing?" Harry asked warily, feeling the hairs on the back of his neck rise.

"Relax," Tom quickly calmed and sent magic into the charm of brotherhood he shared with Harry. He tapped his wand on the obsidian and the water and green liquid began to swirl wildly in a tornado of fluid. Slowly the green liquid crystal separated from the water at the outer reaches of the sealed tube. Thick solid beads of green liquid crystal were sucked away leaving the clear blue water and a reddish table tennis sized ball remaining.

Tom cast another spell and the spherical bubble surrounding the red fluid slid back into itself, allowing the other liquid crystal to disperse in the water. Another whispered spell sent the mixture swirling in a whirlpool until the red liquid crystal separated and was also sucked away. "Have to remove the poisons or they die too quick."

Harry looked curiously as Tom cast another spell into the obsidian. A jellyfish no more than three inches around and eight long appeared lazily contracting in place inside the salt water.

"Watch it," Tom pointed when Harry turned to look at him.

The jellyfish which had been calmly waving on the slightest currents suddenly froze up and darkened from a whitish pink to nearly grey.

"To be on the safe side we don't want to do this with any creatures or weak-willed others around," Tom said as he slid two thin vertical panels of glass straight through the middle of the aquarium. He twisted a few latches and tightened a few flaps before suddenly swinging the prison open. The front half of the bisected cylinder was just water, but the back half housed the anchor and the possessed jellyfish.

"And now through this, we can use legilimency on the jellyfish."

Harry saw Tom look towards the jellyfish and silently aim his wand. Tom winced a little and explained, "It stings a little. Voldemort's not really aware enough for any higher thought processes. He's definitely angry and feels threatened, but his memories are easily viewed."

Tom snapped his legilimency probe free and turned to Harry. "Anything you wanted to know about Voldemort?"

Harry was watching the barely moving jellyfish and recognized a slippery slope to nowhere good. He thought it over though and decided he should familiarize himself with the sensation. "Legilimens," Harry said softly, aiming towards what he hoped was the brain of the jellyfish.

He felt the cold sting in his head and left Voldemort's mind quickly. "Huh."

"What did you see?" Tom asked curiously.

"Briefs," Harry answered.

Tom glanced away from the jellyfish and to Harry. "You have total access to the innermost recesses of one of the darkest minds in centuries and you sought out…"

"Boxers or briefs," Harry nodded. "And I'm not the least bit surprised."

Tom didn't hold back his chuckle. "I should have expected something like that." He swung the two halves of the round aquarium into their closed position and latched the prison back together.

"What is that?" Harry said pointing towards the two panels of glass Tom was leaning against the wall.

"These are just glass, charmed unbreakable. They have to let magic in and out for legilimency to work," Tom explained. He pointed to the aquarium. "All three chambers are dwarven wrought crystal. A diamond blade would chip before scratching it and every form of magic I've found just bounces off it."

Harry was impressed. He saw the jellyfish shake before it twisted around suddenly and floated lifelessly to collide with the aquarium wall. "Dead?"

"Yeah," Tom said. "They only last a few minutes. Now to get Voldemort back into his cell." He cast another spell into the obsidian and the little knoblike anchor flared bright white, glowing with life.

"Ahh," Harry hissed, grabbing at his most famous scar. "What the hell?"

Tom had already sealed the first bubble-shaped chamber and filled it with the red liquid crystal as the button sized anchor darkened to its grey murky state. He turned to Harry warily, "Are you alright?"

"What the fuck is that anchoring him?" Harry snapped, relieved to see his scar hadn't split open. It merely had startled him.

"This is one of those things that sounds a lot worse than it really is."

"Riddlebottom," Harry warned.

Tom admitted sheepishly, "It's the skull of an unborn human fetus at about nine weeks."

"Excuse me?"

"Technically nine seconds after nine minutes after nine hours after nine weeks since conception, but that's just kind of a mouthful and not really relevant."

"What was it doing?"

"It's a cage for unbound souls," Tom explained. "If the two liquid crystals ever combine it creates a fire on the level of Fiendfyre, but it also activates the soul cage to ensnare and hold. When it's activated, I feel it twitter because of what I am, but I didn't think I'd need to warn you. Did you perhaps unsuccessfully dabble in some soul magic?"

Harry sighed, feeling the headache leaving as quickly as it came. "Nope. The scar used to be a link between my Voldemort and me. It's just been a while and feeling anything through it is usually a bad sign."

"I'd imagine so."

"Soul magic scans have always gone a bit nutty on it."

"I assure you I had no idea," Tom diplomatically offered. "I wasn't trying to test you."

Harry waved him off. "Don't worry about it. But I got to say, I'm not big on the idea of you spending a lot of time digging into Voldemort's mind."

"Neither am I," Tom explained. "But I'm not arrogant enough to believe he hasn't left a few traps of his own devising behind. And having access to his memories could prove infinitely valuable."

"You've got a plan," Harry stated firmly while watching Tom.

Tom nodded as he engaged the second chamber and green liquid crystal. He vanished the dead jellyfish's body. "You don't know the spells to manipulate the chambers and I was thinking I wouldn't tell them to you."

"This is what the extra anchor stones are for?"

Tom nodded at how quickly Harry caught on. "Exactly. You put the latches, the doorway, the only way to access the prison under a Fidelius or something similar while leaving the rest of it visible. This way either of us could easily check the status of the prison, but it takes both of us working together to ever open it or attempt to communicate with Voldemort."

"Why?" Harry said, turning to look at Tom curiously.

"Why protect it?"

"No, I think I got that one. I meant why do you keep freely sharing your… control with me?"

Tom waved his wand and conjured a perfect but simple chair. He sat down, expecting this to be a long conversation. "I'm an excellent judge of potential, Harry. Even Voldemort was always cognizant of the power others held. Who was a threat, who had talents, who could be used and how. Admittedly there were a few blind spots…" he paused to allow Harry to chuckle. "But overall, he could watch someone and in a matter of minutes determine their worth with a scary amount of accuracy."

"And you?" Harry said from his own conjured chair.

Tom was not a modest man. "It takes me less than a minute. And do you know what I see when I look at you?"

Several smart-ass remarks came to mind, but Harry was too curious to do anything other than shake his head.

"An equal," Tom admitted looking Harry right in the eye. "Conveniently, one with very little interest in fame or glory."

"An equal?" Harry repeated skeptically.

"Have we not both defeated a Voldemort and fulfilled the same prophecy? We share brother wands from Dumbledore's phoenix. His familiar's blessing for the next leaders of the magical world, perhaps. There are too many similarities to call it coincidence."

Harry was slowly nodding in agreement as he got up. He moved the six extra anchor stones slightly. He began to feed power into them preparing a Fidelius.

"Perhaps it is still unreached potential," Tom softly joked. "Sirius told me that in addition to Black and Slytherin, you're well on your way to earning the title of the Lord of Ointment."

"Yeah," Harry muttered. "Hearing that you and he were getting chummy just about made my weekend."

Tom knew embarrassment and sarcasm were still the way to Harry's heart. "He told me there's even a rumor that the healing community may name this newly discovered strain the Seriously Hairy Black Bumps."

"I'll give you three guesses on who started that rumor and the first two don't count." Harry grumbled remembering several rather unpleasant floo calls he'd made from the healer's office. With a whispered phrase, he activated and sealed the Fidelius charm.

"Oww," Tom said closing his eyes in pain. "Remind me not to be looking when you do that."

Harry plopped back down into his conjured chair. "No. It doesn't feel like enough."

Tom was rubbing his aching head. "It hurts more than the legilimency did."

"Not that," Harry said. "You seeing me as an equal."

"I would think the other reasons are obvious," Tom said waving towards Voldemort's liquid prison.

Harry felt the brotherhood charm buzzing gently, hinting towards a more complicated answer.

Tom took a deep breath and explained, "I'm not going to live forever. And when I go, it's not guaranteed that I'll be pulling him with me. Someone has to make sure he is gone, and given the prophecy, it's possible you're the only person who could even do anything about it if he's not."

"Not going to live forever?" Harry questioned. "You're certain about that?"

"I plan to change the world and have a legacy that lasts the test of time, but I hold no illusions about the fragility of my existence."

"You're a Slytherin wrapped in Hufflepuff clothing, aren't you?"

"I'll take that as a compliment, Lord Slytherin."

Harry was watching Tom closely as he stated, "That was your sacrifice, wasn't it?"

Tom showed no surprise as he turned to Harry.

"I know you've researched the balance. Mortality was your sacrifice?"

Tom's face betrayed no emotion. "What was yours?"

Harry considered it a moment and shook his head. "Not today. Maybe some other time I'll tell you."

Tom inclined his head in understanding, before his eyes lit up. "Was coming here to this world, leaving your own behind, your cost?"

Harry smiled darkly, shaking his head.

"Or do you not know yet?" Tom questioned. "My understanding is that some costs aren't realized for years."

Harry wore a pained smile. "My victory was hollow."

Tom's eyes widened. "Your sacrifice was deemed sufficient?"

Harry nodded.

Tom couldn't keep the look of sympathy off his face. He watched Harry for a few seconds. "My sacrifice was indeed mortality and a pledge to fix Voldemort's mistakes."

"Mistakes?"

"I can't take responsibility for his victims, but his original goals, the admirable ones, are still worth striving for. And now that we know one way not to achieve them, it should be a bit easier, don't you think?"

Harry nodded. "I don't suppose you know your cost yet?"

Tom tried to hide his smile. "Not today, Harry. Maybe some other time."

"Fair enough," Harry agreed while taking note of Tom's curious response. "Where are we anyway?"

"Well, if you'd listened to me in the first place, you'd recognize this room."

"We're at the Shrieking Shack?" Harry asked in surprise.

Tom nodded. "This cellar's been hidden since my days as a student. It's not a Fidelius but a Stavros modification. You were keyed in when I apparated us here."

"You plan to leave Voldemort this close to Hogwarts?" Harry said doubtfully.

"To be honest, I'd prefer to put him in the Chamber of Secrets, but I think we should wait until Dumbledore's tenure as Headmaster is over."

Harry just looked at Tom incredulously.

"Listen, the prison is stronger and causes Voldemort more pain based on the volume of magic nearby. Yes a remote cave or the North Pole would be harder to stumble across but the liquid crystals would weaken over time. And there's nowhere in Europe with ambient magic as strong as Hogwarts. I'm open to options, but it needs to be near a high concentration of magic, which means it'll need to be near wizards and witches. Hogsmeade is the only all wizarding village on the island."

"The Ministry," Harry suggested.

Tom shrugged. "Not nearly as strong. And while I believe it's impossible, if somehow Voldemort got out, he'd run for cover first. Not attack students or villagers. The only added danger is if someone found out he was still alive and where he was."

"Could someone scry his location?"

"When we're trying to read his memories, yes," Tom admitted. "Behind Stavros wards it'd still take them days and we'll never leave him out that long. But as long as he's caged and surrounded by the red liquid crystal, nothing and I mean nothing can find him. No sensory input at all. No magic can find him. He certainly can't see, hear, or even sense us."

"And the Chamber of Secrets?"

"Has plenty of experience having safely housed a 'monster' for centuries," Tom said with a smile at the supposed mystery. "I'd say let's sneak in and put him there now, but Dumbledore's had decades of being attuned to Hogwarts. Whenever the next Headmaster takes the job, we can slip him down there during the turnover, seal it off, and no one will be the wiser."

Harry nodded getting used to the idea that Tom had a rational explanation for everything. "Is the basilisk in the woods behind Riddle Manor?"

Tom shook his head. "I helped him to the ocean and he went for a swim. In a few months he'll probably reach my place in Australia. I must admit I'm surprised you haven't pressed me to reveal myself to Dumbledore."

"You think he'd enjoy that?" Harry said unable to stop himself.

Tom realized his poor choice of words too late and didn't dignify Harry's question with a response.

Harry was snickering at the idea of Tom flashing Albus. "I know, I know. But truthfully, right now, I don't care much either way. Eventually Albus is going to figure you out. He's too smart not to. But it might not be a bad idea to let him see you accomplish some good things first before approaching him."

"I know you trust him," Tom felt the need to defend his position. "But ever since the moment he delivered my Hogwarts letter, he's looked at me with suspicion and fear."

"Like I said, he's smart." Harry retorted with a grin.

"He saw the magic I commanded even before I knew what magic was and he saw me as a threat to his power," Tom argued. "I could see he'd decided I was dark and evil before I'd even learned which end of the wand to hold."

"Not to piss on your parade but he wasn't exactly wrong."

Tom frowned in silent disagreement. "I was one of the younger kids in the orphanage and I had discovered a hidden power; I could bully the bullies. I could stop them from picking on me. Up until the moment Dumbledore met me, I cannot see how any eleven year old could have been any different."

"And from that he made up his mind on me?" Tom shook his head. "It was easier for him to see me as another Grindelwald than anything else."

"Hey, you don't have to sell me," Harry assured. "My Albus fucked me over almost as much as my Voldemort did."

"Really?"

Harry nodded. "I think he may have cared too much in my case though. So while he made a shitload of mistakes, it was always what he believed to be in my best interests or for the so-called greater good."

Tom furrowed his brow. "What did he-"

Harry answered before Tom could finish the question. "He placed my freshly orphaned baby body on the door step of a family that hates magic and hated me for existing. He even admitted he knew I'd have a hard life."

Tom just looked at Harry curiously.

Harry shrugged. "When I feel like blaming someone, it's usually him. But the Dumbledore of this world has always treated me as an adult, as an equal, and there's no denying the man is brilliant. Personally, I think he'll understand and support you, but I also think it's worth waiting until you've got some more evidence that you're on the side of the angels beyond usurping a Death Eater army."

Tom inconclusively nodded. "You're going to tell him about the Slytherin name and some of our plans?"

"Yeah," Harry said. "We're going to need his support on a few."

"I think you underestimate us both, Harry. But it would be easier with Albus on our side. We can focus our initial agenda on areas of common ground."

Harry was looking at Tom curiously. "You know inevitably someone else will notice your charmed necklace. The ministry will record and scan you. What happens if your true name and face come out?"

Tom smiled proudly. "It was actually Alan who came up with this one. But if I'm ever unable to stick that one back in the jar, then I shall readily admit to being Tom Riddle."

"Uh-huh," Harry said.

Tom put on a mask of a deadly serious scholar. "It was in my research on magical applications of mind healing techniques that I attempted to separate negative emotions like rage and jealousy."

"No," Harry shook his head, seeing where this was going.

"I actually separated those pieces of wrong and evil, but in an attempt to remove them, they attached themselves to a piece of my soul, wrenched it free and formed a separate entity from myself."

"Oh boy."

Tom nodded, without any trace of a smile. "This evil twin spiraled way beyond my control. He was as powerful as me and infinitely more ruthless. I tried to hunt him down. I tried to contain him, but people saw his face and his deeds and attributed them to me. I had to hide while I worked to defeat this horrible, unfortunate, but accidental creation."

"Enter That Fucker," Harry narrated.

"I knew I couldn't ever show my face, so I created a new identity. A different face and a new name I could use until the opportunity to finally end the madness presented itself. I was able to destroy Voldemort, but by that time Tom Riddle's legacy had been set in stone. It was not an easy decision but I felt I could help more people by remaining hidden under the only face and name I thought of myself as for the last two decades."

Tom's look of pained sincerity twisted into a smug victorious smile. "Now does that story seem more plausible or does it make more sense that I'm just a split piece of the former Dark Lord's soul who leeched Neville Longbottom's life before suddenly deciding the Dark Lord was a bad guy?"

Harry was suitably impressed. "And of course if or when it breaks you'll also have years of accolades, community service, and countless influential people willing to speak of your high moral character."

"I hope it never does break," Tom agreed. "But I do like to be prepared. Now if you'll excuse me, Alan's going to be getting officially released from custody, be declared a hero by the DMLE, answer a few questions for reporters, and then make the front page for being a close personal friend of mine."

"Yeah, Albus is expecting me by now as well." Harry got up and vanished his own conjured chair. "If I come up with somewhere better for this, are you open to moving it?"

"Harry, if you come up with somewhere better, I'll want to move it just as much as you," Tom assured him.

"You know we're going to have to make plans in case either of us dies," Harry commented.

Tom nodded slowly. "I've actually got a few ideas for that."

"Yeah?"

"But it's a situation a lot like Albus'," Tom explained. "We should put it off for a while. At least until we genuinely trust each other."

Harry thought that one over and suspected it to involve soul magic. "Okay."

"Good luck, Harry," Tom said as he apparated away.

Harry took a breath to ready himself. "I'm only going to be indirectly threatening and blackmailing one of the most powerful and respected wizards of all time. What could I possibly need luck for?" He looked around the room and realized he was talking to himself again. He apparated to the edge of Hogwarts wards.

Right away, the magic of Hogwarts was singing to him in a way it never had before. He used to feel like Hogwarts was his home away from home, but now it felt as natural as an extra layer of skin. He only thought about the reaction when his ring finger began to tingle happily. He twisted it around canceling its invisibility and saw the jewel in the Slytherin family ring was glittering wildly.

Harry knew people said Hogwarts loved and took care of all her children. He grinned under the realization that she had a new favorite.

He cast an oculamagi spell over his eyes and looked at the wards as he walked. They looked no different, but Harry was certain they felt different. He began to theorize that the wards recognized his status too. He had barely considered the possibility before his ring finger was tingling in response.

Harry looked both ways before throwing caution into the wind. He apparated up to the front steps of the castle with a soft pop.

Harry couldn't stop the smile splitting his face in half as he canceled the oculamagi spell. "We're going to keep this little tidbit to ourselves."

When his finger tingled again, he couldn't help but wonder if the Hogwarts' wards had understood and agreed. He pressed his hand against the outer stone wall, closed his eyes in concentration, and thought about what he wanted to see. He opened his eyes and couldn't believe his luck. "Sweet."

He hopped up the stairs and began to walk through the castle with an extra skip in his step. He reached the gargoyle guarding the headmaster's office and began a staring match with it. A few seconds later the gargoyle silently slid out of the way and let Harry up.

Harry knocked on the door from the outer chamber.

"Harry?" Albus called out. "Come in, come in."

"Is this a bad time?"

Albus stacked up the paperwork on his desk and shuffled it into one of his drawers. "Not at all. I've been expecting you in fact, as I'm sure you remember."

"Right," Harry said as he walked over to Fawkes perch and gave the partially sleeping bird a gentle rub on the back of its neck.

"Harry, I know you can't tell me much, but I was hoping-"

"Actually Albus," Harry said, plopping down into the chair across from the Headmaster. "I'm not here to talk about David Monroe."

"Oh?" Albus said in faint shock. "Still waiting on your Order member merit badge?"

Harry chuckled. "No, the truth is I came here to talk about you."

Albus got up from his seat behind the desk and moved to the chair next to Harry's. He turned it to face the younger man on equal ground. "Me?"

"Yeah, you," Harry said. He hesitated only a second before jumping right into it. "Because the thing is, you've been spreading yourself too thin."

Albus popped a lemon sherbet into his mouth and was surprisingly intrigued. He nodded at Harry, indicating he should continue.

"Between running the Order, fighting a war for the past three decades, your duties as Chief Warlock of the Wizengamot, Supreme Mugwump of the International Confederation, and undoubtedly countless more I'm unaware of, you have been only an adequate headmaster of Hogwarts."

"Adequate?"

Harry nodded. "The students look at you in awe and most of them are probably too intimidated to even approach you. I don't doubt you put their health and welfare first, but that is first on a long list of responsibilities."

Albus was frowning. "I admit the times I've had to leave the school and defend innocents from attack, I've had similar worries. But with the defeat of Voldemort, I expect my schedule to lighten."

"Lightening is good," Harry agreed. "Lightening is very good. In fact I was thinking of helping you out with that."

"Oh dear."

"This is a good thing," Harry meekly argued.

Albus warily asked, "What do you want?"

"There are a number of answers to that question," Harry said with a mischievous smile.

"Harry," Albus tiredly urged.

"I want you to become the greatest headmaster Hogwarts has ever had," Harry quickly answered. "I want your complete focus to be on the education of students now that fears of imminent attack will soon be a relic of the past."

Albus still wasn't sure what Harry was up to. "It's not that simple, Harry."

"It can be," Harry said. "Anything you convince me is worth doing, I can help make happen. You want to introduce some new electives, hire more teachers, offer more specialized tuition, host weekend demonstrations, bring in more experts-"

"Harry," Albus interrupted. "I don't think you appreciate how complicated and limited my budget is."

"So let's increase it."

"The Board of Governors would never-"

"Here's a thought," Harry interjected. "You want to get rid of the board? It would certainly make major changes easier."

Albus frowned in confusion. "What's going on?"

Harry helped himself to a glass of firewhiskey and left the bottle out in case Albus wanted some. "When the Wizengamot formally reconvenes in the fall, I will be wearing a declaration patch and Lord Black is going to nominate me for Chief Warlock."

Albus sat up straighter at the implied threat. "Really?"

Harry nodded happily. "Yup. And I'd appreciate it if you seconded the nomination. But if you want to settle it in the ring, I will."

Albus smiled at the idea. "And do you think you could take me?"

"In a fair fight?" Harry shrugged. "I have a few doubts. But I don't fight fair, Albus. I cheat and I cheat a lot."

"Hmm," Albus commented, silently finding himself agreeable to Harry's nomination but not willing to admit that aloud just yet.

"I should mention that Lord Black won't be nominating me as Lord Black," Harry said with a grin and a salute of his glass. "He's going to nominate me under my new title: Lord Slytherin."

Albus wandlessly summoned the bottle of firewhiskey and poured himself a glass.

Harry gave Albus time to compose himself, inwardly relishing moments like these.

"Lord," Albus had to force the name out, "Slytherin."

Harry twisted the ring allowing it to be visible. The ring glittered and twinkled in the light. "Hogwarts loves me."

"The Slytherin family ring accepted you," Albus stated, "and made you Lord Slytherin."

"Don't have kittens on me," Harry chided while twisting it back into invisibility. "The horcrux is gone. And really, did you think I just gave up those other horcruxes for nothing?"

Albus goggled at Harry unable to accept the idea of bartering pieces of the Dark Lord's soul for one of the most infamous and hated wizarding lines.

Harry slowly sipped his glass, waiting for the shock and surprise to leave Albus' face.

Albus couldn't decide what question to ask first. "But you were a Gryffindor!"

"Ironic, isn't it?"

"Harry, this is… this is…"

"I know, I know." Harry pointed towards the snoozing artifact on the shelf behind him. "But the Sorting Hat told me Slytherin would help me on the road to greatness. And you taught me all about second chances. Anyways, I'm telling you this now as a courtesy, and also so that you'll take me a bit more seriously when I say we can dismantle the Board of Governors. I can help get you anything you need to reestablish Hogwarts as the finest institute of magical learning in the world."

Albus was silently watching Harry. "This is what you want? No offense Harry, but it sounds a little more… altruistic than usual."

"The Order's disbanding, the war's over," Harry reminded. "You've had a great run Albus, and you've shouldered the hopes and dreams of several generations of wizards for an immensely long time. But a new world is forming and these metaphorical torches can be passed down smoothly… or I can cheat."

Albus was finding it oddly comforting to hear Harry's willingness to accept responsibility. "And where does David Monroe fit into all of this?"

"He's at the center of it," Harry said. "When I said he was the next Albus Dumbledore, I meant it. I'll tell you now that by next spring, he'll have turned his popularity into the Minster of Magic position."

"Monroe as Minister and you as Chief Warlock?"

"Scary, huh?"

Albus sighed. "I find most prospects involving you to be scary, Harry. And the thought that there's another wizard with an even more mysterious past, as much power, and more ambition than you is even more worrisome."

"For what it's worth," Harry said flaring magic into the charm of brotherhood he shared with Albus, "this is the weaker of the two charms of brotherhood I'm sustaining."

Albus responded with an equal push of magic. "I take it you trust him more now."

Harry got a mixed look on his face. "You know, every day he doesn't try to kill me, I trust him a little bit more."

"Oh Harry."

"Yeah, he's a character."

Albus had already decided to accept Harry's suggestions and was looking forward to the weight of the world on others' shoulders. "I'm guessing that seeking a more active role in politics was not your idea."

Harry grumbled. "Tell me about it. At first, David wanted me to run for Minister. I quickly disabused him of that notion."

"So most of this is his doing?" Albus questioned.

Harry could tell Albus was fishing but he had planned on explaining most of this anyway. "I shit you not. He's got a fifty year plan."

"Oh my," Albus grinned at Harry's reticence.

"Step one is to cultivate the environment, alter public perception on things."

Albus forewent the firewhiskey and poured himself a cup of tea. "Like what?"

"Treatment of dark creatures, misconceptions of muggles and muggle things, power and prestige established by birthright rather than virtue, the usual," Harry explained indifferently.

"And if I were to press you for some more details?"

"Alright, here's one he's talked me into," Harry agreed sitting up straighter. "You know there are dark magics and then there are dark magics."

Albus decided a dash of firewhiskey in his tea wouldn't be such a bad idea.

"I'm referring to the more powerful aspects of magic that get classified as dark out of ignorance or potential for abuse. The idea that if it's something the average wizard cannot safely do, then it's something no one should do."

"Harry, you cannot base your understanding of wizards on men of our caliber."

"I'm not, but here's an example I didn't know," Harry suggested. "Blood magic and necromancy are not things you want just anyone to be able to study, but you can open a line of communication with the dead for just a couple minutes with a cost of two drops of blood and no other adverse affects. That's it. Two drops. Magical portraits require a remarkably similar procedure with the living but for them it's legal and acceptable. Why not allow a murder victim to identify his attacker in a carefully controlled courtroom environment? Why not allow families a safe way to say goodbye?"

"That is never all those magics are used for," Albus pointed out for the sake of argument.

"I know," Harry admitted. "But that's the idea. No magic is forbidden if it doesn't impinge on others' freedoms or rights. I'm not advocating anarchy or a free for all, but merely governmental oversight and regulation. Setting up a system where a wizard like you or I can prove and establish that we have the capability to safely explore an arcane field of magic, and are then authorized to use it."

"That would take a lot of work," Albus commented.

Harry shrugged. "Right now the government's regulating just a few specific things like animagi registration or apparition licensing. We're saying instead of covering a few small exceptions, cover the broader areas."

"As proud as wizards are, you know they won't take kindly to being officially ranked by power and ability," Albus added.

"True," Harry said. "But that's because a bunch of pompous weak arses think the world is entitled to cater to them due to their birthright. All of this will undoubtedly be an ongoing debate."

"I find myself relaxing," Albus admitted. "And looking forward to focusing on Hogwarts."

"So you're in?"

"I am willing to second your nomination," Albus agreed. "In exchange for Lord Slytherin's assistance and hands off approach at Hogwarts."

"An occasional pinkie here and there, but hands off," Harry agreed.

Albus nodded in acquiescence. "And I wouldn't mind getting a crack at that duel behind closed doors. It would give me an opportunity to teach you how to not waste so much energy so quickly."

"Yeah, yeah," Harry grumbled feeling slightly embarrassed over his reliance on pepper-up potions.

Albus was smiling and fighting his instinctual need to know everything. "A fifty year plan?"

"Oh lordy," Harry shook his head. "You wouldn't believe some of the things he wants to do."

"Do tell," Albus urged.

Harry considered it and decided. "Okay, this one is probably… twenty years down the line and will require international assistance."

Albus interjected, "The war with Voldemort has not earned us very good relations with the rest of the world."

"Probably why it's twenty years away," Harry said. "But basically, he thinks that a few European Ministries working together can pitch in and… well, buy the ruins of Atlantis from the merfolk."

Albus' eyes widened having only heard the rumor that the merfolk knew the location of Atlantis.

"Yeah," Harry agreed. "He doesn't think the resources exist to recreate it, but that we could fix the island enough to get it back up into the sky. It comes from a time when they weren't any satellites or airplanes, so it'll be a warder's dream and a diplomatic nightmare. Especially if access is restricted to only the most powerful and intelligent."

"Good lord," Albus blinked.

Harry shrugged indifferent. "I'm still not completely convinced that he's not trying to build an army of super-wizards to conquer the world from the sky with that one. But hey, time will tell, right?"

"Harry," Albus pleaded as he cleaned his glasses out of habit. "Perhaps you should exercise more restraint in revealing the frightening details for the future you and your cohort have planned."

"Perhaps I should," Harry agreed, suspecting he'd already revealed more than Tom would have liked. "But I know it's not escaped your notice that our biggest obstacle is going to be overcoming the ignorance of people and the irrational cultural taboos. That fight begins here, in educating the students and turning Hogwarts into an institution where people don't just learn magic, but they learn to love magic and be challenged by it."

"You don't think we do that now?" Albus asked curiously.

"I think," Harry considered his words carefully. "I think you've taught them how to survive in the face of war, stressing defense and its applications in all the other disciplines."

Albus inclined his head in agreement.

"And I think you have the rest of this year and most of summer to figure out exactly what changes you want to make. If it's significant, you may have to sell me on the idea, but we'll make it happen."

"Headmaster! Headmaster!" the frantic voice of the Deputy Headmistress called out as she rushed up the stairs.

Albus glanced at Harry worriedly. "Minerva, what is it? What's the matter?"

Minerva glanced at Harry sitting there calmly and explained. "It's the castle. All of it."

"What?" Albus asked, sensing nothing through the wards.

"It's," she leaned forward and whispered in horror. "It's green."

Albus hurried to his window and peered around the edge to see the towers and walls had all changed to an unmistakable bright kelly green. "Harry!"

"I should go," Harry shouted as he ran down the steps. His first impulse had been to apparate away but he wasn't ready to reveal that one just yet. "I'll talk to you later, Albus!"

"Harry! Get back here!" Albus yelled. "Change it back, Harry. This isn't hands off!"

Harry's mix of running away and walking nonchalantly had him determinedly power-walking to the entrance hall. He looked to his left as a familiar man came barreling up from the dungeons in a remarkably similar power-walk.

"Sirius?"

"Hey Harry," Sirius said moving way too briskly to call it simply walking.

"What are you doing?"

Sirius smiled brightly. "It's possible I may have been watching an engorging ward in action that was secretly cast over Snivelly's office doorframe. What are you doing?"

Harry grinned in step with his godfather. "It's possible I may have turned Hogwarts green."

"That was you!" Sirius cheered before thinking it over. They both slowed to a walk when they reached open air. "Of course that was you. Hey, I was thinking of messing with Narcissa."

"Yeah?"

"Bellatrix says Narcissa won't answer her letters. I guess she's all snippy about her husband's many disgraces and the arrest of her son."

"The nerve of some people."

"Yeah, well," Sirius grinned. "She's collecting a fat insurance settlement for the loss of their family safe. Tonks was thinking 'Narcissa' could be spotted illegally selling items she claimed lost in the fire."

"That's cold."

Sirius shrugged. "Tonks has a bit of a mean streak."

"Yeah," Harry nodded. "They install those at the auror academy."

"Really?"

Harry sent an invisible finger to poke Sirius in the eye but it crashed into an invisible ward that flickered in and out of view.

"Ha-ha!" Sirius cheered. "Never again shall you-aahh!"

Harry rolled his eyes at the futility of Sirius' attempts at protection and quickly pinched the back of Sirius' knees. He crumpled immediately, flopping backwards with an awkward yelp.

"Oh come on," Sirius shouted indignantly as he struggled to his feet. "How fair is that?"

"I suppose I could've pounded my way through that little ward band, but if I'm not careful about when it collapses I might push your eyeball into your brain."

"That would be bad," Sirius commented dusting his robe off. "Here's a thought to twist your pickle: if you hadn't saved Ginny in the Chamber of Secrets, you could've had teenage Tom Riddle easily clean up a bodiless Voldemort."

"A Riddleasley?" Harry posited. "Can you even imagine how obsessed with me he would have been?"

"Hey!" an angry ghost appeared to defend herself. "Ooh! Are we going to the Hog's Head?"

"Ginny," Harry whined as he made sure no one was looking.

"Here dementor, dementor, dementor," Ginny called out. She covered her translucent mouth with her hands and proceeded to make a rasping noise that sounded vaguely like a strangled penguin.

"Ginny, get outta here," Harry snapped.

"Make me," she pouted before turning towards the forest and making the same strange noise again.

Harry growled slightly and Ginny's ghostly body disappeared from view with a pop.

"Hey Harry," Sirius wondered while glancing over his shoulder. "Was that really a dementor call?"

"I doubt it."

"I have a hypothetical question." Sirius was doing a poor job of concealing his concern. "How much justifiable jealousy is permitted before I turn into a woman?"

Harry arched an eyebrow at his godfather. "If you have to ask, you're a woman. So spit it out already."

"We can't do our thing together anymore," Sirius said thinking the glory of their thieving days had passed. "You're magically bound to a pair of manipulative bastards-"

"I thought you liked them," Harry interrupted.

"I do," Sirius asserted. "They're still manipulative bastards. Moony is a vindictive asshole and I like him well enough."

"Okay," Harry conceded.

"But it feels like we're not going to have nearly as much to do with each other," Sirius said, trying not to pout.

"Padfoot, I'm not kicking you out of the new Slytherin ancestral home or anything."

"Oi!" Sirius shouted. "That's my house!"

"And we've still got our gift."

"The ointment will clear that up."

"Not that gift," Harry chided. "Alright, here's an idea. There's a dueling tournament in Rome in about a month. Top two spots get automatic invitations to the world championships."

"You'd kill me."

"I was thinking the pairs division actually."

Sirius was intrigued. "That could be fun. But it's a little… civilized."

"There's always the rumors about the Vatican while we're there."

"Now we're talking," Sirius agreed. "I was also considering some alternate outlets for our talents."

"Yeah?"

Sirius nodded. "I know the vaults would be either impossible or more trouble than they're worth, but what would you think about breaking into the lowest levels of Gringotts-"

"Sirius," Harry said tiredly in a manner reminiscent of Albus.

"-and stealing a dragon," Sirius finished. "Or two."

Harry sighed. "You know we're supposed to stay out of trouble."

"You're the one tantalizing me with rumors of the Catholic Church's secret stash," Sirius argued.

"That's out of the country," Harry argued. "It doesn't count."

"I thought you might say that," Sirius happily agreed. "And when I did a little dragon-snatching recon, I just happened to have made a copy of all of Gringotts planned future excavation projects in Greece and Egypt."

"You want to go tomb raiding?" Harry asked. "You know curse-breaking isn't the same thing as bypassing modern wards."

"It's similar-ish," Sirius defended.

"You know what could be a lot of fun?" Harry rhetorically asked. "I was thinking we could grab a great big bag of gillyweed-"

"What kind of weed?"

"Gilly, Sirius," Harry said shaking his head. "Just take a whole bunch of it, a couple of kits, and then we could scour some hard to reach ocean floors for sunken ships and buried treasure."

"Booty?" Sirius asked excitedly.

"It can be part of a worldwide tour of nudist beaches," Harry said with a smile. "And there are some pretty scary creatures if we go deep enough."

"In the ocean too," Sirius added.

"Yes, Padfoot," Harry agreed before noticing his godfather was still hesitating. "What's got sand in your vagina now?"

Sirius grinned before making a puppy dog face. "See it's nice that we still can do stuff together, but I was thinking there's this thing called a charm of brotherhood."

"I'm not doing another of those," Harry insisted. "It's weird enough feeling both when I'm talking to one of them about the other. If they were ever in the same room with me, it'd feel like bad sex."

Harry saw Sirius was still pouting. "But you know what we could do is to make an official blood tie between the Houses of Slytherin and Black."

"What's that do?" Sirius asked curiously.

"For one, as the two family Lords, we would legally be blood brothers," Harry explained. "That's way more than any charm."

They'd arrived at the Hog's Head and Sirius held the door open for Harry. "I think I'd like that."

"Will that soothe your overdeveloped feminine side?"

Sirius just smiled and nodded. He pulled Harry over to the side and turned him away from the bar. "Listen Harry."

Harry saw Sirius was still showing emotion and began to wonder if Moony had doused him with a potion or maybe estrogen.

"Things all around us are always going to be changing." Sirius put a comforting hand on Harry's shoulder and gently explained, "And I just want you to know…"

Harry had his back to the bar and no warning before the charm activated and a magical boot swung up into his twig and giggleberries with enough force to lift him off the ground. Harry caught a glimpse of James Potter's smiling face as his body went limp and he fell to the floor.

Sirius shouted the victorious end of his sentence. "You got skunked by bizarro Prongs this time, bitch!"

"Oh," Harry lowly moaned as he cupped his junk. A pair of invisible magical arms grabbed onto Sirius and slammed him headfirst into the bar.

Sirius' forehead hit the brass edge with a loud boink that sent him reeling backward. He crashed into a table and was squeezing his eyes shut while twitching on his back on the floor. "What the fuck!"

James winced at the violent retaliation and began to question his role in this. He heard both Lord Blacks groaning on the floor and noticed no one else in the bar was even paying them much attention.

A regular at the bar saw James' look of confusion. "They're always like that. No, what you gotta watch out for is when that one next to you gets some firewhiskey in him."

"What?" James gasped turning to his son in surprise.

"Moe," Jimmy snipped. "Shut it!"

Moe just laughed and pointed at Jimmy. "I saw this one beat himself up. Punched his own face purple. Damnedest thing."

"Fucking hell, Harry. I think you knocked my brain loose," Sirius said as he made his way back to his feet. "Are we cool?"

Harry was taking slow deliberate steps in an effort to walk it off. "Yeah, we're good."

"Lovely," James said rubbing his hands together. "Because my dinner arrived while we were waiting under the invisibility cloak."

"Oh no, no, no," Harry said, shaking his head. "I'm not done with you yet, Potter."

James saw the look in Harry's eyes and felt the eager glares of most everyone else in the room. "Right. You know I just remembered some paperwork I forgot to finish."

"Dad?" Jimmy said as he saw his father briskly heading for the door. "What about your food?"

James just waved over his shoulder without turning around. "You can keep my sandwich!"

Harry furrowed his brow and tilted his head in thought.

"Is that turkey?" Sirius asked, grabbing half of James' sandwich.

"I'm getting the weirdest feeling of déjà vu," Harry said, grabbing the other half of sandwich. He plopped down into a chair, sitting across from Sirius and Jimmy.

"Any idea from what?" Sirius asked in between bites.

Harry had the answer on the tip of his tongue, but he just couldn't quite get it. "No," he said with a resigned sigh. He chewed up another bite of his sandwich. "It's like I can hear those words, over and over: you can keep my sandwich."

"With all the déjà vu, do you guys ever think that maybe we really did play the Obliviate game?" Jimmy wondered.

Harry glanced at the little brother he never had. "We play it all the time. And yes Jimmy, you're horrible at it."

"Really?"

"It's usually after a few rounds of the Gullibility game."

"Okay now you're just making fun of me," Jimmy insisted, before worriedly clarifying, "Right?"

"Why would you remember 'You can keep my sandwich?'" Sirius repeated.

"I don't know," Harry pleaded. "If I did, it'd just be a memory, or with my luck a traumatic flashback."

"It's a fucking retarded line."

"Thank you, Sirius."

"I'm just saying it'd never make it onto a T-shirt."

"You're still talking."

"But there's nothing memorable about that line."

"You're only harping on it because I can't remember it and you know that frustrates the hell out of me."

Sirius grinned. "And your point is?"

"Hang on," Jimmy interrupted. "I don't even know how to cast a memory charm."

"That's probably why you're so awful at the game," Harry retorted.

"Hmmph," Jimmy grumbled. "And here I was going to tell you the significance of your line."

"Oh come on," Harry whined. "Tell me."

Jimmy thrust a victorious fist into the air. He made the low rumbling sound of an approving crowd. "Ladies and gentlemen, there's a new leader in the Gullibility game."

"All because he can't remember the line 'You can keep my sandwich.'" Sirius happily reminded.

"One of these days," Harry warned them both. "One of these days I'm just gonna snap, go dark, and kill you all. You realize that, right?"

"Not today, Harry," Sirius said.

"No, not today," Harry agreed. "But tomorrow's a distinct possibility."

THE END

Author's Note: I struggled a little, rewriting the last scene a number of times before finally realizing that after well over two hundred thousand words, I didn't have to end it with the perfect zinger as much as I had to end it. This fic has been a lot of work and in my mind will always be remembered as the story that was interrupted by my Mom kicking cancer's ass. It was intended to be different from the usual Harry Potter fanfiction because Voldemort was a minor sub-plot in a story about the relationship between Harry and Sirius. A relationship where instead of Sirius becoming the new James to Harry (father son), it was about Harry becoming the new James to Sirius (best friends).

I think I accomplished my goal, but I'd love to hear any final comments, thoughts, or opinions you are willing to share. Whether you've been waiting on updates eagerly, or were one of the lucky ones to read the whole thing straight through without suffering the anguish of my cliffhangers, a little more feedback will make me feel loved, appreciated, grateful, stroke my ego, make me a better writer, or most likely, inspire me to write more. And feel free to thank the excellent alphas and betas helping me straighten out the mess of ideas that went into this fic: Jim, IP, Chuck, Chris, Rob, Sean, JJ, and the others I will edit in here as soon as I remember them.

Since I've been hearing the calls already, I shall say there are no plans for a sequel here and I'd mark it as 'unlikely' to ever have one. As for what's next for me, I will admit to being taken in by an idea for an original story in a universe of my own making. I'm going to give that a try for a while, but it is inevitable more fanfic bunnies will bug me until I write them. Could be a little while before I get to them as I want to give a fair shot to writing about my own characters, but I'll be back with a new story sometime. Thanks for all the reviews and actually reading this long ass author's note. Now about that one last review I asked for...